<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Yearly Recap on Another Year of Books</title>
    <link>https://anotheryearofbooks.com/categories/yearly-recap/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Yearly Recap on Another Year of Books</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 30 Dec 2022 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://anotheryearofbooks.com/categories/yearly-recap/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Another Year of Books: The 2022 Recap</title>
      <link>https://anotheryearofbooks.com/2022/12/another-year-of-books-the-2022-recap/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 30 Dec 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://anotheryearofbooks.com/2022/12/another-year-of-books-the-2022-recap/</guid>
      <description>And we are back! Briefly, but we’re back. It feels good to be here.
Now, I know it’s been a while - an entire year to be exact. I’m wondering if I’ll even remember how to write a post. Then after I write it, will I remember the steps to publish it? Good news - it looks like I did.
It’s been a year of no posts and no book photos.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Another Year of Books: The 2021 Recap</title>
      <link>https://anotheryearofbooks.com/2021/12/another-year-of-books-the-2021-recap/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 31 Dec 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://anotheryearofbooks.com/2021/12/another-year-of-books-the-2021-recap/</guid>
      <description>Since 2017, I’ve been writing down what books I read. Another Year of Books started in 2018, but the counting started the year before. Until 2021, 2017 remained the winner with 62 books read. This year, however, beats 2017 only slightly - in the end, 64 books were consumed. What a year.
The end of the year means it’s that time - to pick the best, the worst, and the ones I think you should hear about in a recap.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Another Year of Books: The 2020 Recap</title>
      <link>https://anotheryearofbooks.com/2020/12/another-year-of-books-the-2020-recap/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 31 Dec 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://anotheryearofbooks.com/2020/12/another-year-of-books-the-2020-recap/</guid>
      <description>2020 - what a year, am I right? It’s been a tough one, especially this holiday season. Thankfully, it’s coming to a close and the future is looking like it will be more normal. But then again, isn’t less normal sometimes more fun? Maybe, maybe not; it probably depends on what that less normal looks like.
The end of the year means it&amp;rsquo;s time to look back on the books I’ve read, pick a few winners, pick a few losers, and round out the year with a recap, just as I have done in 2018 and 2019.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Another Year of Books: The 2019 Recap</title>
      <link>https://anotheryearofbooks.com/2020/01/another-year-of-books-the-2019-recap/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 Jan 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://anotheryearofbooks.com/2020/01/another-year-of-books-the-2019-recap/</guid>
      <description>Another year has already come and gone. I can’t believe it. I still can’t believe that I read all 52 books in 2019. I was filled with doubt and, mostly, annoyance at myself. But then, after I finished, all I felt was pride, and a little tired. This one is always the hardest… the recap. Which books were the best? Which were the worst? Which books are waiting for Hallmark to pick them up?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Another Year of Books: The 2018 Recap</title>
      <link>https://anotheryearofbooks.com/2018/12/another-year-of-books-the-2018-recap/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 28 Dec 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://anotheryearofbooks.com/2018/12/another-year-of-books-the-2018-recap/</guid>
      <description>Well, 2019 is approaching, surely and quickly, and there’s nothing we can do to slow it down. As 2018 comes to a close, and the goal is officially complete (and then some), it felt like it was time to think back, remember to the good days (or reads), and the bad ones (again, or reads), especially when we are all feeling like this:
I had to dig a little deep to remember which books I liked the most, because there were so many of them.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
