<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>2018 Reads on Another Year of Books</title>
    <link>https://anotheryearofbooks.com/categories/2018-reads/</link>
    <description>Recent content in 2018 Reads on Another Year of Books</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 28 Dec 2018 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://anotheryearofbooks.com/categories/2018-reads/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Another Year of Books: The 2018 Recap</title>
      <link>https://anotheryearofbooks.com/2018/12/another-year-of-books-the-2018-recap/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 28 Dec 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://anotheryearofbooks.com/2018/12/another-year-of-books-the-2018-recap/</guid>
      <description>Well, 2019 is approaching, surely and quickly, and there’s nothing we can do to slow it down. As 2018 comes to a close, and the goal is officially complete (and then some), it felt like it was time to think back, remember to the good days (or reads), and the bad ones (again, or reads), especially when we are all feeling like this:
I had to dig a little deep to remember which books I liked the most, because there were so many of them.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>They’re Still Rich… and Still Crazy</title>
      <link>https://anotheryearofbooks.com/2018/04/theyre-still-rich-and-still-crazy/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 15 Apr 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://anotheryearofbooks.com/2018/04/theyre-still-rich-and-still-crazy/</guid>
      <description>I know it has been awhile - almost 2 weeks to be exact. But, when I went to the library (not at lunch this time – big change for me!) when I was almost done with my last read, I picked up not 1, but 2 books, and they were meant to be read and talked about together. So here you go – a two for one post.
 Book Read: China Rich Girlfriend &amp;amp; Rich People Problems</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>This Next Book is Insane(ly Good)</title>
      <link>https://anotheryearofbooks.com/2018/02/this-next-book-is-insanely-good/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Feb 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://anotheryearofbooks.com/2018/02/this-next-book-is-insanely-good/</guid>
      <description>My sister is getting married. My best friend’s sister is also getting married. Yesterday when we met for lunch, we were comparing the size of the guest lists. But this book trumped us - the wedding of the century with 888 guests. Eight hundred and eighty eight. Wow, sorry Meghan for commenting on the size of yours.
 Book Read: Crazy Rich Asians
Author: Kevin Kwan
Number of Books Read: 11</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>