<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>2018 Reads on Another Year of Books</title>
    <link>https://anotheryearofbooks.com/categories/2018-reads/</link>
    <description>Recent content in 2018 Reads on Another Year of Books</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 28 Dec 2018 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://anotheryearofbooks.com/categories/2018-reads/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Another Year of Books: The 2018 Recap</title>
      <link>https://anotheryearofbooks.com/2018/12/another-year-of-books-the-2018-recap/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 28 Dec 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://anotheryearofbooks.com/2018/12/another-year-of-books-the-2018-recap/</guid>
      <description>Well, 2019 is approaching, surely and quickly, and there’s nothing we can do to slow it down. As 2018 comes to a close, and the goal is officially complete (and then some), it felt like it was time to think back, remember to the good days (or reads), and the bad ones (again, or reads), especially when we are all feeling like this:
I had to dig a little deep to remember which books I liked the most, because there were so many of them.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Class Dismissed.</title>
      <link>https://anotheryearofbooks.com/2018/12/class-dismissed./</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 16 Dec 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://anotheryearofbooks.com/2018/12/class-dismissed./</guid>
      <description>In January, it all began with an Elin Hilderbrand book. Well, actually it began with multiple Elin Hilderbrand books. It seemed fitting that my 52nd read should be her latest winter novel. On Black Friday, thanks to Amazon, it was purchased. Then it laid around waiting to be read.
So without further ado, the 52nd read of 2018.
 Book Read: Winter in Paradise
Author: Elin Hilderbrand
Number of Books Read: 52</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Small Admissions? I Think Not</title>
      <link>https://anotheryearofbooks.com/2018/12/small-admissions-i-think-not/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 10 Dec 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://anotheryearofbooks.com/2018/12/small-admissions-i-think-not/</guid>
      <description>This past week seemed to calm down. Only plan was to do some Christmas shopping. Thank goodness my list is small. Maybe next year everyone will get a print out of this blog accompanied by a book? Just a thought.
 Book Read: Small Admissions
Author: Amy Poeppel
Number of Books Read: 51
 After being dumped at the Paris airport by her “almost” fiancé, Kate finds herself in a serious slump.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Harder than a Bag of Bricks, This One</title>
      <link>https://anotheryearofbooks.com/2018/12/harder-than-a-bag-of-bricks-this-one/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 04 Dec 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://anotheryearofbooks.com/2018/12/harder-than-a-bag-of-bricks-this-one/</guid>
      <description>We all know the holiday season is busy. It never seems like there is enough time to shop, bake, cook and wrap. Add in a book that seems to drag. Trust me, it does not help this time of year.
 Book Read: How Hard Can It Be?
Author: Allison Pearson
Number of Books Read: 50
 Kate Reddy’s life has changed - her adorable kids are now teenagers obsessed with video games and selfies, her family relocated to a house in need of serious work, and her husband, Richard, has decided that bicycling and therapy are better than his job as an architect.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A Power Couple Writes a Book</title>
      <link>https://anotheryearofbooks.com/2018/11/a-power-couple-writes-a-book/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 24 Nov 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://anotheryearofbooks.com/2018/11/a-power-couple-writes-a-book/</guid>
      <description>title: &amp;lsquo;A Power Couple Writes a Book&amp;rsquo; date: 2018-11-24T06:14:00.000-08:00 draft: false When I found myself at the library one day at lunch (again), I couldn&amp;rsquo;t not pick this one up. I mean look at the cover above.
See what I mean?
It’s Karen (also Tammy) and Ron (also the Plumber) telling their story. Each has their own books but this one was different. The two come together to write this one.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ignore the Long Title. It&#39;&#39;s Worth It.</title>
      <link>https://anotheryearofbooks.com/2018/11/ignore-the-long-title.-its-worth-it./</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 18 Nov 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://anotheryearofbooks.com/2018/11/ignore-the-long-title.-its-worth-it./</guid>
      <description>It’s becoming more and more difficult to pick which book I read. Since I’m on the last leg of 52 for the year, I feel as if I should make sure they are good ones (PS - this one worked out in my favor). But my time for reading 52 this year is quickly dwindling. I feel like I woke up one morning and it was Halloween, and the next thing I knew I was figuring out what I’m doing on Turkey Day.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What’s Behind Door 1?</title>
      <link>https://anotheryearofbooks.com/2018/11/whats-behind-door-1/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 Nov 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://anotheryearofbooks.com/2018/11/whats-behind-door-1/</guid>
      <description>Surprise! It’s already mid-November. The year is continuing to fly by. I’m looking forward to the Christmas cookies, and Thanksgiving dinner. Not looking forward to thinking about Christmas gifts. Too soon, Father Time, too soon. But on another note, not too many books left to read!

 Book Read: Surprise Me
Author: Sophie Kinsella
Number of Books Read: 47
 Sylvie and Dan are comfortable. Comfortable in their marriage, their jobs, and at home with their two daughters.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Queue “Save The Last Dance for Me”</title>
      <link>https://anotheryearofbooks.com/2018/11/queue-save-the-last-dance-for-me/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Nov 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://anotheryearofbooks.com/2018/11/queue-save-the-last-dance-for-me/</guid>
      <description>I saw this book at Target once, and added it to my list to read. Target is great for this by the way - gives you an excuse to go pick up a few items you need. I then forgot I saw it at Half Price Books, bought it, and put it on my bookshelf…I then borrowed it from the library and read that copy.
It took me until 5 days after I finished this book (and another) to realize what I had done.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>No Sleep Till Brooklyn</title>
      <link>https://anotheryearofbooks.com/2018/10/no-sleep-till-brooklyn/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 30 Oct 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://anotheryearofbooks.com/2018/10/no-sleep-till-brooklyn/</guid>
      <description>It’s the end of October, and we are on book number 45. I can see the end in sight - pending I get to the library at lunch today because I have nothing to read on the bus. Can we do it? I’m thinking we can.
 Book Read: Halsey Street
Author: Naima Coster
Number of Books Read: 45
 Penelope moves to Pittsburgh after an explosive fight with her mother, looking to make it as an artist.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Advice Found Here</title>
      <link>https://anotheryearofbooks.com/2018/10/advice-found-here/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 21 Oct 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://anotheryearofbooks.com/2018/10/advice-found-here/</guid>
      <description>It’s fall already. FALL. Time for boots, pumpkin patches, and being cold waiting for the bus. This year is flying by, as it usually does. Maybe it’s all the stuff going on, or maybe it’s because I’ve read book #44 already and can (hopefully) see the end in sight.

 Book Read: Dear Mrs. Bird
Author: AJ Pearce
Number of Books Read: 44
 It’s London in the middle of World War II.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>It’s the Final Countdown</title>
      <link>https://anotheryearofbooks.com/2018/10/its-the-final-countdown/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Oct 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://anotheryearofbooks.com/2018/10/its-the-final-countdown/</guid>
      <description>Completing this read means there’s less than 10 books to go until I can call this mission complete. It’s the beginning of October so I have hope. But it’s officially the final countdown. Good or bad, we read on.
 Book Read: The Woman in Cabin 10
Author: Ruth Ware
Number of Books Read: 43
 Lo is a travel journalist looking for more opportunities. When her boss is unable to make a press tour of a new luxury cruise ship, Lo is given one of the best opportunities of her career.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Did You Miss Me?</title>
      <link>https://anotheryearofbooks.com/2018/10/did-you-miss-me/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Oct 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://anotheryearofbooks.com/2018/10/did-you-miss-me/</guid>
      <description>The past two weeks have been busy, so I’ve been MIA for awhile. First my sister got married (that wore me out for days), then this next book was decently long, then there were concerts to go to, plays to usher and a new car to be bought. But we are back and after this, we only have ten more till the goal!
 
 Book Read: Miss You</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ryan Started the Fire!</title>
      <link>https://anotheryearofbooks.com/2018/09/ryan-started-the-fire/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 21 Sep 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://anotheryearofbooks.com/2018/09/ryan-started-the-fire/</guid>
      <description>“We didn&amp;rsquo;t start the fire
It was always burning
Since the world&amp;rsquo;s been turning.”
But wait, in this case, someone did start the little fires.
 Book Read: Little Fires Everywhere
Author: Celeste Ng
Number of Books Read: 41
 In Shaker Heights, everything has a purpose, and it’s planned. Shaker was built on it. When Mia Warren and her daughter Pearl arrive in town, one family will never be the same.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>You Can’t Always Get What You Want</title>
      <link>https://anotheryearofbooks.com/2018/09/you-cant-always-get-what-you-want/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 19 Sep 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://anotheryearofbooks.com/2018/09/you-cant-always-get-what-you-want/</guid>
      <description>I was supposed to pick a happier book to read for number 40. After all the suspenseful, slightly disturbing reads, my boyfriend told me it would be a good idea. This read has a happy ending but is pretty socially relevant all at the same time.
 Book Read: All We Ever Wanted
Author: Emily Giffin
Number of Books Read: 40
 Emily Giffin’s latest novel is written in the point of view of three people - Nina, whose son has done something really stupid, Tom, whose daughter is impacted by this stupidity, and Lyla, who just wants to get through high school.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Thank Goodness This Isn’t My Neighborhood</title>
      <link>https://anotheryearofbooks.com/2018/09/thank-goodness-this-isnt-my-neighborhood/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 12 Sep 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://anotheryearofbooks.com/2018/09/thank-goodness-this-isnt-my-neighborhood/</guid>
      <description>My boyfriend and I bought a townhouse a few months back, so when we say we have neighbors, they is no yard to separate us. Luckily, we like them.
 Book Read: The Couple Next Door
Author: Shari Lapena
Number of Books Read: 39
 Anne and Marco Conti go to a dinner party next door. They decide it’s best to leave their newborn daughter at home, checking on her with a clockwork-like schedule.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tell Me Something I Don’t Know</title>
      <link>https://anotheryearofbooks.com/2018/09/tell-me-something-i-dont-know/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 06 Sep 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://anotheryearofbooks.com/2018/09/tell-me-something-i-dont-know/</guid>
      <description>Imagine you think your husband is a serial killer. Actually you’re convinced he is because you keep finding evidence it may be true. How would you react?
My guess: probably not well. Not well at all.
 Book Read: Tell Me I’m Wrong
Author: Adam Croft
Number of Books Read: 38
 Megan Miller thought her life was normal. She and her husband, an elementary school teacher, seem happy with their newborn daughter.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>In The Sky With Diamonds</title>
      <link>https://anotheryearofbooks.com/2018/08/in-the-sky-with-diamonds/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 30 Aug 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://anotheryearofbooks.com/2018/08/in-the-sky-with-diamonds/</guid>
      <description>Sometimes, I don’t have a reason for picking up at pickup at the library. If it’s not a book on my ever-growing iPhone list titled “Books,” it may be someone, somewhere told me to read it. Or in this case, the cover reminds be of a Fredrik Backman novel. That alone is enough to make me read a book.
 Book Read: We Own the Sky
Author: Luke Allnutt
Number of Books Read: 37</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>That&#39;s My Name. Don&#39;t Wear It Out.</title>
      <link>https://anotheryearofbooks.com/2018/08/thats-my-name.-dont-wear-it-out./</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 24 Aug 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://anotheryearofbooks.com/2018/08/thats-my-name.-dont-wear-it-out./</guid>
      <description>Ever since I saw the movie version of The Notebook before I read the book (loved both by the way), I have always tried to read books before I watch the movie. See The Mountain Between Us as an example. This movie had serious Oscar buzz, but let’s not let that stray us from tradition here.
 Book Read: Call Me By Your Name
Author: Andre Aciman
Number of Books Read: 36</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Seven Days Can Be a Long Time</title>
      <link>https://anotheryearofbooks.com/2018/08/seven-days-can-be-a-long-time/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 12 Aug 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://anotheryearofbooks.com/2018/08/seven-days-can-be-a-long-time/</guid>
      <description>I mentioned I read two books during my weekend of relaxation in Sea Isle City. You already know I liked the first - did I like the second? Considering I read both in 6 days, you probably can guess. But let’s talk about it anyway. So picture you’re sitting here with this view, and read on!

 Book Read: Seven Days of Us
Author: Francesca Hornak
Number of Books Read: 35</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Here Comes the Bride (maybe?)</title>
      <link>https://anotheryearofbooks.com/2018/08/here-comes-the-bride-maybe/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 Aug 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://anotheryearofbooks.com/2018/08/here-comes-the-bride-maybe/</guid>
      <description>I spent this past weekend completely relaxed on vacation in Sea Isle City, NJ. My plans consisted of eating, drinking, walking, sitting in the sand with SPF 50 on, and reading a book or two. All objectives: met.
My boyfriend’s objectives: take some photos with his drone. Objective: met.

Spoiler: two books were read during the weekend - but let’s only focus on one for now.)
 Book Read: The Perfect Couple</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>They’re Still Rich… and Still Crazy</title>
      <link>https://anotheryearofbooks.com/2018/04/theyre-still-rich-and-still-crazy/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 15 Apr 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://anotheryearofbooks.com/2018/04/theyre-still-rich-and-still-crazy/</guid>
      <description>I know it has been awhile - almost 2 weeks to be exact. But, when I went to the library (not at lunch this time – big change for me!) when I was almost done with my last read, I picked up not 1, but 2 books, and they were meant to be read and talked about together. So here you go – a two for one post.
 Book Read: China Rich Girlfriend &amp;amp; Rich People Problems</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>This Next Book is Insane(ly Good)</title>
      <link>https://anotheryearofbooks.com/2018/02/this-next-book-is-insanely-good/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Feb 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://anotheryearofbooks.com/2018/02/this-next-book-is-insanely-good/</guid>
      <description>My sister is getting married. My best friend’s sister is also getting married. Yesterday when we met for lunch, we were comparing the size of the guest lists. But this book trumped us - the wedding of the century with 888 guests. Eight hundred and eighty eight. Wow, sorry Meghan for commenting on the size of yours.
 Book Read: Crazy Rich Asians
Author: Kevin Kwan
Number of Books Read: 11</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>No One is Going to Save Me... From this Book</title>
      <link>https://anotheryearofbooks.com/2018/01/no-one-is-going-to-save-me...-from-this-book/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 19 Jan 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://anotheryearofbooks.com/2018/01/no-one-is-going-to-save-me...-from-this-book/</guid>
      <description>I tend to find books as I’m wandering the library at lunch. Sometimes, if I can’t find a book on my “to read” list, I pick one based on the cover, the author, or if I saw other people looking at it. Usually, it works out pretty well. This one… I’m still not convinced that picking a book because Powell was in the author’s name was a good idea. You win some, you lose some.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>