<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>2018 Reads on Another Year of Books</title>
    <link>https://anotheryearofbooks.com/categories/2018-reads/</link>
    <description>Recent content in 2018 Reads on Another Year of Books</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 28 Dec 2018 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://anotheryearofbooks.com/categories/2018-reads/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Another Year of Books: The 2018 Recap</title>
      <link>https://anotheryearofbooks.com/2018/12/another-year-of-books-the-2018-recap/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 28 Dec 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://anotheryearofbooks.com/2018/12/another-year-of-books-the-2018-recap/</guid>
      <description>Well, 2019 is approaching, surely and quickly, and there’s nothing we can do to slow it down. As 2018 comes to a close, and the goal is officially complete (and then some), it felt like it was time to think back, remember to the good days (or reads), and the bad ones (again, or reads), especially when we are all feeling like this:
I had to dig a little deep to remember which books I liked the most, because there were so many of them.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Class Dismissed</title>
      <link>https://anotheryearofbooks.com/2018/12/class-dismissed/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 16 Dec 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://anotheryearofbooks.com/2018/12/class-dismissed/</guid>
      <description>In January, it all began with an Elin Hilderbrand book. Well, actually it began with multiple Elin Hilderbrand books. It seemed fitting that my 52nd read should be her latest winter novel. On Black Friday, thanks to Amazon, it was purchased. Then it laid around waiting to be read.
So without further ado, the 52nd read of 2018.
 Book Read: Winter in Paradise
Author: Elin Hilderbrand
Number of Books Read: 52</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Small Admissions? I Think Not</title>
      <link>https://anotheryearofbooks.com/2018/12/small-admissions-i-think-not/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 10 Dec 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://anotheryearofbooks.com/2018/12/small-admissions-i-think-not/</guid>
      <description>This past week seemed to calm down. Only plan was to do some Christmas shopping. Thank goodness my list is small. Maybe next year everyone will get a print out of this blog accompanied by a book? Just a thought.
 Book Read: Small Admissions
Author: Amy Poeppel
Number of Books Read: 51
 After being dumped at the Paris airport by her “almost” fiancé, Kate finds herself in a serious slump.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Harder than a Bag of Bricks, This One</title>
      <link>https://anotheryearofbooks.com/2018/12/harder-than-a-bag-of-bricks-this-one/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 04 Dec 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://anotheryearofbooks.com/2018/12/harder-than-a-bag-of-bricks-this-one/</guid>
      <description>We all know the holiday season is busy. It never seems like there is enough time to shop, bake, cook and wrap. Add in a book that seems to drag. Trust me, it does not help this time of year.
 Book Read: How Hard Can It Be?
Author: Allison Pearson
Number of Books Read: 50
 Kate Reddy’s life has changed - her adorable kids are now teenagers obsessed with video games and selfies, her family relocated to a house in need of serious work, and her husband, Richard, has decided that bicycling and therapy are better than his job as an architect.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A Power Couple Writes a Book</title>
      <link>https://anotheryearofbooks.com/2018/11/a-power-couple-writes-a-book/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 24 Nov 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://anotheryearofbooks.com/2018/11/a-power-couple-writes-a-book/</guid>
      <description>title: &amp;lsquo;A Power Couple Writes a Book&amp;rsquo; date: 2018-11-24T06:14:00.000-08:00 draft: false When I found myself at the library one day at lunch (again), I couldn&amp;rsquo;t not pick this one up. I mean look at the cover above.
See what I mean?
It’s Karen (also Tammy) and Ron (also the Plumber) telling their story. Each has their own books but this one was different. The two come together to write this one.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ignore the Long Title. It&#39;&#39;s Worth It.</title>
      <link>https://anotheryearofbooks.com/2018/11/ignore-the-long-title.-its-worth-it./</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 18 Nov 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://anotheryearofbooks.com/2018/11/ignore-the-long-title.-its-worth-it./</guid>
      <description>It’s becoming more and more difficult to pick which book I read. Since I’m on the last leg of 52 for the year, I feel as if I should make sure they are good ones (PS - this one worked out in my favor). But my time for reading 52 this year is quickly dwindling. I feel like I woke up one morning and it was Halloween, and the next thing I knew I was figuring out what I’m doing on Turkey Day.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What’s Behind Door 1?</title>
      <link>https://anotheryearofbooks.com/2018/11/whats-behind-door-1/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 Nov 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://anotheryearofbooks.com/2018/11/whats-behind-door-1/</guid>
      <description>Surprise! It’s already mid-November. The year is continuing to fly by. I’m looking forward to the Christmas cookies, and Thanksgiving dinner. Not looking forward to thinking about Christmas gifts. Too soon, Father Time, too soon. But on another note, not too many books left to read!

 Book Read: Surprise Me
Author: Sophie Kinsella
Number of Books Read: 47
 Sylvie and Dan are comfortable. Comfortable in their marriage, their jobs, and at home with their two daughters.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Queue “Save The Last Dance for Me”</title>
      <link>https://anotheryearofbooks.com/2018/11/queue-save-the-last-dance-for-me/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Nov 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://anotheryearofbooks.com/2018/11/queue-save-the-last-dance-for-me/</guid>
      <description>I saw this book at Target once, and added it to my list to read. Target is great for this by the way - gives you an excuse to go pick up a few items you need. I then forgot I saw it at Half Price Books, bought it, and put it on my bookshelf…I then borrowed it from the library and read that copy.
It took me until 5 days after I finished this book (and another) to realize what I had done.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>No Sleep Till Brooklyn</title>
      <link>https://anotheryearofbooks.com/2018/10/no-sleep-till-brooklyn/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 30 Oct 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://anotheryearofbooks.com/2018/10/no-sleep-till-brooklyn/</guid>
      <description>It’s the end of October, and we are on book number 45. I can see the end in sight - pending I get to the library at lunch today because I have nothing to read on the bus. Can we do it? I’m thinking we can.
 Book Read: Halsey Street
Author: Naima Coster
Number of Books Read: 45
 Penelope moves to Pittsburgh after an explosive fight with her mother, looking to make it as an artist.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Advice Found Here</title>
      <link>https://anotheryearofbooks.com/2018/10/advice-found-here/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 21 Oct 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://anotheryearofbooks.com/2018/10/advice-found-here/</guid>
      <description>It’s fall already. FALL. Time for boots, pumpkin patches, and being cold waiting for the bus. This year is flying by, as it usually does. Maybe it’s all the stuff going on, or maybe it’s because I’ve read book #44 already and can (hopefully) see the end in sight.

 Book Read: Dear Mrs. Bird
Author: AJ Pearce
Number of Books Read: 44
 It’s London in the middle of World War II.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>It’s the Final Countdown</title>
      <link>https://anotheryearofbooks.com/2018/10/its-the-final-countdown/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Oct 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://anotheryearofbooks.com/2018/10/its-the-final-countdown/</guid>
      <description>Completing this read means there’s less than 10 books to go until I can call this mission complete. It’s the beginning of October so I have hope. But it’s officially the final countdown. Good or bad, we read on.
 Book Read: The Woman in Cabin 10
Author: Ruth Ware
Number of Books Read: 43
 Lo is a travel journalist looking for more opportunities. When her boss is unable to make a press tour of a new luxury cruise ship, Lo is given one of the best opportunities of her career.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Did You Miss Me?</title>
      <link>https://anotheryearofbooks.com/2018/10/did-you-miss-me/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Oct 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://anotheryearofbooks.com/2018/10/did-you-miss-me/</guid>
      <description>The past two weeks have been busy, so I’ve been MIA for awhile. First my sister got married (that wore me out for days), then this next book was decently long, then there were concerts to go to, plays to usher and a new car to be bought. But we are back and after this, we only have ten more till the goal!
 
 Book Read: Miss You</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ryan Started the Fire!</title>
      <link>https://anotheryearofbooks.com/2018/09/ryan-started-the-fire/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 21 Sep 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://anotheryearofbooks.com/2018/09/ryan-started-the-fire/</guid>
      <description>“We didn&amp;rsquo;t start the fire
It was always burning
Since the world&amp;rsquo;s been turning.”
But wait, in this case, someone did start the little fires.
 Book Read: Little Fires Everywhere
Author: Celeste Ng
Number of Books Read: 41
 In Shaker Heights, everything has a purpose, and it’s planned. Shaker was built on it. When Mia Warren and her daughter Pearl arrive in town, one family will never be the same.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>You Can’t Always Get What You Want</title>
      <link>https://anotheryearofbooks.com/2018/09/you-cant-always-get-what-you-want/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 19 Sep 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://anotheryearofbooks.com/2018/09/you-cant-always-get-what-you-want/</guid>
      <description>I was supposed to pick a happier book to read for number 40. After all the suspenseful, slightly disturbing reads, my boyfriend told me it would be a good idea. This read has a happy ending but is pretty socially relevant all at the same time.
 Book Read: All We Ever Wanted
Author: Emily Giffin
Number of Books Read: 40
 Emily Giffin’s latest novel is written in the point of view of three people - Nina, whose son has done something really stupid, Tom, whose daughter is impacted by this stupidity, and Lyla, who just wants to get through high school.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Thank Goodness This Isn’t My Neighborhood</title>
      <link>https://anotheryearofbooks.com/2018/09/thank-goodness-this-isnt-my-neighborhood/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 12 Sep 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://anotheryearofbooks.com/2018/09/thank-goodness-this-isnt-my-neighborhood/</guid>
      <description>My boyfriend and I bought a townhouse a few months back, so when we say we have neighbors, they is no yard to separate us. Luckily, we like them.
 Book Read: The Couple Next Door
Author: Shari Lapena
Number of Books Read: 39
 Anne and Marco Conti go to a dinner party next door. They decide it’s best to leave their newborn daughter at home, checking on her with a clockwork-like schedule.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tell Me Something I Don’t Know</title>
      <link>https://anotheryearofbooks.com/2018/09/tell-me-something-i-dont-know/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 06 Sep 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://anotheryearofbooks.com/2018/09/tell-me-something-i-dont-know/</guid>
      <description>Imagine you think your husband is a serial killer. Actually you’re convinced he is because you keep finding evidence it may be true. How would you react?
My guess: probably not well. Not well at all.
 Book Read: Tell Me I’m Wrong
Author: Adam Croft
Number of Books Read: 38
 Megan Miller thought her life was normal. She and her husband, an elementary school teacher, seem happy with their newborn daughter.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>In The Sky With Diamonds</title>
      <link>https://anotheryearofbooks.com/2018/08/in-the-sky-with-diamonds/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 30 Aug 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://anotheryearofbooks.com/2018/08/in-the-sky-with-diamonds/</guid>
      <description>Sometimes, I don’t have a reason for picking up at pickup at the library. If it’s not a book on my ever-growing iPhone list titled “Books,” it may be someone, somewhere told me to read it. Or in this case, the cover reminds be of a Fredrik Backman novel. That alone is enough to make me read a book.
 Book Read: We Own the Sky
Author: Luke Allnutt
Number of Books Read: 37</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>That&#39;s My Name. Don&#39;t Wear It Out.</title>
      <link>https://anotheryearofbooks.com/2018/08/thats-my-name.-dont-wear-it-out./</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 24 Aug 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://anotheryearofbooks.com/2018/08/thats-my-name.-dont-wear-it-out./</guid>
      <description>Ever since I saw the movie version of The Notebook before I read the book (loved both by the way), I have always tried to read books before I watch the movie. See The Mountain Between Us as an example. This movie had serious Oscar buzz, but let’s not let that stray us from tradition here.
 Book Read: Call Me By Your Name
Author: Andre Aciman
Number of Books Read: 36</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Seven Days Can Be a Long Time</title>
      <link>https://anotheryearofbooks.com/2018/08/seven-days-can-be-a-long-time/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 12 Aug 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://anotheryearofbooks.com/2018/08/seven-days-can-be-a-long-time/</guid>
      <description>I mentioned I read two books during my weekend of relaxation in Sea Isle City. You already know I liked the first - did I like the second? Considering I read both in 6 days, you probably can guess. But let’s talk about it anyway. So picture you’re sitting here with this view, and read on!

 Book Read: Seven Days of Us
Author: Francesca Hornak
Number of Books Read: 35</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Here Comes the Bride (maybe?)</title>
      <link>https://anotheryearofbooks.com/2018/08/here-comes-the-bride-maybe/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 Aug 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://anotheryearofbooks.com/2018/08/here-comes-the-bride-maybe/</guid>
      <description>I spent this past weekend completely relaxed on vacation in Sea Isle City, NJ. My plans consisted of eating, drinking, walking, sitting in the sand with SPF 50 on, and reading a book or two. All objectives: met.
My boyfriend’s objectives: take some photos with his drone. Objective: met.

Spoiler: two books were read during the weekend - but let’s only focus on one for now.)
 Book Read: The Perfect Couple</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Teach Them to Fly (or Roar)</title>
      <link>https://anotheryearofbooks.com/2018/08/teach-them-to-fly-or-roar/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 Aug 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://anotheryearofbooks.com/2018/08/teach-them-to-fly-or-roar/</guid>
      <description>Most of us understand being in a sports town. Whether it’s football, soccer, hockey, curling or any other sort, we understand it. Beartown looks like Pittsburgh on steroids when it comes to hockey. And that’s saying something.
 Book Read: Us Against You
Author: Fredrik Backman
Number of Books Read: 33
 Spoilers ahead: stop here, go borrow Beartown from your local library, then come back to finish reading this post.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Week and a Half I Wanted a Book to Fall Apart</title>
      <link>https://anotheryearofbooks.com/2018/07/the-week-and-a-half-i-wanted-a-book-to-fall-apart/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Jul 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://anotheryearofbooks.com/2018/07/the-week-and-a-half-i-wanted-a-book-to-fall-apart/</guid>
      <description>I very rarely give up on a book. I can probably actually count on one hand how many times I haven&amp;rsquo;t finished a book I started. So I forced myself to finish book 32, with many complaints about it along the way.
 Book Read: The Summer We Fell Apart
Author: Robin Antalek
Number of Books Read: 32
 I picked this one up at the library book sale, and luckily only spent a single dollar on it.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Queue the Pretty Little Liars Theme Song</title>
      <link>https://anotheryearofbooks.com/2018/07/queue-the-pretty-little-liars-theme-song/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Jul 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://anotheryearofbooks.com/2018/07/queue-the-pretty-little-liars-theme-song/</guid>
      <description>“Got a secret, Can you keep it? Swear this one you’ll save. Better lock it, in your pocket, Taking this one to the grave.”
Keep in mind, all I know about Pretty Liars is this theme song. I once tried to watch it with my sister and she became so annoyed with my questions, told me not to watch it and I’m pretty sure changed the channel.
I only bring it up because the theme song was constantly playing in my head as I read book #31 of 2018.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Take This Book to the Beach</title>
      <link>https://anotheryearofbooks.com/2018/07/take-this-book-to-the-beach/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Jul 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://anotheryearofbooks.com/2018/07/take-this-book-to-the-beach/</guid>
      <description>Another library book find, another book that really is a beach read. While reading this book on the bus daily, I found myself wishing it were August so I could be sitting in the sand, SPF 75 on, a book in hand with the ocean in view.
 Book Read: Falling Together
Author: Maria de los Santos
Number of Books Read: 30
 Pen, Will and Cat became instant friends in college.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>But Will The Glass Castle Look Like the One in Frozen?</title>
      <link>https://anotheryearofbooks.com/2018/07/but-will-the-glass-castle-look-like-the-one-in-frozen/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 Jul 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://anotheryearofbooks.com/2018/07/but-will-the-glass-castle-look-like-the-one-in-frozen/</guid>
      <description>Another Beaver library book sale find, and another book to read before watching the movie. Except unlike my last read, this one is a memoir by a woman who has had an adventure of a life.
 Book Read: The Glass Castle
Author: Jeannette Walls
Number of Books Read: 29
 Jeannette Walls’ family is different, to say the least. Vibrant is another good way to describe them and their adventures.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Cause Baby There Ain’t No Mountain High Enough</title>
      <link>https://anotheryearofbooks.com/2018/06/cause-baby-there-aint-no-mountain-high-enough/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Jun 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://anotheryearofbooks.com/2018/06/cause-baby-there-aint-no-mountain-high-enough/</guid>
      <description>But maybe, there actually is? The Beaver library’s annual book sale came in for the win again when I found the next read just lying around, waiting to be purchased (along with about 8 others that filled my bag). I’m a big believer in reading the book before you see the movie based on it (did it in reverse for The Notebook and we all know that movie is fantastic). So when I found this next read, I had to buy it.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Give Me a Beach Read and I’ll Want to Be at the Beach</title>
      <link>https://anotheryearofbooks.com/2018/06/give-me-a-beach-read-and-ill-want-to-be-at-the-beach/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 Jun 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://anotheryearofbooks.com/2018/06/give-me-a-beach-read-and-ill-want-to-be-at-the-beach/</guid>
      <description>This book was a hand-me down, which always seems to work out well for me. This one went from Massachusetts to Brooklyn to Carnegie (and will probably go to Beaver next). It reminded me a book that you would read while sitting on a beach chair, feet in the water, SPF 50 on and getting some sun. (Or maybe SPF 75 - your call).
 Book Read: The Glass Kitchen</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Every Family Has Its Secrets. This One is No Different</title>
      <link>https://anotheryearofbooks.com/2018/06/every-family-has-its-secrets.-this-one-is-no-different/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 09 Jun 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://anotheryearofbooks.com/2018/06/every-family-has-its-secrets.-this-one-is-no-different/</guid>
      <description>This book has been on my list for a while now. It worked out that one day in the Big Apple while visiting my sister and her fiancé, it rained. We looked for something to do. Matt suggested the Amazon Book store…. yes the Amazon book store (NYC has these things). Perfect opportunity to buy a new book, no?
 Book Read: Everything I Never Told You
Author: Celeste Ng</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>It&#39;s Been Awhile</title>
      <link>https://anotheryearofbooks.com/2018/06/its-been-awhile/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Jun 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://anotheryearofbooks.com/2018/06/its-been-awhile/</guid>
      <description>I haven’t posted anything for two weeks… I know, two weeks is a long time. What have I been doing in these two weeks you may ask? Visiting my sister and her fiancé in Brooklyn, working, getting settled in our new house, and reading. That’s right, this one took me two full weeks to read.
 Book Read: The Sparsholt Affair
Author: Alan Hollinghurst
Number of Books Read: 25
 This another “Emily went to the library at lunch and picked up a book.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Promise Me You’ll Think About Reading It</title>
      <link>https://anotheryearofbooks.com/2018/05/promise-me-youll-think-about-reading-it/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 16 May 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://anotheryearofbooks.com/2018/05/promise-me-youll-think-about-reading-it/</guid>
      <description>I have no desire to bring politics into Another Year of Books. I promise not to preach to you if you promise not to preach to me. When I picked up my latest read, there were many reasons and very few were political. The most important one being I heard it was a really well written book.
 Book Read: Promise Me, Dad
Author: Joe Biden
Number of Books Read: 24</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>You Write It, I&#39;&#39;ll Read It</title>
      <link>https://anotheryearofbooks.com/2018/05/you-write-it-ill-read-it/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 11 May 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://anotheryearofbooks.com/2018/05/you-write-it-ill-read-it/</guid>
      <description>Not going to lie… my reading has been suffering some. Between buying a house, moving into said house, and running a half marathon, my focus has been on other things. Reading a book of short stories helped some – more stop and go then others.
 Book Read: You Think It, I’ll Say It
Author: Curtis Sittenfield
Number of Books Read: 23
 I’ve read a couple of Sittenfield’s books previously (Prep, Eligible) so when I was wandering the library (after work this time, not a lunch) and saw this one, I figured she wouldn’t lead me astray.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>I Now Understand Why HBO Made This a Show</title>
      <link>https://anotheryearofbooks.com/2018/05/i-now-understand-why-hbo-made-this-a-show/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 05 May 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://anotheryearofbooks.com/2018/05/i-now-understand-why-hbo-made-this-a-show/</guid>
      <description>I’m sure most of you have heard of it. It swept awards shows, Nicole Kidman gave a few speeches, so did Laura Dern. And drumroll please… Meryl will be on season 2 (MERYL!), which takes us to book number 22…
 Book Read: Big Little Lies
Author: Liane Moriarty
Number of Books Read: 22
 A coworker recommended I read Moriarty’s The Husband’s Secret, so I went hunting for it at the library.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Every Note Leads to Every Page</title>
      <link>https://anotheryearofbooks.com/2018/04/every-note-leads-to-every-page/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Apr 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://anotheryearofbooks.com/2018/04/every-note-leads-to-every-page/</guid>
      <description>Let me start with one note… I read this book in two day. Two days. Two days of wishing the bus ride was longer so I could keep reading, two days of reading before falling asleep (which I usually don’t do anymore), two days of a great read. And away we go&amp;hellip;
 Book Read: Every Note Played
Author: Lisa Genova
Number of Books Read: 21
 If the two days comment didn’t tell you I liked this book, I’m not sure what will.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>She Isn’t a Nobody Anymore</title>
      <link>https://anotheryearofbooks.com/2018/04/she-isnt-a-nobody-anymore/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Apr 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://anotheryearofbooks.com/2018/04/she-isnt-a-nobody-anymore/</guid>
      <description>You know her from Into the Woods, Pitch Perfect and Trolls. Maybe you even remember she was in Twilight (I do). Apparently she also wrote a book!
 Book Read: Scrappy Little Nobody
Author: Anna Kendrick
Number of Books Read: 20
 My sister Meghan was kind enough to lug Scrappy Little Nobody all the way from Brooklyn so I figured I’d give it a go. Nice of me, huh?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>They’re Still Rich… and Still Crazy</title>
      <link>https://anotheryearofbooks.com/2018/04/theyre-still-rich-and-still-crazy/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 15 Apr 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://anotheryearofbooks.com/2018/04/theyre-still-rich-and-still-crazy/</guid>
      <description>I know it has been awhile - almost 2 weeks to be exact. But, when I went to the library (not at lunch this time – big change for me!) when I was almost done with my last read, I picked up not 1, but 2 books, and they were meant to be read and talked about together. So here you go – a two for one post.
 Book Read: China Rich Girlfriend &amp;amp; Rich People Problems</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A Book that Speaks to My Appetite</title>
      <link>https://anotheryearofbooks.com/2018/04/a-book-that-speaks-to-my-appetite/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 03 Apr 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://anotheryearofbooks.com/2018/04/a-book-that-speaks-to-my-appetite/</guid>
      <description>An autobiography that ties almost every story back to food? Check. A book that has recipes about these experiences at the end of every section? Check. Another random find at the library? Check. A book for you to read? Check.
 Book Read: Blue Plate Special: An Autobiography of My Appetites
Author: Kate Christensen
Number of Books Read: 17
 Kate Christensen has had a lot of experiences, all which shaped her life.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Well, Plot Twist... You Got Me</title>
      <link>https://anotheryearofbooks.com/2018/03/well-plot-twist...-you-got-me/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 26 Mar 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://anotheryearofbooks.com/2018/03/well-plot-twist...-you-got-me/</guid>
      <description>I didn&amp;rsquo;t know what to expect for this one. I picked it up at the library’s new bookshelf, drawn to the colorful cover and the description in the flap (I know, something new for me). Did I see this ending coming? Nope. I usually can guess, which means this was a well written novel.
 Book Read: Speak No Evil
Author: Uzodinma Iweala
Number of Books Read: 16
 Niru’s parents are conservative Nigerians, who came to the US hoping to give the family a better life.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A Room Can Be a Scary Place</title>
      <link>https://anotheryearofbooks.com/2018/03/a-room-can-be-a-scary-place/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Mar 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://anotheryearofbooks.com/2018/03/a-room-can-be-a-scary-place/</guid>
      <description>This one has been on my bookshelf for a year or two. I picked it up at my local library’s annual book sale because I heard it was a great novel and a great movie. So when I accidently picked up a book I had already read, I went to the shelf and Room caught my eye.
 Book Read: Room
Author: Emma Donoghue
Number of Books Read: 15
 Most probably know of it… Room, the Oscar nominated/winning movie based on the novel about a woman, Joy “Ma,” who is being held against her own will, and her young son, Jack, who knows nothing but the Room they are in, and their journey to see the outside world.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A Rose is a Rose is a Rose is a Rosie</title>
      <link>https://anotheryearofbooks.com/2018/03/a-rose-is-a-rose-is-a-rose-is-a-rosie/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Mar 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://anotheryearofbooks.com/2018/03/a-rose-is-a-rose-is-a-rose-is-a-rosie/</guid>
      <description>Books with the name Rosie in the title catch my eye. It’s probably because I really liked The Rosie Project. While in the middle of my last read, I once again found myself at the library during lunch, picking out the next one. This one was on the new book shelf, caught my eye, and here we are, book number 14 of 2018.
 Book Read: Rosie Colored Glasses
Author: Brianna Wolfson</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Name &#39;Tom Hanks&#39; Got Me</title>
      <link>https://anotheryearofbooks.com/2018/03/the-name-tom-hanks-got-me/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Mar 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://anotheryearofbooks.com/2018/03/the-name-tom-hanks-got-me/</guid>
      <description>T-Hanks… famous actor, director, producer, voice of Woody, most importantly star of one of my favorite movies You’ve Got Mail. Add author to the list and you&amp;rsquo;ve got book #13.
 Book Read: Uncommon Type: Some Stories
Author: Tom Hanks
Number of Books Read: 13
 Not going to lie, it took me about a week to read this book. At first, I thought it was because collections of fictional short stories may not be my thing, and it may be best to read one at a time rather than straight through.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Louisa Clark is Back, and Tougher than Ever</title>
      <link>https://anotheryearofbooks.com/2018/02/louisa-clark-is-back-and-tougher-than-ever/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 26 Feb 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://anotheryearofbooks.com/2018/02/louisa-clark-is-back-and-tougher-than-ever/</guid>
      <description>When I read the third part of the Me Before You trilogy was due to come out, I had to have it right away because Louisa Clark’s story wasn’t over yet. I loved Me Before You, I loved After You. So I asked my BF, who has Amazon prime, to buy Still Me. After a purchase of the wrong book (way to go, Matt), the book was on its way and I was ready to read.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>This Next Book is Insane(ly Good)</title>
      <link>https://anotheryearofbooks.com/2018/02/this-next-book-is-insanely-good/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Feb 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://anotheryearofbooks.com/2018/02/this-next-book-is-insanely-good/</guid>
      <description>My sister is getting married. My best friend’s sister is also getting married. Yesterday when we met for lunch, we were comparing the size of the guest lists. But this book trumped us - the wedding of the century with 888 guests. Eight hundred and eighty eight. Wow, sorry Meghan for commenting on the size of yours.
 Book Read: Crazy Rich Asians
Author: Kevin Kwan
Number of Books Read: 11</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Turtles Will Get Ya</title>
      <link>https://anotheryearofbooks.com/2018/02/the-turtles-will-get-ya/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Feb 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://anotheryearofbooks.com/2018/02/the-turtles-will-get-ya/</guid>
      <description>When I think of turtles, my mind goes to Sea Isle City, NJ. Why? Well, each year I visit, I see a turtle, they have signs about turtles crossing the road, and my cousin is a turtle whisperer. I realize these are not the turtles John Green had in mind, so I digress.
 Book Read: Turtles All The Way Down
Author: John Green
Number of Books Read: 10
 Technically, this is a “young adult” novel.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Where Are They? Do They Live Forever? I still have no idea</title>
      <link>https://anotheryearofbooks.com/2018/02/where-are-they-do-they-live-forever-i-still-have-no-idea/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 Feb 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://anotheryearofbooks.com/2018/02/where-are-they-do-they-live-forever-i-still-have-no-idea/</guid>
      <description>Since I read and loved Dave Egger’s The Circle a couple of years back, I have been trying to give him another chance. I finished The Circle in one weekend on a girls’ trip to the beach, so I tried a few of his other books… no success. When I saw this one at the library (again at lunchtime), I decided to give it another go. It helped that the book was relatively short.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>I’m Glad… I Picked Up This Book</title>
      <link>https://anotheryearofbooks.com/2018/02/im-glad-i-picked-up-this-book/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 04 Feb 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://anotheryearofbooks.com/2018/02/im-glad-i-picked-up-this-book/</guid>
      <description>Back to fiction we go with another the Skimm recommendation. According to this novel, the Navajo do not have words for “I love you.” They believe that no one can possess another. Instead, they say “I’m glad about you” (I did consult the Google on this and can’t find any evidence to the contrary). Either way, a fitting title for this read.  Book Read: I’m Glad About You
Author: Theresa Rebeck</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>12 Things I Would Like You to Tell Me More About</title>
      <link>https://anotheryearofbooks.com/2018/02/12-things-i-would-like-you-to-tell-me-more-about/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Feb 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://anotheryearofbooks.com/2018/02/12-things-i-would-like-you-to-tell-me-more-about/</guid>
      <description>The 7th book of 2018, I picked up because the cover was colorful. I walked into the library, looked at the front tables, and it caught my eye. Unless it’s an author I have heard of, or someone recommended it to me, I usually struggle with the essay/memoir type of book (example: didn’t think twice about Anna Faris’s). Frankly, I tend to avoid them.
But – if you read the author information on the back sleeve, the author has been called the “voice of her generation” by O: The Oprah Magazine; when has Oprah ever been wrong?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Astonish Me… With Your Ballet Moves</title>
      <link>https://anotheryearofbooks.com/2018/01/astonish-me-with-your-ballet-moves/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 26 Jan 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://anotheryearofbooks.com/2018/01/astonish-me-with-your-ballet-moves/</guid>
      <description>After my previous read, all I wanted was the next book to be light-hearted, not as challenging to read and to not fall asleep on the bus. Good news… I didn’t fall asleep once reading this one!
 Book Read: Astonish Me
Author: Maggie Shipstead
Books Read: 6
 I have had Shipstead’s other novel Seating Arrangements on my “to read” list for a while now, and haven’t picked it up yet.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>No One is Going to Save Me... From this Book</title>
      <link>https://anotheryearofbooks.com/2018/01/no-one-is-going-to-save-me...-from-this-book/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 19 Jan 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://anotheryearofbooks.com/2018/01/no-one-is-going-to-save-me...-from-this-book/</guid>
      <description>I tend to find books as I’m wandering the library at lunch. Sometimes, if I can’t find a book on my “to read” list, I pick one based on the cover, the author, or if I saw other people looking at it. Usually, it works out pretty well. This one… I’m still not convinced that picking a book because Powell was in the author’s name was a good idea. You win some, you lose some.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Anna Faris Is, In Fact, Qualified</title>
      <link>https://anotheryearofbooks.com/2018/01/anna-faris-is-in-fact-qualified/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 13 Jan 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://anotheryearofbooks.com/2018/01/anna-faris-is-in-fact-qualified/</guid>
      <description>I listen to the podcast Anna Faris is Unqualified religiously (seriously, once a week, just like going to church except the podcast comes out Tuesday mornings), so I was pretty excited when Anna Faris announced she was writing a book.
 Book Read: Unqualified
Author: Anna Faris
Number of Books Read: 4
 I can’t tell you how many times I have actually laughed out loud while listening to this podcast at the gym (I mean come on, have you seen The House Bunny?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The First Three of 2018</title>
      <link>https://anotheryearofbooks.com/2018/01/the-first-three-of-2018/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Jan 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://anotheryearofbooks.com/2018/01/the-first-three-of-2018/</guid>
      <description>I’ll start by saying this should probably be called the “first four” because it&amp;rsquo;s about a series, but since I finished the first on New Year’s Eve, we’ll go with the first three of 2018.
 Books Read: Winter Stroll; Winter Storms; Winter Solstice
Author: Elin Hilderbrand
2018 Book Count: 3
 First let me say, I am already a big fan of Elin Hilderbrand. Each book that I have read, I&amp;rsquo;ve enjoyed (The Identicals_ made it on the 2017 challenge list), so when my sister brought the 2 newest books in this series home over Christmas, I was ready to read.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>