<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>2019 Reads on Another Year of Books</title>
    <link>https://anotheryearofbooks.com/categories/2019-reads/</link>
    <description>Recent content in 2019 Reads on Another Year of Books</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 10 Jan 2020 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://anotheryearofbooks.com/categories/2019-reads/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Another Year of Books: The 2019 Recap</title>
      <link>https://anotheryearofbooks.com/2020/01/another-year-of-books-the-2019-recap/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 Jan 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://anotheryearofbooks.com/2020/01/another-year-of-books-the-2019-recap/</guid>
      <description>Another year has already come and gone. I can’t believe it. I still can’t believe that I read all 52 books in 2019. I was filled with doubt and, mostly, annoyance at myself. But then, after I finished, all I felt was pride, and a little tired. This one is always the hardest… the recap. Which books were the best? Which were the worst? Which books are waiting for Hallmark to pick them up?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>NUMBER 52</title>
      <link>https://anotheryearofbooks.com/2020/01/number-52/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Jan 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://anotheryearofbooks.com/2020/01/number-52/</guid>
      <description>On December 31, 2019, at 12:04 PM, I sent my sister this text:

It was the last day of the year. Since December 25, I had read three books (and wrote 0 posts). On Christmas Eve, when asked if I was going to read all 52, I said no. I didn’t anticipate reading three books in 6 days. It helped that Matt has been sick and we didn’t leave the house much, and that the three books kept my attention.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Double Dutch</title>
      <link>https://anotheryearofbooks.com/2020/01/double-dutch/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 Jan 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://anotheryearofbooks.com/2020/01/double-dutch/</guid>
      <description>I actually started reading this book before I picked up The Christmas Star. I was only 10 pages or so into this one when I set it back down. Then when I picked it back up again, I started over. It only seemed right. I don’t often start a book and stop for another, but decided that Christmas was an acceptable night to do so.  Book Read: Going Dutch</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>SO THIS IS CHRISTMAS</title>
      <link>https://anotheryearofbooks.com/2019/12/so-this-is-christmas/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 31 Dec 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://anotheryearofbooks.com/2019/12/so-this-is-christmas/</guid>
      <description>On Christmas night, I put on How the Grinch Stole Christmas (first the animated version, which was then followed by the Jim Carrey version) and settled in with a comfy blanket. I was in the mood for a Christmas themed book. Luckily, I had one on my shelf. I mean, truthfully, I only have one. This was my only option. I picked it up, and by the time I went to bed, I was half way finished.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>THIS COULD BE THE START OF SOMETHING NEW</title>
      <link>https://anotheryearofbooks.com/2019/12/this-could-be-the-start-of-something-new/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 28 Dec 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://anotheryearofbooks.com/2019/12/this-could-be-the-start-of-something-new/</guid>
      <description>Every Friday, theSkimm recommends a book. I look forward to it every week. I reckon all but one a month make it onto my “to read” list. This Friday, I beat theSkimm! What a day. Last week at the library, I picked up yesterday&amp;rsquo;s recommendation. I am impressed with myself to say the least.
 Book Read: Evvie Drake Starts Over
Author: Linda Holmes
Number of Books Read, 2019 Edition: 49</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>TROUBLE, TROUBLE, TROUBLE</title>
      <link>https://anotheryearofbooks.com/2019/12/trouble-trouble-trouble/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Dec 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://anotheryearofbooks.com/2019/12/trouble-trouble-trouble/</guid>
      <description>It’s hard to find time to read during all the holiday hooplah. There’s the cooking, the baking, the wrapping, the cleaning, the Christmas movies, the family time. Although a book is a good excuse to avoid family time. Just saying. (I did not do this, also just saying.)
 Book Read: Fleishman is In Trouble
Author: Taffy Brodesser-Akner
Number of Books Read, 2019 Edition: 48
 Toby Fleishman became a ladies’ man after his wife finally agreed to his requested divorce.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CIRCLE, CIRCLE, DOT, DOT</title>
      <link>https://anotheryearofbooks.com/2019/12/circle-circle-dot-dot/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Dec 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://anotheryearofbooks.com/2019/12/circle-circle-dot-dot/</guid>
      <description>The last read was a heavy topic. I enjoyed it (find out here), but afterwards, I wanted my next read to be more mindless and quick. I found it at my trip to the library at lunchtime last week (I know, a book found at a library - shocking!)
 Book Read: The Friend Zone
Author: Abby Jimenez
Number of Books Read, 2019 Edition: 47
 Kristen Peterson’s best friend is getting married.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>WHEN I GROW UP</title>
      <link>https://anotheryearofbooks.com/2019/12/when-i-grow-up/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 15 Dec 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://anotheryearofbooks.com/2019/12/when-i-grow-up/</guid>
      <description>In the first grade, our teacher asked us what we wanted to be when we grew up. I remember I wanted to be a teacher. We made paper dolls showing what we wanted to be - I can still picture what mine looked like (she was wearing a pink shirt). I also remember multiple girls in my class wanting to be models. But I’m pretty sure one girl copied the other, so who knows!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>PARADISE BY THE DASHBOARD LIGHT</title>
      <link>https://anotheryearofbooks.com/2019/12/paradise-by-the-dashboard-light/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 08 Dec 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://anotheryearofbooks.com/2019/12/paradise-by-the-dashboard-light/</guid>
      <description>Sequels can be tough to write about. I don’t want to give away too much. That way you want to read this book, but you also want to read the first in the series. It is a line easily crossed. If I say too much for the second book, do I give away the ending of the first?
Gosh, I hope not.  Book Read: What Happens in Paradise
Author: Elin Hilderbrand</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>LET&#39;S FEAST!</title>
      <link>https://anotheryearofbooks.com/2019/11/lets-feast/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Nov 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://anotheryearofbooks.com/2019/11/lets-feast/</guid>
      <description>I hope at this point, everyone has watched Always Be My Maybe on Netflix, or maybe the comedy specials Baby Cobra or Hard Knock Wife. Because Ali Wong is hysterical; completely hysterical. My friends and I are obsessed. I’ve watched Always Be My Maybe I don’t even know how many times. I mean, it has Keanu Reeves! It’s a laugh-out-loud romantic comedy, that is more comedy than most.
When I saw that Ali Wong wrote a book, I knew I had to read it, leading to read number 44.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>FASTER, DENNY, FASTER</title>
      <link>https://anotheryearofbooks.com/2019/11/faster-denny-faster/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 23 Nov 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://anotheryearofbooks.com/2019/11/faster-denny-faster/</guid>
      <description>This next read came as a recommendation from a friend. Yes, I know it’s a movie too, so eventually I would have gotten to it. But a recommendation usually bumps up the book on the &amp;ldquo;to read&amp;rdquo; list. Really, if this book wasn’t as good as I expected, who knows what would have happened - awkwardness, bitterness, loss of a friend. Just kidding of course. I will never hold a book recommendation grudge… unless it is really, really bad.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>AND MY FLIPPY FLOPPIES</title>
      <link>https://anotheryearofbooks.com/2019/11/and-my-flippy-floppies/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 17 Nov 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://anotheryearofbooks.com/2019/11/and-my-flippy-floppies/</guid>
      <description>In the first weekend of November, my mom, aunt and I ventured to New York City to visit my sister and brother-in-law. We planned ahead for 2 main events - to see Waitress on Broadway, since it is in its final run, and to go to Strand Book Store. Strand is a magical place that has EIGHTEEN miles of books. You read that right - eighteen miles. Us visitors came prepared with room in our suitcases.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>EVERYTHING IS FINE</title>
      <link>https://anotheryearofbooks.com/2019/11/everything-is-fine/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 07 Nov 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://anotheryearofbooks.com/2019/11/everything-is-fine/</guid>
      <description>I’m writing this while it is 34 degrees outside. Thirty four! Did I blink and miss fall? It really feels like I did. It’s a good thing there are so many books that go well with a cozy blanket. It’s also a good thing that I bought four new books on a trip to visit my sister and brother-in-law in New York City (shout out to the Strand!).
 Book Read: Mrs.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CAUSE I&#39;M BURNIN&#39; UP</title>
      <link>https://anotheryearofbooks.com/2019/10/cause-im-burnin-up/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 Oct 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://anotheryearofbooks.com/2019/10/cause-im-burnin-up/</guid>
      <description>When I was writing this, I could not get Burnin’ Up by the Jonas Brothers out of my head. Why? Because it is a catchy song. Also, because I love the Jonas Brothers; meaning I LOVE the Jonas Brothers. My aunt and I had a fabulous time at their concert in September. “I’m hot. You’re cold…”  Book Read: Things You Save in a Fire
Author: Katherine Carter
Number of Books Read, 2019 Edition: 40</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>OK, LADIES...</title>
      <link>https://anotheryearofbooks.com/2019/10/ok-ladies.../</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Oct 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://anotheryearofbooks.com/2019/10/ok-ladies.../</guid>
      <description>Let us get in formation.
I struggle with non-fiction. I’m sure I’ve mentioned this each time I talk about non-fiction, but it’s true. This book took me awhile to read. Not because it was a bad book, but because I feel like I have to really pay attention to what I’m reading.
This is a book that requires your attention, for good reasons. And I’m not just talking to the ladies.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>DECISIONS, DECISIONS, DECISIONS</title>
      <link>https://anotheryearofbooks.com/2019/10/decisions-decisions-decisions/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 11 Oct 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://anotheryearofbooks.com/2019/10/decisions-decisions-decisions/</guid>
      <description>I look forward to Friday’s. Not just because TGIF, but because every Friday, the Skimm has a book recommendation. I’d say 95% of the time, I end up adding the book to my “to read” list; then, I wait. I wait until the book is finally available at the library. Usually it takes weeks, at the minimum.
Somehow, when I went to return An American Marriage to the library, I found this next read.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>NOW, DO YOU LOVE ME?</title>
      <link>https://anotheryearofbooks.com/2019/10/now-do-you-love-me/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 06 Oct 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://anotheryearofbooks.com/2019/10/now-do-you-love-me/</guid>
      <description>It seems like October crashed into me. I looked up and BAM&amp;hellip; October. I feel like I should have seen it coming considering Giant Eagle had Halloween candy out before school started. This is entirely too soon, by the way. Don’t even get me started on the Christmas decorations that are already out in stores.
Finishing this book means I have 15 more to read to make it to 52 books read in 2019.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>I GOT MY FIRST REAL SIX-STRING</title>
      <link>https://anotheryearofbooks.com/2019/10/i-got-my-first-real-six-string/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Oct 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://anotheryearofbooks.com/2019/10/i-got-my-first-real-six-string/</guid>
      <description>Another Year of Books started with an Elin Hilderbrand novel. In fact, it started with three. She’s appeared over and over again ever since. It’s a cycle: Hilderbrand writes a book, I read it, Hilderbrand writes a book, I read it. I blame my sister. If I remember correctly, she started reading Hilderbrand’s books first, then I picked them up. Now, we alternate who buys the newest one. FYI - she bought this one.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Loving You Isn’t the Right Thing to Do</title>
      <link>https://anotheryearofbooks.com/2019/09/loving-you-isnt-the-right-thing-to-do/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 Sep 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://anotheryearofbooks.com/2019/09/loving-you-isnt-the-right-thing-to-do/</guid>
      <description>When I was reading this next read on the bus, the woman who sat down next to me asked how it was. I have been taking the bus for almost three years now, and this is the first time someone has asked me how my book was. Why did she ask? Because this one was also on her list to read. It had good reviews and was supposed to be a good read.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>GO AWAY, ANNA</title>
      <link>https://anotheryearofbooks.com/2019/09/go-away-anna/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 14 Sep 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://anotheryearofbooks.com/2019/09/go-away-anna/</guid>
      <description>I feel very fortunate I have great friends: great friends who always pay me back; great friends I always pay back. Venmo definitely helps. A few weeks ago, when I met my BFF for brunch, she bought us a pastry. I felt so guilty that I owed her two dollars! But alas she didn’t make me pay. Like I said, great friends.
Rachel DeLoache Williams was not as lucky.  Book Read: My Friend Anna: The True Story of a Fake Heiress</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Alexa, Play “One Day More”</title>
      <link>https://anotheryearofbooks.com/2019/09/alexa-play-one-day-more/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Sep 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://anotheryearofbooks.com/2019/09/alexa-play-one-day-more/</guid>
      <description>There were multiple times when reading this book and typing this post when the song from Les Miserables “One Day More” started playing in my head. I can even picture the movie seen when Hugh Jackman is belting out “ONE DAY MOREEEE” when Helena Bohnam Carter and Sasha Baron Cohen jump in with “watch ‘em run amuck.” Maybe even this is a result of buying tickets to see Hugh Jackman in October?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Way Out Yonder, Where the Crawdads Sing</title>
      <link>https://anotheryearofbooks.com/2019/09/way-out-yonder-where-the-crawdads-sing/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 Sep 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://anotheryearofbooks.com/2019/09/way-out-yonder-where-the-crawdads-sing/</guid>
      <description>This next read came as a recommendation from a fellow library-goer and reader, known by her family as GMA. That’s right, this book came recommended by Grandma Donna. She told me to read it, told my aunt (probably both of my aunts), and told my sister to read it. She may have told my mom too - not 100% on that one, but I feel confident. So I listened to her advice, and reserved a copy at the library… after 3 weeks, I was still waiting.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hey, Hey, Hey. Just Walk Away.</title>
      <link>https://anotheryearofbooks.com/2019/08/hey-hey-hey.-just-walk-away./</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 24 Aug 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://anotheryearofbooks.com/2019/08/hey-hey-hey.-just-walk-away./</guid>
      <description>I have a love-hate relationship with Target, as most people do. The one thing I love/hate as much as Target? The Target Cartwheel app, especially when it gives me twenty percent off books. That means a new book, like this week’s read, to add to my ever-growing bookshelf. How can anyone pass that up?  Book Read: How to Walk Away
Author: Katherine Carter
Number of Books Read, 2019 Edition: 31</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Never Drink the Kool Aid (or Smoothie)</title>
      <link>https://anotheryearofbooks.com/2019/05/never-drink-the-kool-aid-or-smoothie/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://anotheryearofbooks.com/2019/05/never-drink-the-kool-aid-or-smoothie/</guid>
      <description>I am eagerly waiting for the second season of Big Little Lies. I loved the show, and the book started me down a path of reading Liane Moriarty’s books. Of course, I had to read her newest novel:
Book Read: Nine Perfect Strangers
Author: Liane Moriarty
Number of Books Read, 2019 Edition: 15
Frances Welty fell victim to an Internet dating scam. Heartbroken and in need of a break, at the advice of a friend, she signs up for a 10 day cleanse at the Tranquillum House.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Do You Remember, the 21st Night of December?</title>
      <link>https://anotheryearofbooks.com/2019/01/do-you-remember-the-21st-night-of-december/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 19 Jan 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://anotheryearofbooks.com/2019/01/do-you-remember-the-21st-night-of-december/</guid>
      <description>I’m 26 years old, and every year, I’m still asked what’s on my Christmas list. The answer is usually pretty standard: money, something I’ve been putting off buying, and books. Becoming was a Christmas gift (thanks, Mom), as was this next read (thanks, Aunt Barb), and the one after this (again, thanks Aunt Barb). My philosophy: there is plenty of room on my bookshelf, so no amount of books is too many.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>