<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>2019 Reads on Another Year of Books</title>
    <link>https://anotheryearofbooks.com/categories/2019-reads/</link>
    <description>Recent content in 2019 Reads on Another Year of Books</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 10 Jan 2020 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://anotheryearofbooks.com/categories/2019-reads/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Another Year of Books: The 2019 Recap</title>
      <link>https://anotheryearofbooks.com/2020/01/another-year-of-books-the-2019-recap/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 Jan 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://anotheryearofbooks.com/2020/01/another-year-of-books-the-2019-recap/</guid>
      <description>Another year has already come and gone. I can’t believe it. I still can’t believe that I read all 52 books in 2019. I was filled with doubt and, mostly, annoyance at myself. But then, after I finished, all I felt was pride, and a little tired. This one is always the hardest… the recap. Which books were the best? Which were the worst? Which books are waiting for Hallmark to pick them up?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>NUMBER 52</title>
      <link>https://anotheryearofbooks.com/2020/01/number-52/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Jan 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://anotheryearofbooks.com/2020/01/number-52/</guid>
      <description>On December 31, 2019, at 12:04 PM, I sent my sister this text:

It was the last day of the year. Since December 25, I had read three books (and wrote 0 posts). On Christmas Eve, when asked if I was going to read all 52, I said no. I didn’t anticipate reading three books in 6 days. It helped that Matt has been sick and we didn’t leave the house much, and that the three books kept my attention.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Double Dutch</title>
      <link>https://anotheryearofbooks.com/2020/01/double-dutch/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 Jan 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://anotheryearofbooks.com/2020/01/double-dutch/</guid>
      <description>I actually started reading this book before I picked up The Christmas Star. I was only 10 pages or so into this one when I set it back down. Then when I picked it back up again, I started over. It only seemed right. I don’t often start a book and stop for another, but decided that Christmas was an acceptable night to do so.  Book Read: Going Dutch</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>SO THIS IS CHRISTMAS</title>
      <link>https://anotheryearofbooks.com/2019/12/so-this-is-christmas/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 31 Dec 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://anotheryearofbooks.com/2019/12/so-this-is-christmas/</guid>
      <description>On Christmas night, I put on How the Grinch Stole Christmas (first the animated version, which was then followed by the Jim Carrey version) and settled in with a comfy blanket. I was in the mood for a Christmas themed book. Luckily, I had one on my shelf. I mean, truthfully, I only have one. This was my only option. I picked it up, and by the time I went to bed, I was half way finished.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>THIS COULD BE THE START OF SOMETHING NEW</title>
      <link>https://anotheryearofbooks.com/2019/12/this-could-be-the-start-of-something-new/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 28 Dec 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://anotheryearofbooks.com/2019/12/this-could-be-the-start-of-something-new/</guid>
      <description>Every Friday, theSkimm recommends a book. I look forward to it every week. I reckon all but one a month make it onto my “to read” list. This Friday, I beat theSkimm! What a day. Last week at the library, I picked up yesterday&amp;rsquo;s recommendation. I am impressed with myself to say the least.
 Book Read: Evvie Drake Starts Over
Author: Linda Holmes
Number of Books Read, 2019 Edition: 49</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>TROUBLE, TROUBLE, TROUBLE</title>
      <link>https://anotheryearofbooks.com/2019/12/trouble-trouble-trouble/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Dec 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://anotheryearofbooks.com/2019/12/trouble-trouble-trouble/</guid>
      <description>It’s hard to find time to read during all the holiday hooplah. There’s the cooking, the baking, the wrapping, the cleaning, the Christmas movies, the family time. Although a book is a good excuse to avoid family time. Just saying. (I did not do this, also just saying.)
 Book Read: Fleishman is In Trouble
Author: Taffy Brodesser-Akner
Number of Books Read, 2019 Edition: 48
 Toby Fleishman became a ladies’ man after his wife finally agreed to his requested divorce.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CIRCLE, CIRCLE, DOT, DOT</title>
      <link>https://anotheryearofbooks.com/2019/12/circle-circle-dot-dot/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Dec 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://anotheryearofbooks.com/2019/12/circle-circle-dot-dot/</guid>
      <description>The last read was a heavy topic. I enjoyed it (find out here), but afterwards, I wanted my next read to be more mindless and quick. I found it at my trip to the library at lunchtime last week (I know, a book found at a library - shocking!)
 Book Read: The Friend Zone
Author: Abby Jimenez
Number of Books Read, 2019 Edition: 47
 Kristen Peterson’s best friend is getting married.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>WHEN I GROW UP</title>
      <link>https://anotheryearofbooks.com/2019/12/when-i-grow-up/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 15 Dec 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://anotheryearofbooks.com/2019/12/when-i-grow-up/</guid>
      <description>In the first grade, our teacher asked us what we wanted to be when we grew up. I remember I wanted to be a teacher. We made paper dolls showing what we wanted to be - I can still picture what mine looked like (she was wearing a pink shirt). I also remember multiple girls in my class wanting to be models. But I’m pretty sure one girl copied the other, so who knows!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>PARADISE BY THE DASHBOARD LIGHT</title>
      <link>https://anotheryearofbooks.com/2019/12/paradise-by-the-dashboard-light/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 08 Dec 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://anotheryearofbooks.com/2019/12/paradise-by-the-dashboard-light/</guid>
      <description>Sequels can be tough to write about. I don’t want to give away too much. That way you want to read this book, but you also want to read the first in the series. It is a line easily crossed. If I say too much for the second book, do I give away the ending of the first?
Gosh, I hope not.  Book Read: What Happens in Paradise
Author: Elin Hilderbrand</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>LET&#39;S FEAST!</title>
      <link>https://anotheryearofbooks.com/2019/11/lets-feast/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Nov 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://anotheryearofbooks.com/2019/11/lets-feast/</guid>
      <description>I hope at this point, everyone has watched Always Be My Maybe on Netflix, or maybe the comedy specials Baby Cobra or Hard Knock Wife. Because Ali Wong is hysterical; completely hysterical. My friends and I are obsessed. I’ve watched Always Be My Maybe I don’t even know how many times. I mean, it has Keanu Reeves! It’s a laugh-out-loud romantic comedy, that is more comedy than most.
When I saw that Ali Wong wrote a book, I knew I had to read it, leading to read number 44.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>FASTER, DENNY, FASTER</title>
      <link>https://anotheryearofbooks.com/2019/11/faster-denny-faster/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 23 Nov 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://anotheryearofbooks.com/2019/11/faster-denny-faster/</guid>
      <description>This next read came as a recommendation from a friend. Yes, I know it’s a movie too, so eventually I would have gotten to it. But a recommendation usually bumps up the book on the &amp;ldquo;to read&amp;rdquo; list. Really, if this book wasn’t as good as I expected, who knows what would have happened - awkwardness, bitterness, loss of a friend. Just kidding of course. I will never hold a book recommendation grudge… unless it is really, really bad.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>AND MY FLIPPY FLOPPIES</title>
      <link>https://anotheryearofbooks.com/2019/11/and-my-flippy-floppies/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 17 Nov 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://anotheryearofbooks.com/2019/11/and-my-flippy-floppies/</guid>
      <description>In the first weekend of November, my mom, aunt and I ventured to New York City to visit my sister and brother-in-law. We planned ahead for 2 main events - to see Waitress on Broadway, since it is in its final run, and to go to Strand Book Store. Strand is a magical place that has EIGHTEEN miles of books. You read that right - eighteen miles. Us visitors came prepared with room in our suitcases.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>EVERYTHING IS FINE</title>
      <link>https://anotheryearofbooks.com/2019/11/everything-is-fine/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 07 Nov 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://anotheryearofbooks.com/2019/11/everything-is-fine/</guid>
      <description>I’m writing this while it is 34 degrees outside. Thirty four! Did I blink and miss fall? It really feels like I did. It’s a good thing there are so many books that go well with a cozy blanket. It’s also a good thing that I bought four new books on a trip to visit my sister and brother-in-law in New York City (shout out to the Strand!).
 Book Read: Mrs.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CAUSE I&#39;M BURNIN&#39; UP</title>
      <link>https://anotheryearofbooks.com/2019/10/cause-im-burnin-up/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 Oct 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://anotheryearofbooks.com/2019/10/cause-im-burnin-up/</guid>
      <description>When I was writing this, I could not get Burnin’ Up by the Jonas Brothers out of my head. Why? Because it is a catchy song. Also, because I love the Jonas Brothers; meaning I LOVE the Jonas Brothers. My aunt and I had a fabulous time at their concert in September. “I’m hot. You’re cold…”  Book Read: Things You Save in a Fire
Author: Katherine Center Number of Books Read, 2019 Edition: 40</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>OK, LADIES</title>
      <link>https://anotheryearofbooks.com/2019/10/ok-ladies/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Oct 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://anotheryearofbooks.com/2019/10/ok-ladies/</guid>
      <description>Let us get in formation.
I struggle with non-fiction. I’m sure I’ve mentioned this each time I talk about non-fiction, but it’s true. This book took me awhile to read. Not because it was a bad book, but because I feel like I have to really pay attention to what I’m reading.
This is a book that requires your attention, for good reasons. And I’m not just talking to the ladies.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>DECISIONS, DECISIONS, DECISIONS</title>
      <link>https://anotheryearofbooks.com/2019/10/decisions-decisions-decisions/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 11 Oct 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://anotheryearofbooks.com/2019/10/decisions-decisions-decisions/</guid>
      <description>I look forward to Friday’s. Not just because TGIF, but because every Friday, the Skimm has a book recommendation. I’d say 95% of the time, I end up adding the book to my “to read” list; then, I wait. I wait until the book is finally available at the library. Usually it takes weeks, at the minimum.
Somehow, when I went to return An American Marriage to the library, I found this next read.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>NOW, DO YOU LOVE ME?</title>
      <link>https://anotheryearofbooks.com/2019/10/now-do-you-love-me/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 06 Oct 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://anotheryearofbooks.com/2019/10/now-do-you-love-me/</guid>
      <description>It seems like October crashed into me. I looked up and BAM&amp;hellip; October. I feel like I should have seen it coming considering Giant Eagle had Halloween candy out before school started. This is entirely too soon, by the way. Don’t even get me started on the Christmas decorations that are already out in stores.
Finishing this book means I have 15 more to read to make it to 52 books read in 2019.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>I GOT MY FIRST REAL SIX-STRING</title>
      <link>https://anotheryearofbooks.com/2019/10/i-got-my-first-real-six-string/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Oct 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://anotheryearofbooks.com/2019/10/i-got-my-first-real-six-string/</guid>
      <description>Another Year of Books started with an Elin Hilderbrand novel. In fact, it started with three. She’s appeared over and over again ever since. It’s a cycle: Hilderbrand writes a book, I read it, Hilderbrand writes a book, I read it. I blame my sister. If I remember correctly, she started reading Hilderbrand’s books first, then I picked them up. Now, we alternate who buys the newest one. FYI - she bought this one.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Loving You Isn’t the Right Thing to Do</title>
      <link>https://anotheryearofbooks.com/2019/09/loving-you-isnt-the-right-thing-to-do/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 Sep 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://anotheryearofbooks.com/2019/09/loving-you-isnt-the-right-thing-to-do/</guid>
      <description>When I was reading this next read on the bus, the woman who sat down next to me asked how it was. I have been taking the bus for almost three years now, and this is the first time someone has asked me how my book was. Why did she ask? Because this one was also on her list to read. It had good reviews and was supposed to be a good read.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>GO AWAY, ANNA</title>
      <link>https://anotheryearofbooks.com/2019/09/go-away-anna/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 14 Sep 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://anotheryearofbooks.com/2019/09/go-away-anna/</guid>
      <description>I feel very fortunate I have great friends: great friends who always pay me back; great friends I always pay back. Venmo definitely helps. A few weeks ago, when I met my BFF for brunch, she bought us a pastry. I felt so guilty that I owed her two dollars! But alas she didn’t make me pay. Like I said, great friends.
Rachel DeLoache Williams was not as lucky.  Book Read: My Friend Anna: The True Story of a Fake Heiress</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Alexa, Play “One Day More”</title>
      <link>https://anotheryearofbooks.com/2019/09/alexa-play-one-day-more/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Sep 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://anotheryearofbooks.com/2019/09/alexa-play-one-day-more/</guid>
      <description>There were multiple times when reading this book and typing this post when the song from Les Miserables “One Day More” started playing in my head. I can even picture the movie seen when Hugh Jackman is belting out “ONE DAY MOREEEE” when Helena Bohnam Carter and Sasha Baron Cohen jump in with “watch ‘em run amuck.” Maybe even this is a result of buying tickets to see Hugh Jackman in October?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Way Out Yonder, Where the Crawdads Sing</title>
      <link>https://anotheryearofbooks.com/2019/09/way-out-yonder-where-the-crawdads-sing/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 Sep 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://anotheryearofbooks.com/2019/09/way-out-yonder-where-the-crawdads-sing/</guid>
      <description>This next read came as a recommendation from a fellow library-goer and reader, known by her family as GMA. That’s right, this book came recommended by Grandma Donna. She told me to read it, told my aunt (probably both of my aunts), and told my sister to read it. She may have told my mom too - not 100% on that one, but I feel confident. So I listened to her advice, and reserved a copy at the library… after 3 weeks, I was still waiting.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hey, Hey, Hey. Just Walk Away</title>
      <link>https://anotheryearofbooks.com/2019/08/hey-hey-hey.-just-walk-away/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 24 Aug 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://anotheryearofbooks.com/2019/08/hey-hey-hey.-just-walk-away/</guid>
      <description>I have a love-hate relationship with Target, as most people do. The one thing I love/hate as much as Target? The Target Cartwheel app, especially when it gives me twenty percent off books. That means a new book, like this week’s read, to add to my ever-growing bookshelf. How can anyone pass that up?  Book Read: How to Walk Away
Author: Katherine Center Number of Books Read, 2019 Edition: 31</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Make Some LuluLemonade (Bag Not Included)</title>
      <link>https://anotheryearofbooks.com/2019/08/make-some-lululemonade-bag-not-included/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Aug 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://anotheryearofbooks.com/2019/08/make-some-lululemonade-bag-not-included/</guid>
      <description>When I was reading Revenge Wears Prada, I had a strange feeling that I had read it before. At least I had started it, and maybe read the ending? I still am not 100% sure, but if I did read it before, the last two reads were the only time during Another Year of Books that I reread a book. 82 books in, and that’s a pretty good statistic. I know, with 100% confidence, that I have not read this next read.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>I Beat Meryl</title>
      <link>https://anotheryearofbooks.com/2019/08/i-beat-meryl/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 Aug 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://anotheryearofbooks.com/2019/08/i-beat-meryl/</guid>
      <description>I found the third book in this series at the Beaver Library book sale. You can&amp;rsquo;t just start with book three and not read the first two, am I right? So back to the start I went, all leading to BOGO day here at Another Year of Books.
 Book Read: The Devil Wears Prada
Author: Lauren Weisberger
Number of Books Read, 2019 Edition: 28
 Andy Sachs lands the job “a million girls would die for,” when she becomes Miranda Priestly’s junior assistant at Runway.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kissing in a Tree, K-I-S-S-I-N-G</title>
      <link>https://anotheryearofbooks.com/2019/07/kissing-in-a-tree-k-i-s-s-i-n-g/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 29 Jul 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://anotheryearofbooks.com/2019/07/kissing-in-a-tree-k-i-s-s-i-n-g/</guid>
      <description>I learned how to make macarons on Saturday. It was a magical experience. The class was three hours long and well worth every minute. We have already ate half of one box. By the end of the afternoon following, I almost fell asleep reading a book. Not a bad way to spend a Saturday, right?
 Book Read: The Kiss Quotient
Author: Helen Hoang
Number of Books Read, 2019 Edition: 27</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Halfway Point</title>
      <link>https://anotheryearofbooks.com/2019/07/the-halfway-point/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 25 Jul 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://anotheryearofbooks.com/2019/07/the-halfway-point/</guid>
      <description>It’s official. Twenty six books down, twenty six books to go. But only twenty three weeks left in the year (if I counted correctly). I better get moving on the next twenty six. The next option may be to read when my boyfriend drives me too work, but he drives pretty quickly. I should probably stick to reading when I get home.  Book Read: The Unlikely Adventures of the Shergill Sisters</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A Reserved, Family Cloud</title>
      <link>https://anotheryearofbooks.com/2019/07/a-reserved-family-cloud/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 15 Jul 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://anotheryearofbooks.com/2019/07/a-reserved-family-cloud/</guid>
      <description>The hardest part of writing Another Year of Books is this intro paragraph. Sometimes, I have a hundred things to say. Other days, like today, I can’t think of even one. I’ve complained about the weather plenty of times, I’ve mentioned my love of walking to the library at lunch, and besides some family visits and yard work, my week has been pretty ordinary. So, I’ll just get right to the point:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>One Glass of Drama, Please</title>
      <link>https://anotheryearofbooks.com/2019/07/one-glass-of-drama-please/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Jul 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://anotheryearofbooks.com/2019/07/one-glass-of-drama-please/</guid>
      <description>The week after a holiday, aka a day off, seems to either fly by or drag along. I can’t decide what this week is doing. One day fast, the next day slow. Maybe it’s the heat (I know, I’m still complaining about the heat), or it’s that it just feels like we should all be on a beach. If you are one of the lucky few, don’t forget your hat, sunscreen and a good book.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Six Feet Under the Stars (All Time Low)</title>
      <link>https://anotheryearofbooks.com/2019/07/six-feet-under-the-stars-all-time-low/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 07 Jul 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://anotheryearofbooks.com/2019/07/six-feet-under-the-stars-all-time-low/</guid>
      <description>It is hot outside. Unbearably hot, which means I usually get slightly sun burnt on any walks/runs, and come back to work sweating from my lunchtime walk. It’s super fun, let me tell you. But when it’s this hot, there’s no better time to stay cool in the AC with a good book and an ice cold drink.
 Book Read: This Will Only Hurt a Little
Author: Busy Philipps</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>I Can Still Recall Our Last Summer</title>
      <link>https://anotheryearofbooks.com/2019/06/i-can-still-recall-our-last-summer/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Jun 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://anotheryearofbooks.com/2019/06/i-can-still-recall-our-last-summer/</guid>
      <description>Every year, ‍I look forward to the Beaver Area Library book sale. Over the years, I have found some gems. Since I moved, for the past two book sales, I drive to Beaver so my mom and I can walk to the book sale. This year was a successful year. Just ask my mom, she went back and got even more books.  Book Read: Invincible Summer
Author: Alice Adams</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>I Call It an Education</title>
      <link>https://anotheryearofbooks.com/2019/06/i-call-it-an-education/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Jun 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://anotheryearofbooks.com/2019/06/i-call-it-an-education/</guid>
      <description>I just celebrated my five-year anniversary at work. That means I get to attend the fancy lunch in the fall (finally), but it also means I, along with the rest of the Class of 2014, graduated college 5 years ago. Time flies - especially when you have 52 books a year to read.
 Book Read: Educated
Author: Tara Westover
Number of Books Read, 2019 Edition: 21
 Tara Westover was raised by survivalists in Idaho.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>I Get By With a Little Help From My Friends</title>
      <link>https://anotheryearofbooks.com/2019/06/i-get-by-with-a-little-help-from-my-friends/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Jun 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://anotheryearofbooks.com/2019/06/i-get-by-with-a-little-help-from-my-friends/</guid>
      <description>I have been putting off writing this post because I’ve been feeling discouraged when it came to AYOB. While I’m slowly marching towards 52 books, I feel behind. Then I had myself convinced that despite knowing people read this, no one was actually reading. I mean, even my best friend openly admits she doesn’t read it.
Then, I went to visit my aunt and grandparents this past weekend. My aunt was telling her friends about my blog and then commented that other friends read every post and take the recommendations.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mind the Gap</title>
      <link>https://anotheryearofbooks.com/2019/05/mind-the-gap/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 May 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://anotheryearofbooks.com/2019/05/mind-the-gap/</guid>
      <description>AYOB has been MIA as my boyfriend, Matt, and I traveled to London and Paris for a vacation. While away, we took in historical sights, watched the Eiffel Tower&amp;rsquo;s 130th Anniversary light show, walked 124 total miles, and ate a lot of pastries. I mean a lot of pastries. Along the way, we found a bookshop in each city, each with its own uniqueness and fame (I might have picked up a book or two).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>In the Words of Aerosmith, Dream On</title>
      <link>https://anotheryearofbooks.com/2019/05/in-the-words-of-aerosmith-dream-on/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 May 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://anotheryearofbooks.com/2019/05/in-the-words-of-aerosmith-dream-on/</guid>
      <description>The only medical show I have watched (and thoroughly enjoyed) was House. It wasn’t too gruesome, and it had a way of looking deeper. The synopsis of this book reminded me of it. How House would weave into the patient’s mind or body to show you something. This book sounded like it would do the same.
 Book Read: The Book of Dreams
Author: Nina George
Number of Books Read, 2019 Edition: 16</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Never Drink the Kool Aid (or Smoothie)</title>
      <link>https://anotheryearofbooks.com/2019/05/never-drink-the-kool-aid-or-smoothie/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://anotheryearofbooks.com/2019/05/never-drink-the-kool-aid-or-smoothie/</guid>
      <description>I am eagerly waiting for the second season of Big Little Lies. I loved the show, and the book started me down a path of reading Liane Moriarty’s books. Of course, I had to read her newest novel.
 Book Read: Nine Perfect Strangers
Author: Liane Moriarty
Number of Books Read, 2019 Edition: 15
 Frances Welty fell victim to an Internet dating scam. Heartbroken and in need of a break, at the advice of a friend, she signs up for a 10 day cleanse at the Tranquillum House.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>IOU ... a Post</title>
      <link>https://anotheryearofbooks.com/2019/04/iou-...-a-post/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 25 Apr 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://anotheryearofbooks.com/2019/04/iou-...-a-post/</guid>
      <description>Is this year flying by, or is it just me? It seems there is never enough time for reading, writing, running, laundry, the packing list I’ve been meaning to start. It feels like a week ago that my boyfriend and I booked our vacation. Now it’s less than 20 days away… all this makes me think I better get moving on this list of books.
 Book Read: I Owe You</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>It’s BOGO Day on Another Year of Books</title>
      <link>https://anotheryearofbooks.com/2019/04/its-bogo-day-on-another-year-of-books/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Apr 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://anotheryearofbooks.com/2019/04/its-bogo-day-on-another-year-of-books/</guid>
      <description>Last weekend, we ventured to Texas for a wedding. The wedding was spectacular, the bride was beautiful, and the BBQ was delicious. In the words of my BFF, 10/10. Sitting in an airport, then flying home gives me the perfect excuse to read. I was determined to finish Girl, Stop Apologizing before we left. Luckily, I did, so I could read More Than Words while we dealt with a two hour delay before getting home.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>No, Not the Morgan Freeman Movie</title>
      <link>https://anotheryearofbooks.com/2019/04/no-not-the-morgan-freeman-movie/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Apr 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://anotheryearofbooks.com/2019/04/no-not-the-morgan-freeman-movie/</guid>
      <description>I am sure I’ve mentioned this before, but I keep an ever-growing list of books I want to read on my phone. It just makes it easier when I go to the library to pick a new one, or when I find one at a bookstore and don’t want to buy it just yet. Slowly, I’ve been dwindling it down, only to have it shoot back up, but a new tactic: request the books from the library so you can keep reading.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A History Lesson</title>
      <link>https://anotheryearofbooks.com/2019/03/a-history-lesson/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://anotheryearofbooks.com/2019/03/a-history-lesson/</guid>
      <description>In the 8th grade, our teacher gave us each an assignment - a book report written about a book focused on the Holocaust. I still remember mine - a collection of stories, each about a different race or religion impacted. I remember reading it, and visiting the Holocaust Museum as we wrapped up the lesson (that includes a group of 8th grade girls offering to sing Baby Got Back in order get on the radio&amp;hellip; only to end up in a tunnel when we had our shot).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>You Remind Me of Sunshine</title>
      <link>https://anotheryearofbooks.com/2019/03/you-remind-me-of-sunshine/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://anotheryearofbooks.com/2019/03/you-remind-me-of-sunshine/</guid>
      <description>I enjoy a good sequel. There are always some good ones, and there are also some bad ones. Like movies, some books don’t need sequels but you get them anyway. For others, a sequel or companion never hurt anybody. Case in point: book #9 for 2019.
 Book Read: Puddin’
Author: Julie Murphy
Number of Books Read, 2019 Edition: 9
 Millie Michalchuk took a chance and signed up for the Miss Blue Bonnet Teen Pageant in Dumplin’.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Take a Chance, Take a-take a Chance-Chance, Take a Chance, Take a Chance</title>
      <link>https://anotheryearofbooks.com/2019/03/take-a-chance-take-a-take-a-chance-chance-take-a-chance-take-a-chance/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://anotheryearofbooks.com/2019/03/take-a-chance-take-a-take-a-chance-chance-take-a-chance-take-a-chance/</guid>
      <description>Daylight Savings Time. It&amp;rsquo;s amazing how one hour can make a difference. By difference, I mean make you annoyed that it&amp;rsquo;s dark when you go to work, or you&amp;rsquo;re just tired for the next few days. That sounds like a good opportunity to read a new book (or blog) before you fall asleep.
 Book Read: This is Your Life, Harriet Chance!
Author: Jonathan Evison
Number of Books Read, 2019 Edition: 8</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>You can tell she&#39;&#39;s a good dancer by the way she drinks her soda pop.</title>
      <link>https://anotheryearofbooks.com/2019/03/you-can-tell-shes-a-good-dancer-by-the-way-she-drinks-her-soda-pop./</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 03 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://anotheryearofbooks.com/2019/03/you-can-tell-shes-a-good-dancer-by-the-way-she-drinks-her-soda-pop./</guid>
      <description>The bargain finds section of Barnes and Noble occasionally has some gems that either sound interesting or have been on my list to read. So some weekends, I just like to browse. For my seventh of read of 2019, I just happened to pick one up that had a fun cover.
 Book Read: The Decent Proposal
Author: Kemper Donovan
Number of Books Read, 2019 Edition: 7
 In The Decent Proposal, two strangers are given an interesting proposal - if they spend 2 hours a week together for the next year, they’ll split a million dollars.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Take a Breath and Let the Rest Come Easy</title>
      <link>https://anotheryearofbooks.com/2019/02/take-a-breath-and-let-the-rest-come-easy/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 23 Feb 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://anotheryearofbooks.com/2019/02/take-a-breath-and-let-the-rest-come-easy/</guid>
      <description>Rom-coms. Admit it or not, everyone occasionally likes them, book or movie. The books are usually a quick read, and pass the time. So when I felt behind on the number of books, reading one seemed like a good way to catch up. One author rarely lets me down.
 Book Read: Every Breath
Author: Nicholas Sparks
Number of Books Read, 2019 Edition: 6
 Hope Anderson and Tru Wells have never met.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>In Family We Trust (Maybe?)</title>
      <link>https://anotheryearofbooks.com/2019/02/in-family-we-trust-maybe/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 Feb 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://anotheryearofbooks.com/2019/02/in-family-we-trust-maybe/</guid>
      <description>It&amp;rsquo;s been awhile since my last post. I&amp;rsquo;ll make no excuses. Maybe I&amp;rsquo;ve taken the bus a few times less than normal recently. Maybe I&amp;rsquo;ve spent some nights just watching Seinfeld (only 119 episodes more to go). Or maybe, it&amp;rsquo;s because this book took exactly two weeks to read. That&amp;rsquo;s not an excuse, right?
 Book Read: Family Trust
Author: Kathy Wang
Number of Books Read, 2019 Edition: 5
 Patriarch Stanley Huang has been recently diagnosed with pancreatic cancer and his death is soon approaching.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Pour Myself a Cup of Ambition</title>
      <link>https://anotheryearofbooks.com/2019/02/pour-myself-a-cup-of-ambition/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Feb 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://anotheryearofbooks.com/2019/02/pour-myself-a-cup-of-ambition/</guid>
      <description>I admit, I went against my normal principle of reading the book before watching the movie for this one. I couldn’t help it! The Netflix movie got my attention. So I backtracked…
 Book Read: Dumplin’
Author: Julie Murphy
Number of Books Read, 2019 Edition: 4
 Willowdean Dickson, aka Dumplin’, is growing up in a town that lives for its Miss Teen Blue Bonnet beauty pageant. Her mom is the perfect example - a former winner, she runs the pageant and has been wearing her victory dress since she won (will it fit this year?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>And the Winner Is...</title>
      <link>https://anotheryearofbooks.com/2019/01/and-the-winner-is.../</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 Jan 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://anotheryearofbooks.com/2019/01/and-the-winner-is.../</guid>
      <description>When the weather is as bad as it has been in western PA (if you don’t live here, just let me tell you, it has not been good), all I want to do is curl up in a blanket and read (or watch Netflix - both are acceptable). But I still have to go to work, so I find a little joy in getting to the bus stop three minutes before it pulls up, finding a seat, and pulling out my current read for the next 30 minutes.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Do You Remember, the 21st Night of December?</title>
      <link>https://anotheryearofbooks.com/2019/01/do-you-remember-the-21st-night-of-december/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 19 Jan 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://anotheryearofbooks.com/2019/01/do-you-remember-the-21st-night-of-december/</guid>
      <description>I’m 26 years old, and every year, I’m still asked what’s on my Christmas list. The answer is usually pretty standard: money, something I’ve been putting off buying, and books. Becoming was a Christmas gift (thanks, Mom), as was this next read (thanks, Aunt Barb), and the one after this (again, thanks Aunt Barb). My philosophy: there is plenty of room on my bookshelf, so no amount of books is too many.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2019 is Becoming a Good One</title>
      <link>https://anotheryearofbooks.com/2019/01/2019-is-becoming-a-good-one/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 13 Jan 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://anotheryearofbooks.com/2019/01/2019-is-becoming-a-good-one/</guid>
      <description>It’s been awhile. At least it seems like it. 2019 is here, holiday decorations are coming down, the weather is see-sawing and can’t make up its mind, and right now, in Pennsylvania, it’s, frankly, frigid as heck.
I’ve still been reading, just not typing. We’re also trying to build a 1500 piece puzzle (as you can see, it’s a slow process over 3 weeks in).

But the first book of 2019 is officially complete.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
