<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>2021 Reads on Another Year of Books</title>
    <link>https://anotheryearofbooks.com/categories/2021-reads/</link>
    <description>Recent content in 2021 Reads on Another Year of Books</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 04 May 2021 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://anotheryearofbooks.com/categories/2021-reads/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Thanks, Obama</title>
      <link>https://anotheryearofbooks.com/2021/05/thanks-obama/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 04 May 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://anotheryearofbooks.com/2021/05/thanks-obama/</guid>
      <description>&lt;!-- raw HTML omitted --&gt;
&lt;p&gt;There were two main things I wanted for Christmas this past year - a set of all 8 &lt;em&gt;Harry Potter&lt;/em&gt; movies (thanks, Mom) and &lt;em&gt;A Promised Land&lt;/em&gt;. I figured it would be a good read, would take some time to get through, and I’d learn something along the way. Plus, it would make a good addition to my bookshelf, considering we have Michelle Obama’s &lt;em&gt;Becoming&lt;/em&gt; and Pete Souza’s &lt;em&gt;Obama: An Intimate Portrait&lt;/em&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;When Gma (aka Grandma) called and asked what was on my Christmas list, I told her about &lt;em&gt;A Promised Land.&lt;/em&gt; As expected, it was wrapped and given to me on Christmas day. I put it on the bookshelf and didn’t think much of it, until I picked it up to read in early April. As I do with every book when I first pull it off the shelf, I went to put my bookmark on the first page, while reading through the table of contents and what not. To my surprise, Gma wrote me a note on a blank page. I loved it. No matter what the outcome of the book, I knew this one would be a keeper.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Honey, Honey</title>
      <link>https://anotheryearofbooks.com/2021/04/honey-honey/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Apr 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://anotheryearofbooks.com/2021/04/honey-honey/</guid>
      <description>&lt;!-- raw HTML omitted --&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I commented to Matt recently that I have been saying I was going to watch a handful of shows for the past year, and despite having all this time at home, I haven’t. I don’t know if I should be proud for not watching too much TV or disappointed that I’m missing out on some good shows. But, I know that when I do have time to watch an episode or two, I’d rather be reading. That way, I can picture it all in my head, rather than on a screen. It’s a great hobby to have.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Checking Out a Book?</title>
      <link>https://anotheryearofbooks.com/2021/04/checking-out-a-book/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Apr 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://anotheryearofbooks.com/2021/04/checking-out-a-book/</guid>
      <description>&lt;!-- raw HTML omitted --&gt;
&lt;p&gt;As an early birthday present, Matt bought me the &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.amazon.com/All-new-Kindle-Oasis-now-with-adjustable-warm-light/dp/B07F7TLZF4/ref=sr_1_1?crid=16X48GP0I2CU7&amp;amp;dchild=1&amp;amp;keywords=kindle+oasis&amp;amp;qid=1617721749&amp;amp;sprefix=kindle+oas%2Caps%2C153&amp;amp;sr=8-1&#34;&gt;Amazon Kindle Oasis&lt;/a&gt;. For the past year, I have been borrowing ebooks from the library, or buying Kindle books and reading them on my phone or iPad. It was a great alternative since I couldn’t visit the library and check out a book. I never minded it, but it did hurt my eyes. Plus, as Matt will tell you, I would often be sitting on the coach with a charger plugged into my iPad while reading. His solution: a Kindle. I love it.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I had plans to read a paperback from my shelf, but made a detour to use my new Kindle. I had to give it a try with a book that has been sitting in my account for some time.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>So Kiss Me</title>
      <link>https://anotheryearofbooks.com/2021/03/so-kiss-me/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 26 Mar 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://anotheryearofbooks.com/2021/03/so-kiss-me/</guid>
      <description>&lt;!-- raw HTML omitted --&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I have never watched &lt;em&gt;The Bachelor&lt;/em&gt;, &lt;em&gt;The Bachelorette&lt;/em&gt;, or any of their many spin offs. I know people love to watch them; I have no desire. I’m sure at some point, in the many years the shows have been on air, that I have seen part of or all of one episode. But I don’t recall and I will not admit it.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Because of this, it seems odd that I would want to read the next book. It is, essentially, a book about a show like &lt;em&gt;The Bachelorette&lt;/em&gt;, but when I read the synopsis, I added it to my list. It sounded like a good read. Then one day, when I found myself at Target, I bought a copy. I still won’t be tuning into the shows anytime soon, but clearly, I will read books along the same lines.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tell a Friend</title>
      <link>https://anotheryearofbooks.com/2021/03/tell-a-friend/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Mar 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://anotheryearofbooks.com/2021/03/tell-a-friend/</guid>
      <description>&lt;!-- raw HTML omitted --&gt;
&lt;p&gt;It&amp;rsquo;s been a minute or two since there was a new post on Another Year of Books. After reading &lt;a href=&#34;https://anotheryearofbooks.com/2021/02/lend-me-your-ears/&#34;&gt;&lt;em&gt;Group&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/a&gt;, I quickly read through three other books (but didn&amp;rsquo;t post about them). By the end of February, I had already finished 10 books this year, so I decided to take a break. I couldn’t get myself to pick up one of the many books I have to read from my bookshelves; instead, I spent my time skimming books I have read before, which is what I do everytime I can’t get myself to focus on one book.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;On March 5, I picked up this next book. It was a Barnes &amp;amp; Noble monthly pick in January, and I found it when we stopped to browse one day.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Lend Me Your Ears</title>
      <link>https://anotheryearofbooks.com/2021/02/lend-me-your-ears/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 21 Feb 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://anotheryearofbooks.com/2021/02/lend-me-your-ears/</guid>
      <description>&lt;!-- raw HTML omitted --&gt;
&lt;p&gt;When someone asks me what I want for Christmas or my birthday, I always have a book on standby. Well, usually I have more than one. The same way I always have a lot of books on standby to be read. I try not to read all my new books right away and want to spread them out. This next read marks the second new, Christmas gift, book.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>LBD</title>
      <link>https://anotheryearofbooks.com/2021/02/lbd/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Feb 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://anotheryearofbooks.com/2021/02/lbd/</guid>
      <description>&lt;!-- raw HTML omitted --&gt;
&lt;p&gt;As I write this post, I am struggling to come up with the opening tidbit, which happens sometimes. I could make small talk and talk about the weather (it’s winter in Western PA, it sucks), or talk about my plans for the upcoming week (work, reading, celebrating Matt’s birthday). But, for some reason, I’m just not feeling it, so we’ll just jump right in.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>On Holiday</title>
      <link>https://anotheryearofbooks.com/2021/02/on-holiday/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Feb 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://anotheryearofbooks.com/2021/02/on-holiday/</guid>
      <description>&lt;!-- raw HTML omitted --&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Holiday reads should never be limited to the holiday season, which is why in January, I picked up &lt;em&gt;In a Holidaze&lt;/em&gt;, which was on loan to me from my sister. Maybe it was in an effort to hit up the bookshelf again, or it was because I was feeling nostalgic after taking down our Christmas tree in mid-January. Either way, it seemed like a wise decision (it did end up being a good decision).&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;It’s also fitting that this post is being published on Groundhog Day.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>U There?</title>
      <link>https://anotheryearofbooks.com/2021/01/u-there/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Jan 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://anotheryearofbooks.com/2021/01/u-there/</guid>
      <description>&lt;!-- raw HTML omitted --&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I love a good bookshelf. Whether it’s in someone’s home or a store or a library, bookshelves are cool. I was lucky that our house came with one. It’s been featured in a few pictures on AYOB already. Because I like to show off other items besides books on the shelf, I run out of room often. We ended up buying a small bookshelf for our guest bedroom. It added something to that part of the wall and gave me an extra spot to store books. Just what I need - more space!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I decided to focus on reading some of my unread, bookshelf books this year. This next read came from the Annual Library Book Sale I attend each year.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Back Again</title>
      <link>https://anotheryearofbooks.com/2021/01/back-again/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 16 Jan 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://anotheryearofbooks.com/2021/01/back-again/</guid>
      <description>&lt;!-- raw HTML omitted --&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The first AYOB post of 2021 is finally here! I spent some time at the very end of 2020 and the beginning of 2021 reading &lt;em&gt;Harry Potter and the Order of the Phoenix&lt;/em&gt; before digging into the first official book of 2021. I decided, after conferring with Matt, that to be counted towards the 2021 read count, the book must be completely finished during 2021. &lt;em&gt;Harry Potter&lt;/em&gt; spanned two years, so it won’t count towards either read count; however, this next read will.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Without further ado… the first official read of 2021.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
