<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>2021 Reads on Another Year of Books</title>
    <link>https://anotheryearofbooks.com/categories/2021-reads/</link>
    <description>Recent content in 2021 Reads on Another Year of Books</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 05 Dec 2021 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://anotheryearofbooks.com/categories/2021-reads/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Have We Met?</title>
      <link>https://anotheryearofbooks.com/2021/12/have-we-met/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 05 Dec 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://anotheryearofbooks.com/2021/12/have-we-met/</guid>
      <description>&lt;!-- raw HTML omitted --&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I didn’t do much shopping over Thanksgiving weekend. I bought a few clothing items, a couple of gifts, and that was pretty much it. But on the Sunday after Thanksgiving, after we watched Part 1 of &lt;em&gt;Get Back&lt;/em&gt; on Disney+ (I&amp;rsquo;d highly recommend watching this - it&amp;rsquo;s a time commitment but worth it), I was in the mood to go to Barnes and Noble. Mostly, I wanted to browse because that’s always a good way to add to your TBR list; but I knew I’d buy at least one book. I ended up with two. Then, I came home and started reading this next book.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hello, Hello</title>
      <link>https://anotheryearofbooks.com/2021/11/hello-hello/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 28 Nov 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://anotheryearofbooks.com/2021/11/hello-hello/</guid>
      <description>&lt;!-- raw HTML omitted --&gt;
&lt;p&gt;On a whim, I bought the first book below to read on my Kindle. I figured I’d read it and then wait for the second book from the library. After I finished the first in three days, I was so tempted to buy the second. I mentioned it to Matt and he said “you have a gift card, buy it.” He was right, so I bought it. Then, I read that one in three days as well.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Since these are the first two books in a series (the third, I expect will be released next year), I thought why not include them both in one post?&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Do I Know You?</title>
      <link>https://anotheryearofbooks.com/2021/11/do-i-know-you/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Nov 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://anotheryearofbooks.com/2021/11/do-i-know-you/</guid>
      <description>&lt;!-- raw HTML omitted --&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Let’s cut to the chase. I have no idea what to talk about in this intro blurb today. It’s just not coming to me, which seems to happen decently often. Sometimes, I just roll with it (like now) and other times, I think about it for a couple of days before inevitably talking about the weather, how it’s already almost a holiday (I’m talking to you, Thanksgiving), or about my TBR list. Well, now I’ve managed to talk about all three at once. Go me. Might as well just get on with it&amp;hellip;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The 52nd Read of 2021</title>
      <link>https://anotheryearofbooks.com/2021/11/the-52nd-read-of-2021/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 14 Nov 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://anotheryearofbooks.com/2021/11/the-52nd-read-of-2021/</guid>
      <description>&lt;!-- raw HTML omitted --&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Earlier this year, I hosted a “Ladies Movie Day” at my house. We decided to watch the 2019 version of &lt;em&gt;Little Women&lt;/em&gt;. Every one of us enjoyed it. I’ve watched it multiple times since and would highly recommend you watch it. I mean it has Meryl, Timothee Chalamet, Emma Watson, Laura Dern, Saorise Ronan and more! All are great! Anyway, great movie. Add that to your to watch list. I am partially ashamed to admit that prior to watching the movie, I never read the actual book. I always thought I’d get around to it and never did. So when I was visiting Meghan in August, we went by a bookstore and I picked up a copy. I decided it was the perfect book for the 52nd read of 2021.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Vacation, All I Ever Wanted</title>
      <link>https://anotheryearofbooks.com/2021/11/vacation-all-i-ever-wanted/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Nov 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://anotheryearofbooks.com/2021/11/vacation-all-i-ever-wanted/</guid>
      <description>&lt;!-- raw HTML omitted --&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Sometimes, you need to purchase a random book on your TBR list, just because it sounds like a good idea. That’s what happened with this next read. I have so many books waiting to be read, either on my bookshelf or loaded on my Kindle, but I skipped all of those and bought this next one with my Amazon gift card. I have no other explanation except I had a gift card and felt like buying a book. &lt;em&gt;The Layover&lt;/em&gt; was chosen.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Do You Like Me? Check Yes or No</title>
      <link>https://anotheryearofbooks.com/2021/10/do-you-like-me-check-yes-or-no/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Oct 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://anotheryearofbooks.com/2021/10/do-you-like-me-check-yes-or-no/</guid>
      <description>&lt;!-- raw HTML omitted --&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If I find an author I like, I tend to commit. I’ll go back and read all of their previous books (time permitting) and then automatically save their next releases to my “books” list on Amazon. That way, I don’t forget to check out the new ones, even if the release date is a year from now. I did the same with this next author. Guillory’s books have been featured on AYOB in the past, and her next book, due to be released in May 2022, is sitting in my TBR list.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>AYOB Goes On a Honeymoon</title>
      <link>https://anotheryearofbooks.com/2021/10/ayob-goes-on-a-honeymoon/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Oct 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://anotheryearofbooks.com/2021/10/ayob-goes-on-a-honeymoon/</guid>
      <description>&lt;!-- raw HTML omitted --&gt;
&lt;p&gt;On September 24, Matt and I did a big thing - we got married! It was great. Then, a couple of days later, we set off on a honeymoon. We planned to sit at the pool, relax and just enjoy ourselves. Of course, I was armed with my Kindle with multiple books downloaded and ready to go.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I started this first book on our first flight and finished the last the day after we got home. Rather than share three separate posts, I decided to combine all three books into one “AYOB Goes On a Honeymoon” event.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What a Week</title>
      <link>https://anotheryearofbooks.com/2021/10/what-a-week/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 10 Oct 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://anotheryearofbooks.com/2021/10/what-a-week/</guid>
      <description>&lt;!-- raw HTML omitted --&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I meant to post this a few days after the last post. Time got away from me. But after a three week hiatus, AYOB is back!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I read this one back in mid-September after purchasing it during a summertime “Amazon has buy-two-get-one-free, must buy three books” purchase. These sales will get me every time. It’s always a little tough to recap a plot after you’ve already read a handful of books in the meantime, but here we go!&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Chasing After You</title>
      <link>https://anotheryearofbooks.com/2021/09/chasing-after-you/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 Sep 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://anotheryearofbooks.com/2021/09/chasing-after-you/</guid>
      <description>&lt;!-- raw HTML omitted --&gt;
&lt;p&gt;It seems impossible to me that it’s already almost the end of September. But here we are. I feel like time is moving fast because all of the sudden, I have things to do. It’s not that I mind having things to do… I enjoy most of them. That said, I do like to sit inside, or outside pending the weather, and read a book, build a puzzle or just stay in. But here we are. Back to plans. I shall take it in stride.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>You&#39;re My Favorite Place</title>
      <link>https://anotheryearofbooks.com/2021/09/youre-my-favorite-place/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 18 Sep 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://anotheryearofbooks.com/2021/09/youre-my-favorite-place/</guid>
      <description>&lt;!-- raw HTML omitted --&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Reading a series can go one way or another. It could be &lt;em&gt;Harry Potter&lt;/em&gt;&amp;hellip; they are all great and you have to read one before you read the next. It could also be Kristen Ashley&amp;rsquo;s &lt;em&gt;Dream Team&lt;/em&gt; series or Jasmine Guillory&amp;rsquo;s &lt;em&gt;Wedding Date&lt;/em&gt; series&amp;hellip; they fit well as a series, but each could also be standalone novels. These ones could share characters and a common theme, yet can stand on their own two legs. This next read is the third in a series and falls into the second category.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Equation of Love</title>
      <link>https://anotheryearofbooks.com/2021/09/the-equation-of-love/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Sep 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://anotheryearofbooks.com/2021/09/the-equation-of-love/</guid>
      <description>&lt;!-- raw HTML omitted --&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In nine days, Matt and I are getting married. We got engaged in October 2019 and planned to get married in 2021. Even with all of this crazy going on, it all worked in our favor and the day is almost here. What an adventure. I’m looking forward to it, but I won’t lie … going to sit at a pool for a week afterwards is going to be great. I already have my Kindle books queued up and ready to roll.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Please Stand Clear of the Closing Doors</title>
      <link>https://anotheryearofbooks.com/2021/09/please-stand-clear-of-the-closing-doors/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 Sep 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://anotheryearofbooks.com/2021/09/please-stand-clear-of-the-closing-doors/</guid>
      <description>&lt;!-- raw HTML omitted --&gt;
&lt;p&gt;It seemed well timed that I finished this next book on the same day I was flying to New York City. I didn’t ride the Q when I was there (or at least, I don’t think I did. I just follow Meghan when she leads), but we did ride a lot of trains. Most importantly, we went to an All Time Low concert. Live music is great.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Every Rose Has Its Thorn</title>
      <link>https://anotheryearofbooks.com/2021/09/every-rose-has-its-thorn/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 Sep 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://anotheryearofbooks.com/2021/09/every-rose-has-its-thorn/</guid>
      <description>&lt;!-- raw HTML omitted --&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I’m usually behind on the TV shows everyone else is binging, with the exception of &lt;em&gt;Bridgerton&lt;/em&gt;. For years, I have been saying I was going to watch &lt;em&gt;Schitt’s Creek&lt;/em&gt;. I slowly watched the first and second season, then I couldn’t stop watching the third. I think I watched 7 episodes in 2 days. In the middle of reading &lt;em&gt;The Lost Apothecary&lt;/em&gt;, I made it to the opening of Rose Apothecary on the show. I found it funny that in a matter of days, I was hit with a single word that I barely can pronounce.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Sky is More Blue in Malibu</title>
      <link>https://anotheryearofbooks.com/2021/08/the-sky-is-more-blue-in-malibu/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 22 Aug 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://anotheryearofbooks.com/2021/08/the-sky-is-more-blue-in-malibu/</guid>
      <description>&lt;!-- raw HTML omitted --&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I’m sure I’ve mentioned before that my sister and I are constantly trading books. When she was last in Pittsburgh, she brought with her &lt;em&gt;Malibu Rising&lt;/em&gt;. I added it to the pile of books I had borrowed from her, knowing I’d end up reading it way before I read the two I’ve had on loan for the past year (or close to it). I was correct… I couldn’t wait to read this one, so I bumped it up on the list. Read on to see how that worked out for me.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tell Me More</title>
      <link>https://anotheryearofbooks.com/2021/08/tell-me-more/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 15 Aug 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://anotheryearofbooks.com/2021/08/tell-me-more/</guid>
      <description>&lt;!-- raw HTML omitted --&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I swear I add at least one book to my “To Be Read” list each week. Some weeks, it’s more depending on what is released. A while back, I added &lt;em&gt;The Husband Hour&lt;/em&gt;. I figured I’d get around to it at some point. Then Meghan, my sister, asked if I had read any of Jamie Brenner’s books and said that she liked this one. I then moved it up on the list and read it within 4 days. No sooner did I read it, then another book (or two… or five) took its spot on the TBR list.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>I Can Still Recall</title>
      <link>https://anotheryearofbooks.com/2021/08/i-can-still-recall/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Aug 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://anotheryearofbooks.com/2021/08/i-can-still-recall/</guid>
      <description>&lt;!-- raw HTML omitted --&gt;
&lt;p&gt;August, is that you? Ugh, it is. Gosh, summer is halfway over. It keeps getting hotter. I still need a tan… I should get on that (after I put on my sunscreen, of course). We’ve found ourselves out on our deck a lot more this summer. It’s been so nice to sit outside, put my feet up, and read a book (or several) until I get too hot (during the day) or too chilly (at night). Given that it’s August, it seems fitting that the next book is about summer.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Play It Again</title>
      <link>https://anotheryearofbooks.com/2021/07/play-it-again/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Jul 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://anotheryearofbooks.com/2021/07/play-it-again/</guid>
      <description>&lt;!-- raw HTML omitted --&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Do you ever hear a song on the radio (or Spotify or Apple Music) and it just fits? Fits the mood you’re in, fits what’s going on in your life at the moment, fits the traffic. I’m sure you have; it happens to me all the time. I’m guilty of hearing a song, album or artist I like so much, I constantly listen to the same thing for a period of time. I listen while I work, while I commute, while I cook, while I clean. Recently, it happened with the &lt;em&gt;In the Heights&lt;/em&gt; soundtrack, then before that, I listened to Pink because I watched her documentary, before that a song that came up in &lt;em&gt;Dream Spinner&lt;/em&gt;. Now, you all know my music listening habits. Soon, the playlist will strictly be All Time Low… have to be ready for my first in person concert in almost 2 years.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Had to Get Away</title>
      <link>https://anotheryearofbooks.com/2021/07/had-to-get-away/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Jul 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://anotheryearofbooks.com/2021/07/had-to-get-away/</guid>
      <description>&lt;!-- raw HTML omitted --&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Sometimes, this little intro blurb comes to me without any problems. Other times, like today, it is a struggle to think of anything to write. Should I talk about the weather? Summer flying by? Fun trips I have planned? Fun trips I hope you have planned? Or maybe I should just get to it. I think I’ll go with the last option.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hello, Jerry</title>
      <link>https://anotheryearofbooks.com/2021/07/hello-jerry/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Jul 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://anotheryearofbooks.com/2021/07/hello-jerry/</guid>
      <description>&lt;!-- raw HTML omitted --&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In 2018, we bought tickets to see Jerry Seinfeld in Pittsburgh in early 2019. I knew of him (of course - who doesn&amp;rsquo;t?), had seen &lt;em&gt;Comedians in Cars Getting Coffee&lt;/em&gt;, but had never seen much of &lt;em&gt;Seinfeld&lt;/em&gt;. We decided that we would start watching the show from the very beginning. At first, we had a lofty goal of finishing the sitcom before we went to the live show. That was a REALLY lofty goal; I mean there are 9 seasons and 180 episodes. It’s a time commitment. I think it took us over a year to finish all 9 seasons (we are slow when it comes to watching shows). By the end of the 9 seasons, I loved it.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Three Books, One Post</title>
      <link>https://anotheryearofbooks.com/2021/07/three-books-one-post/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Jul 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://anotheryearofbooks.com/2021/07/three-books-one-post/</guid>
      <description>&lt;!-- raw HTML omitted --&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I debated writing about the first two of these three books. I wasn’t feeling it; not because I didn’t like the books, I just didn’t feel like writing about them. I also read them in pretty quick succession. As I was reading &lt;em&gt;The Star-Crossed Sisters of Tuscany&lt;/em&gt;, I had the same thought. I liked the book, but I didn&amp;rsquo;t want to dedicate an entire post to it.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Then, I had an idea - I’ll write a small blurb about all three and put them in one post. That way, I get to talk about them, you get to read about them, and I don&amp;rsquo;t feel like I&amp;rsquo;m skipping a good amount of books on here. So without further ado, three books&amp;hellip; one post.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Who&#39;s That Creeping in the Window?</title>
      <link>https://anotheryearofbooks.com/2021/06/whos-that-creeping-in-the-window/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jun 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://anotheryearofbooks.com/2021/06/whos-that-creeping-in-the-window/</guid>
      <description>&lt;!-- raw HTML omitted --&gt;
&lt;p&gt;As I am sitting here trying to think of how to open this blog, I am listening to the &lt;em&gt;In the Heights&lt;/em&gt; film soundtrack. My mom came over this weekend and we watched it on HBO Max. I know that Another Year of Books is a blog about what books you should (and shouldn’t) read, but I feel the need to plug the movie here. We LOVED it. I thought it was amazing. I plan on watching it many more times before it leaves HBO Max on July 11. I probably will listen to the soundtrack all week (which is exactly what I did both when I saw &lt;em&gt;Hamilton&lt;/em&gt; in Pittsburgh and when we watched the movie). You should do the same.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Baby Fish Mouth</title>
      <link>https://anotheryearofbooks.com/2021/06/baby-fish-mouth/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 16 Jun 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://anotheryearofbooks.com/2021/06/baby-fish-mouth/</guid>
      <description>&lt;!-- raw HTML omitted --&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I will never commit to having only one favorite movie. I know myself too well to do that. I’ll end up changing my favorite each and every time. One time, it’ll be &lt;em&gt;The Sound of Music&lt;/em&gt;; another, &lt;em&gt;Guys and Dolls&lt;/em&gt;; the next, &lt;em&gt;First Wives Club&lt;/em&gt;. So instead, I have a top five, and on that top five, is the classic, 1989 Nora Ephron written, Rob Reiner direct, rom-com, &lt;em&gt;When Harry Met Sally&lt;/em&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I absolutely love it. I could watch it daily. I’d probably most often cite it as my favorite movie. Recently, it was added to HBOMax… I watched it the same day. It’s quotable, it’s funny, it’s the best. Even if you disagree, you can’t deny that &lt;em&gt;When Harry Met Sally&lt;/em&gt; has one pretty iconic scene. Plus, we all know “Baby Fish Mouth” is a GREAT pictionary answer. Actually, it’s probably the best.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Nice to Meet Ya</title>
      <link>https://anotheryearofbooks.com/2021/06/nice-to-meet-ya/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 10 Jun 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://anotheryearofbooks.com/2021/06/nice-to-meet-ya/</guid>
      <description>&lt;!-- raw HTML omitted --&gt;
&lt;p&gt;It’s weird to be social again. For over a year, we have all gotten up, gone to work (mostly in our homes), came home (or logged off your computer), and stayed in watching old favorites, new TV shows, or finally catching up on that one everyone has been talking about. The main character in this next read has pretty much been living our quarantine lives. Her goal? To put herself out there. My goal? To go outside into the world again. So far, it’s been fun.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>I&#39;ve Seen Fire and I&#39;ve Seen Rain</title>
      <link>https://anotheryearofbooks.com/2021/06/ive-seen-fire-and-ive-seen-rain/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 04 Jun 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://anotheryearofbooks.com/2021/06/ive-seen-fire-and-ive-seen-rain/</guid>
      <description>&lt;!-- raw HTML omitted --&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The number of books I have to read, whether they are on loan from my sister, on hold from the library, or my own books sitting on one of my bookshelves, keeps growing. So much so that I’ve decided to come up with a pattern to read them. This read is from my bookshelf. The next read is an e-book from the library. Following that I will be visiting one book on loan, before going back to the bookshelf. The only damper in my plans… The annual Library Book Sale is this weekend, and who knows what I could find. Wish me luck!&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sweet Dreams are Made of This</title>
      <link>https://anotheryearofbooks.com/2021/05/sweet-dreams-are-made-of-this/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 30 May 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://anotheryearofbooks.com/2021/05/sweet-dreams-are-made-of-this/</guid>
      <description>&lt;!-- raw HTML omitted --&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Anytime you are waiting for the next book in a series, it feels like the release date takes forever to arrive. This is exactly what happened to me with this next read. I read the second book in the series after it came out last December. I pre-ordered the third for my Kindle. When I saw that Barnes &amp;amp; Noble had the third book in stock the weekend before the offical release day, I cancelled my Kindle pre-order and headed to the store. Now, I’m back to waiting for the fourth book, which comes out in November&amp;hellip; the countdown is on.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>She&#39;s So Lucky</title>
      <link>https://anotheryearofbooks.com/2021/05/shes-so-lucky/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 May 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://anotheryearofbooks.com/2021/05/shes-so-lucky/</guid>
      <description>&lt;!-- raw HTML omitted --&gt;
&lt;p&gt;It’s hard to believe Memorial Day is creeping up on us, especially since a week and a half ago, I had to wear a thick sweater and a jacket because it was chilly outside. Now it&amp;rsquo;s shorts weather. That’s Western PA weather for you. I, for one, am looking forward to being able to sit on my deck and read, all while working on the little tan I will get.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>I&#39;m on a Boat</title>
      <link>https://anotheryearofbooks.com/2021/05/im-on-a-boat/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 12 May 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://anotheryearofbooks.com/2021/05/im-on-a-boat/</guid>
      <description>&lt;!-- raw HTML omitted --&gt;
&lt;p&gt;It seems like almost every time I go to Target, my book list grows by at least one, sometimes more. Occasionally, I actually buy the book I see, like when I bought &lt;a href=&#34;https://anotheryearofbooks.com/2021/03/so-kiss-me/&#34;&gt;&lt;em&gt;One to Watch&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/a&gt;; other times, I just add the book to my Amazon list for future reference. I stumbled upon this next read on a Target run. It sounded fun. Then, Amazon sent a promo code to buy it for my Kindle. I usually can’t turn down the promo codes, so here we are with book #18.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Thanks, Obama</title>
      <link>https://anotheryearofbooks.com/2021/05/thanks-obama/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 04 May 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://anotheryearofbooks.com/2021/05/thanks-obama/</guid>
      <description>&lt;!-- raw HTML omitted --&gt;
&lt;p&gt;There were two main things I wanted for Christmas this past year - a set of all 8 &lt;em&gt;Harry Potter&lt;/em&gt; movies (thanks, Mom) and &lt;em&gt;A Promised Land&lt;/em&gt;. I figured it would be a good read, would take some time to get through, and I’d learn something along the way. Plus, it would make a good addition to my bookshelf, considering we have Michelle Obama’s &lt;em&gt;Becoming&lt;/em&gt; and Pete Souza’s &lt;em&gt;Obama: An Intimate Portrait&lt;/em&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;When Gma (aka Grandma) called and asked what was on my Christmas list, I told her about &lt;em&gt;A Promised Land.&lt;/em&gt; As expected, it was wrapped and given to me on Christmas day. I put it on the bookshelf and didn’t think much of it, until I picked it up to read in early April. As I do with every book when I first pull it off the shelf, I went to put my bookmark on the first page, while reading through the table of contents and what not. To my surprise, Gma wrote me a note on a blank page. I loved it. No matter what the outcome of the book, I knew this one would be a keeper.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Honey, Honey</title>
      <link>https://anotheryearofbooks.com/2021/04/honey-honey/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Apr 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://anotheryearofbooks.com/2021/04/honey-honey/</guid>
      <description>&lt;!-- raw HTML omitted --&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I commented to Matt recently that I have been saying I was going to watch a handful of shows for the past year, and despite having all this time at home, I haven’t. I don’t know if I should be proud for not watching too much TV or disappointed that I’m missing out on some good shows. But, I know that when I do have time to watch an episode or two, I’d rather be reading. That way, I can picture it all in my head, rather than on a screen. It’s a great hobby to have.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Checking Out a Book?</title>
      <link>https://anotheryearofbooks.com/2021/04/checking-out-a-book/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Apr 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://anotheryearofbooks.com/2021/04/checking-out-a-book/</guid>
      <description>&lt;!-- raw HTML omitted --&gt;
&lt;p&gt;As an early birthday present, Matt bought me the &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.amazon.com/All-new-Kindle-Oasis-now-with-adjustable-warm-light/dp/B07F7TLZF4/ref=sr_1_1?crid=16X48GP0I2CU7&amp;amp;dchild=1&amp;amp;keywords=kindle+oasis&amp;amp;qid=1617721749&amp;amp;sprefix=kindle+oas%2Caps%2C153&amp;amp;sr=8-1&#34;&gt;Amazon Kindle Oasis&lt;/a&gt;. For the past year, I have been borrowing ebooks from the library, or buying Kindle books and reading them on my phone or iPad. It was a great alternative since I couldn’t visit the library and check out a book. I never minded it, but it did hurt my eyes. Plus, as Matt will tell you, I would often be sitting on the coach with a charger plugged into my iPad while reading. His solution: a Kindle. I love it.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I had plans to read a paperback from my shelf, but made a detour to use my new Kindle. I had to give it a try with a book that has been sitting in my account for some time.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>So Kiss Me</title>
      <link>https://anotheryearofbooks.com/2021/03/so-kiss-me/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 26 Mar 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://anotheryearofbooks.com/2021/03/so-kiss-me/</guid>
      <description>&lt;!-- raw HTML omitted --&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I have never watched &lt;em&gt;The Bachelor&lt;/em&gt;, &lt;em&gt;The Bachelorette&lt;/em&gt;, or any of their many spin offs. I know people love to watch them; I have no desire. I’m sure at some point, in the many years the shows have been on air, that I have seen part of or all of one episode. But I don’t recall and I will not admit it.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Because of this, it seems odd that I would want to read the next book. It is, essentially, a book about a show like &lt;em&gt;The Bachelorette&lt;/em&gt;, but when I read the synopsis, I added it to my list. It sounded like a good read. Then one day, when I found myself at Target, I bought a copy. I still won’t be tuning into the shows anytime soon, but clearly, I will read books along the same lines.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tell a Friend</title>
      <link>https://anotheryearofbooks.com/2021/03/tell-a-friend/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Mar 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://anotheryearofbooks.com/2021/03/tell-a-friend/</guid>
      <description>&lt;!-- raw HTML omitted --&gt;
&lt;p&gt;It&amp;rsquo;s been a minute or two since there was a new post on Another Year of Books. After reading &lt;a href=&#34;https://anotheryearofbooks.com/2021/02/lend-me-your-ears/&#34;&gt;&lt;em&gt;Group&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/a&gt;, I quickly read through three other books (but didn&amp;rsquo;t post about them). By the end of February, I had already finished 10 books this year, so I decided to take a break. I couldn’t get myself to pick up one of the many books I have to read from my bookshelves; instead, I spent my time skimming books I have read before, which is what I do everytime I can’t get myself to focus on one book.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;On March 5, I picked up this next book. It was a Barnes &amp;amp; Noble monthly pick in January, and I found it when we stopped to browse one day.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Lend Me Your Ears</title>
      <link>https://anotheryearofbooks.com/2021/02/lend-me-your-ears/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 21 Feb 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://anotheryearofbooks.com/2021/02/lend-me-your-ears/</guid>
      <description>&lt;!-- raw HTML omitted --&gt;
&lt;p&gt;When someone asks me what I want for Christmas or my birthday, I always have a book on standby. Well, usually I have more than one. The same way I always have a lot of books on standby to be read. I try not to read all my new books right away and want to spread them out. This next read marks the second new, Christmas gift, book.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>LBD</title>
      <link>https://anotheryearofbooks.com/2021/02/lbd/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Feb 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://anotheryearofbooks.com/2021/02/lbd/</guid>
      <description>&lt;!-- raw HTML omitted --&gt;
&lt;p&gt;As I write this post, I am struggling to come up with the opening tidbit, which happens sometimes. I could make small talk and talk about the weather (it’s winter in Western PA, it sucks), or talk about my plans for the upcoming week (work, reading, celebrating Matt’s birthday). But, for some reason, I’m just not feeling it, so we’ll just jump right in.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>On Holiday</title>
      <link>https://anotheryearofbooks.com/2021/02/on-holiday/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Feb 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://anotheryearofbooks.com/2021/02/on-holiday/</guid>
      <description>&lt;!-- raw HTML omitted --&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Holiday reads should never be limited to the holiday season, which is why in January, I picked up &lt;em&gt;In a Holidaze&lt;/em&gt;, which was on loan to me from my sister. Maybe it was in an effort to hit up the bookshelf again, or it was because I was feeling nostalgic after taking down our Christmas tree in mid-January. Either way, it seemed like a wise decision (it did end up being a good decision).&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;It’s also fitting that this post is being published on Groundhog Day.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>U There?</title>
      <link>https://anotheryearofbooks.com/2021/01/u-there/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Jan 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://anotheryearofbooks.com/2021/01/u-there/</guid>
      <description>&lt;!-- raw HTML omitted --&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I love a good bookshelf. Whether it’s in someone’s home or a store or a library, bookshelves are cool. I was lucky that our house came with one. It’s been featured in a few pictures on AYOB already. Because I like to show off other items besides books on the shelf, I run out of room often. We ended up buying a small bookshelf for our guest bedroom. It added something to that part of the wall and gave me an extra spot to store books. Just what I need - more space!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I decided to focus on reading some of my unread, bookshelf books this year. This next read came from the Annual Library Book Sale I attend each year.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Back Again</title>
      <link>https://anotheryearofbooks.com/2021/01/back-again/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 16 Jan 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://anotheryearofbooks.com/2021/01/back-again/</guid>
      <description>&lt;!-- raw HTML omitted --&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The first AYOB post of 2021 is finally here! I spent some time at the very end of 2020 and the beginning of 2021 reading &lt;em&gt;Harry Potter and the Order of the Phoenix&lt;/em&gt; before digging into the first official book of 2021. I decided, after conferring with Matt, that to be counted towards the 2021 read count, the book must be completely finished during 2021. &lt;em&gt;Harry Potter&lt;/em&gt; spanned two years, so it won’t count towards either read count; however, this next read will.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Without further ado… the first official read of 2021.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
