<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>2021 Reads on Another Year of Books</title>
    <link>https://anotheryearofbooks.com/categories/2021-reads/</link>
    <description>Recent content in 2021 Reads on Another Year of Books</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 26 Jan 2021 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://anotheryearofbooks.com/categories/2021-reads/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>U There?</title>
      <link>https://anotheryearofbooks.com/2021/01/u-there/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Jan 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://anotheryearofbooks.com/2021/01/u-there/</guid>
      <description>&lt;!-- raw HTML omitted --&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I love a good bookshelf. Whether it’s in someone’s home or a store or a library, bookshelves are cool. I was lucky that our house came with one. It’s been featured in a few pictures on AYOB already. Because I like to show off other items besides books on the shelf, I run out of room often. We ended up buying a small bookshelf for our guest bedroom. It added something to that part of the wall and gave me an extra spot to store books. Just what I need - more space!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I decided to focus on reading some of my unread, bookshelf books this year. This next read came from the Annual Library Book Sale I attend each year.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Back Again</title>
      <link>https://anotheryearofbooks.com/2021/01/back-again/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 16 Jan 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://anotheryearofbooks.com/2021/01/back-again/</guid>
      <description>&lt;!-- raw HTML omitted --&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The first AYOB post of 2021 is finally here! I spent some time at the very end of 2020 and the beginning of 2021 reading &lt;em&gt;Harry Potter and the Order of the Phoenix&lt;/em&gt; before digging into the first official book of 2021. I decided, after conferring with Matt, that to be counted towards the 2021 read count, the book must be completely finished during 2021. &lt;em&gt;Harry Potter&lt;/em&gt; spanned two years, so it won’t count towards either read count; however, this next read will.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Without further ado… the first official read of 2021.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
