<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Book Reviews on Another Year of Books</title>
    <link>https://anotheryearofbooks.com/categories/book-reviews/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Book Reviews on Another Year of Books</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 10 Jul 2020 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://anotheryearofbooks.com/categories/book-reviews/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>AN UPDATE</title>
      <link>https://anotheryearofbooks.com/2020/07/an-update/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 Jul 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://anotheryearofbooks.com/2020/07/an-update/</guid>
      <description>&lt;!-- raw HTML omitted --&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Greetings, readers of Another Year of Books!&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>HEY NOW, HEY NOW</title>
      <link>https://anotheryearofbooks.com/2020/06/hey-now-hey-now/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 25 Jun 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://anotheryearofbooks.com/2020/06/hey-now-hey-now/</guid>
      <description>&lt;!-- raw HTML omitted --&gt;
&lt;p&gt;… this is what dreams are made of! Apologies if that song is now stuck in your head.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Usually, I try to come up with a tidbit to include at the beginning of a post, before I go into the book and my thoughts on it. Today, I am struggling to come up with anything to say, so I’ll just jump right into it!&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>WHERE DO YOU SEE YOURSELF?</title>
      <link>https://anotheryearofbooks.com/2020/06/where-do-you-see-yourself/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Jun 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://anotheryearofbooks.com/2020/06/where-do-you-see-yourself/</guid>
      <description>&lt;!-- raw HTML omitted --&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Where do you see yourself?” is my least favorite question. I never know how to answer because it seems like a trick question. It could lead to great things, but it could lead to weird ones. Plus, life changes so constantly, how can you predict what life will be like in five years?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;That is why when asked, I don’t give an answer, or I give the broadest answer possible (i.e.: “Well, I would like to have a job.”). It’s better that way.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>&#39;OUR STORY BEGINS...&#39;</title>
      <link>https://anotheryearofbooks.com/2020/06/our-story-begins.../</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Jun 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://anotheryearofbooks.com/2020/06/our-story-begins.../</guid>
      <description>&lt;!-- raw HTML omitted --&gt;
&lt;p&gt;It’s hard to believe that it’s pretty much summer. Even though Memorial Day is the “unofficial” start to summer, the temperatures would make me think it’s summer anyway. I’ve had to start wearing sunscreen on longer walks. But the best part of summertime? Being able to stay in the AC and read a good book. I’ve already started participating.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>LOVE IT IF WE MADE IT</title>
      <link>https://anotheryearofbooks.com/2020/05/love-it-if-we-made-it/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 May 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://anotheryearofbooks.com/2020/05/love-it-if-we-made-it/</guid>
      <description>&lt;!-- raw HTML omitted --&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I do my best to remember when a sequel I want to read is coming out. Some authors make it easy, like Elin Hilderbrand. For the past three years, I could count on her to put out a new book in her Winter in Paradise series in the fall. When I stumble upon a sequel I forgot about, it’s always a nice thrill. This next book is a sequel that I completely forgot about until I was browsing Amazon one day and found it.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>BOW DOWN</title>
      <link>https://anotheryearofbooks.com/2020/05/bow-down/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 May 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://anotheryearofbooks.com/2020/05/bow-down/</guid>
      <description>&lt;!-- raw HTML omitted --&gt;
&lt;p&gt;It seems like the weather is finally turning here in Pittsburgh. Although, I can’t be too sure, as it snowed last week and now it’s 80 degrees. I&amp;rsquo;m hoping Mother Nature throws us a bone and it stays this way. It&amp;rsquo;s been nice to sit outside and read, or even walk and read if I can read the book on my phone and it looks safe.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>REWRITE THE STARS</title>
      <link>https://anotheryearofbooks.com/2020/05/rewrite-the-stars/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 08 May 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://anotheryearofbooks.com/2020/05/rewrite-the-stars/</guid>
      <description>&lt;!-- raw HTML omitted --&gt;
&lt;p&gt;It’s been a while since my last post. Don&amp;rsquo;t think I haven’t been reading - I’ve knocked out a few more books since the last post; I just decided not to write about them. While I’ve been gone, here is what I’ve read and a quick “should you read this?&amp;rdquo; answer.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;em&gt;Red, White &amp;amp; Royal Blue&lt;/em&gt; by Casey McQuiston
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;What would happen if the First Son of the USA and the Prince of England hooked up? I finished this one in two days if that tells you if I liked it or not. Warning, it is a little risque.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;em&gt;Harry Potter and the Prisoner of Azkaban&lt;/em&gt; by JK Rowling
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Do you even have to ask if you should read this one?&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;em&gt;The Wedding Party&lt;/em&gt; by Jasmine Guillory
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;I went back and read the third book of &lt;a href=&#34;https://anotheryearofbooks.com/2020/04/london-calling/&#34;&gt;this&lt;/a&gt; series. It was as I predicted; skip this one.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Read on to learn more about my latest read.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Yas, Queen</title>
      <link>https://anotheryearofbooks.com/2020/04/yas-queen/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 19 Apr 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://anotheryearofbooks.com/2020/04/yas-queen/</guid>
      <description>&lt;!-- raw HTML omitted --&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If you haven’t watched &lt;em&gt;Queer Eye: More than a Makeover&lt;/em&gt; on Netflix, I recommend you do so immediately. There are already four seasons, so it’ll occupy some of your time. I&amp;rsquo;m guessing you probably have some time on your hands right now. Each time a new season comes out, we watch the whole season within two weeks (we try to pace ourselves so we can enjoy it more).&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Why am I suggesting this at the beginning of my post? Well, the author of this next read is one of the stars.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>YOU HAVE HOPE AS EACH NEW DAY DAWNS</title>
      <link>https://anotheryearofbooks.com/2020/04/you-have-hope-as-each-new-day-dawns/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 Apr 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://anotheryearofbooks.com/2020/04/you-have-hope-as-each-new-day-dawns/</guid>
      <description>&lt;!-- raw HTML omitted --&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Back before we all stayed home, I visited my aunt and grandparents to play cards. It’s one of our favorite things to do. Books came up as part of the conversation, as they usually do. My aunt told me I needed to read this book next. She even brought her copy to lend to me. Turns out, I already bought it on my latest trip to Half Price Books. After I finished Harry Potter and the Chamber of Secrets, I bumped this one up to next on my list.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>London Calling</title>
      <link>https://anotheryearofbooks.com/2020/04/london-calling/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Apr 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://anotheryearofbooks.com/2020/04/london-calling/</guid>
      <description>I won’t lie. I skipped the third book in this series. Whoops. I honestly didn’t mean to, but when I realized I did, I decided to push on and not turn back. Now, I’m not going to, but just a forewarning that this is book number four in the series, not three. If you are looking for three, The Wedding Party is the name.
 Book Read: Royal Holiday
Author: Jasmine Guillory</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Not Even Close, Not Even a Little Bit, Not Even at All</title>
      <link>https://anotheryearofbooks.com/2020/03/not-even-close-not-even-a-little-bit-not-even-at-all/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 30 Mar 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://anotheryearofbooks.com/2020/03/not-even-close-not-even-a-little-bit-not-even-at-all/</guid>
      <description>&lt;!-- raw HTML omitted --&gt;
&lt;p&gt;At this point, while staying in as much as possible since last weekend, I finished reading one book (Harry Potter and the Chamber of Secrets), downloaded a workout app (and used it), watched over two seasons of The Office, survived five days of working from home, and cleaned our stove. I figured after all of that, it was time to write another blog. Which brings us here.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Thank You for Being a Friend</title>
      <link>https://anotheryearofbooks.com/2020/03/thank-you-for-being-a-friend/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 15 Mar 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://anotheryearofbooks.com/2020/03/thank-you-for-being-a-friend/</guid>
      <description>Let’s admit it. We all know we are living in a weird time. I mean, no March Madness?! What will I do without it? Not lose in the family bracket, that&amp;rsquo;s what I&amp;rsquo;ll do.
I do see a bright side… there is always another book to read. What better way to pass the time? Yes, I know there’s such things as Netflix and Disney+, but to me, there is still nothing better than a great read.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>To the Window, to the Wall!</title>
      <link>https://anotheryearofbooks.com/2020/03/to-the-window-to-the-wall/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 07 Mar 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://anotheryearofbooks.com/2020/03/to-the-window-to-the-wall/</guid>
      <description>After I read something more challenging, like the last read, I always want my next book to be easy and light-hearted. Usually, I stick to the authors I know. That’s exactly how I picked this next book. Book Read: The Proposal 
Author: Jasmine Guillory
2020 Book Count: 6
Nikole Paterson’s boyfriend of five months just proposed on the Jumbotron at a baseball game, with no warning. Nik says no. It doesn’t go over well, at all.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Life Is Like a Cactus</title>
      <link>https://anotheryearofbooks.com/2020/02/life-is-like-a-cactus/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 29 Feb 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://anotheryearofbooks.com/2020/02/life-is-like-a-cactus/</guid>
      <description>This was the first e-book I borrowed from the library. I haven’t tried it before, because I always just went to the library. But at some point soon, the library I go to is closing for renovations. I wanted to make sure I had a back up plan, besides ordering ahead and picking it up.
Except when my eyes were tired, it definitely is a great alternative. Book Read: The Cactus</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>I&#39;m The Wife</title>
      <link>https://anotheryearofbooks.com/2020/02/im-the-wife/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Feb 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://anotheryearofbooks.com/2020/02/im-the-wife/</guid>
      <description>I am trying to clean out my bookshelf by reading the books I haven’t yet read. Mostly, I’m doing this so I can give some back to the library before I buy more later this year. It’s important to have priorities, right? This next read is one of those books - I purchased it at the library’s book sale last summer. I needed to decide if it would stay or go back to the library.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Now You’re Just Somebody</title>
      <link>https://anotheryearofbooks.com/2020/02/now-youre-just-somebody/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 12 Feb 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://anotheryearofbooks.com/2020/02/now-youre-just-somebody/</guid>
      <description>Since I started writing/editing this post, I have been singing Goyte’s hit… “Now you’re just somebody that I used to know… SOMEBODY (I used to know).” I’m not sure if that’s exactly how the lyrics go, but in my head, it makes perfect sense. This would be why I write blogs and not song lyrics. Stick to what you think you are good at, right?
Book Read: The Girl He Used to Know</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A Drop of Golden Sun</title>
      <link>https://anotheryearofbooks.com/2020/02/a-drop-of-golden-sun/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 06 Feb 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://anotheryearofbooks.com/2020/02/a-drop-of-golden-sun/</guid>
      <description>The Sound of Music is one of my all time favorite movies, hands down. I always have loved it. My family will tell you they can’t count how many times they had to rewind the two VHS’s so I could watch it again. Even now, I have watched it on Disney+ at least five times (they even have the intermission!). I can’t help it. I want to climb every mountain! So, of course I wanted to read Julie Andrews’ latest memoir.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Guess Who&#39;s Back...</title>
      <link>https://anotheryearofbooks.com/2020/01/guess-whos-back.../</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 Jan 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://anotheryearofbooks.com/2020/01/guess-whos-back.../</guid>
      <description>It’s Another Year of Books! I seem to have a trend when it comes to my first book of the year (or within the first 3). I always seem to start with an autobiography or memoir. In 2018, Anna Faris’s Unqualified was number 3; in 2019, Michelle Obama’s Becoming was the first read.
2020 is no different.
Book Read: Me
Author: Elton John
2020 Book Count: 1
We all know Elton John.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Never Drink the Kool Aid (or Smoothie)</title>
      <link>https://anotheryearofbooks.com/2019/05/never-drink-the-kool-aid-or-smoothie/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://anotheryearofbooks.com/2019/05/never-drink-the-kool-aid-or-smoothie/</guid>
      <description>I am eagerly waiting for the second season of Big Little Lies. I loved the show, and the book started me down a path of reading Liane Moriarty’s books. Of course, I had to read her newest novel:
Book Read: Nine Perfect Strangers
Author: Liane Moriarty
Number of Books Read, 2019 Edition: 15
Frances Welty fell victim to an Internet dating scam. Heartbroken and in need of a break, at the advice of a friend, she signs up for a 10 day cleanse at the Tranquillum House.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Do You Remember, the 21st Night of December?</title>
      <link>https://anotheryearofbooks.com/2019/01/do-you-remember-the-21st-night-of-december/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 19 Jan 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://anotheryearofbooks.com/2019/01/do-you-remember-the-21st-night-of-december/</guid>
      <description>I’m 26 years old, and every year, I’m still asked what’s on my Christmas list. The answer is usually pretty standard: money, something I’ve been putting off buying, and books. Becoming was a Christmas gift (thanks, Mom), as was this next read (thanks, Aunt Barb), and the one after this (again, thanks Aunt Barb). My philosophy: there is plenty of room on my bookshelf, so no amount of books is too many.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>