<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Book Reviews on Another Year of Books</title>
    <link>https://anotheryearofbooks.com/categories/book-reviews/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Book Reviews on Another Year of Books</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 15 Aug 2020 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://anotheryearofbooks.com/categories/book-reviews/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>KEVIN KWAN IS BACK</title>
      <link>https://anotheryearofbooks.com/2020/08/kevin-kwan-is-back/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 15 Aug 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://anotheryearofbooks.com/2020/08/kevin-kwan-is-back/</guid>
      <description>&lt;!-- raw HTML omitted --&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I try to do my best to keep up with authors that I like; meaning, I try to pay attention to when a new book is coming out. A week after this one came out, it was already at my house, waiting to be read on vacation. Why? If I enjoyed Kevin Kwan’s newest book half as much as I enjoyed the Crazy Rich Asians series, it would be a great read.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>WE&#39;RE BACK IN 3, 2, 1...</title>
      <link>https://anotheryearofbooks.com/2020/08/were-back-in-3-2-1.../</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 05 Aug 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://anotheryearofbooks.com/2020/08/were-back-in-3-2-1.../</guid>
      <description>&lt;!-- raw HTML omitted --&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Welcome back to Another Year of Books! It’s been over a month since my last post about a recently read book. I’ve taken the past month to just relax, whether it was by re-reading some books I previously read, or by reading some corny romance novels I stumbled upon. Long story short, I didn’t have much to write home about. But I’m back! Don’t worry, more reads are coming soon.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>AN UPDATE</title>
      <link>https://anotheryearofbooks.com/2020/07/an-update/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 Jul 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://anotheryearofbooks.com/2020/07/an-update/</guid>
      <description>&lt;!-- raw HTML omitted --&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Greetings, readers of Another Year of Books!&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>HEY NOW, HEY NOW</title>
      <link>https://anotheryearofbooks.com/2020/06/hey-now-hey-now/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 25 Jun 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://anotheryearofbooks.com/2020/06/hey-now-hey-now/</guid>
      <description>&lt;!-- raw HTML omitted --&gt;
&lt;p&gt;… this is what dreams are made of! Apologies if that song is now stuck in your head.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Usually, I try to come up with a tidbit to include at the beginning of a post, before I go into the book and my thoughts on it. Today, I am struggling to come up with anything to say, so I’ll just jump right into it!&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>WHERE DO YOU SEE YOURSELF?</title>
      <link>https://anotheryearofbooks.com/2020/06/where-do-you-see-yourself/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Jun 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://anotheryearofbooks.com/2020/06/where-do-you-see-yourself/</guid>
      <description>&lt;!-- raw HTML omitted --&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Where do you see yourself?” is my least favorite question. I never know how to answer because it seems like a trick question. It could lead to great things, but it could lead to weird ones. Plus, life changes so constantly, how can you predict what life will be like in five years?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;That is why when asked, I don’t give an answer, or I give the broadest answer possible (i.e.: “Well, I would like to have a job.”). It’s better that way.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>&#39;OUR STORY BEGINS...&#39;</title>
      <link>https://anotheryearofbooks.com/2020/06/our-story-begins.../</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Jun 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://anotheryearofbooks.com/2020/06/our-story-begins.../</guid>
      <description>&lt;!-- raw HTML omitted --&gt;
&lt;p&gt;It’s hard to believe that it’s pretty much summer. Even though Memorial Day is the “unofficial” start to summer, the temperatures would make me think it’s summer anyway. I’ve had to start wearing sunscreen on longer walks. But the best part of summertime? Being able to stay in the AC and read a good book. I’ve already started participating.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>LOVE IT IF WE MADE IT</title>
      <link>https://anotheryearofbooks.com/2020/05/love-it-if-we-made-it/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 May 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://anotheryearofbooks.com/2020/05/love-it-if-we-made-it/</guid>
      <description>&lt;!-- raw HTML omitted --&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I do my best to remember when a sequel I want to read is coming out. Some authors make it easy, like Elin Hilderbrand. For the past three years, I could count on her to put out a new book in her Winter in Paradise series in the fall. When I stumble upon a sequel I forgot about, it’s always a nice thrill. This next book is a sequel that I completely forgot about until I was browsing Amazon one day and found it.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>BOW DOWN</title>
      <link>https://anotheryearofbooks.com/2020/05/bow-down/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 May 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://anotheryearofbooks.com/2020/05/bow-down/</guid>
      <description>&lt;!-- raw HTML omitted --&gt;
&lt;p&gt;It seems like the weather is finally turning here in Pittsburgh. Although, I can’t be too sure, as it snowed last week and now it’s 80 degrees. I&amp;rsquo;m hoping Mother Nature throws us a bone and it stays this way. It&amp;rsquo;s been nice to sit outside and read, or even walk and read if I can read the book on my phone and it looks safe.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>REWRITE THE STARS</title>
      <link>https://anotheryearofbooks.com/2020/05/rewrite-the-stars/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 08 May 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://anotheryearofbooks.com/2020/05/rewrite-the-stars/</guid>
      <description>&lt;!-- raw HTML omitted --&gt;
&lt;p&gt;It’s been a while since my last post. Don&amp;rsquo;t think I haven’t been reading - I’ve knocked out a few more books since the last post; I just decided not to write about them. While I’ve been gone, here is what I’ve read and a quick “should you read this?&amp;rdquo; answer.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;em&gt;Red, White &amp;amp; Royal Blue&lt;/em&gt; by Casey McQuiston
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;What would happen if the First Son of the USA and the Prince of England hooked up? I finished this one in two days if that tells you if I liked it or not. Warning, it is a little risque.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;em&gt;Harry Potter and the Prisoner of Azkaban&lt;/em&gt; by JK Rowling
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Do you even have to ask if you should read this one?&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;em&gt;The Wedding Party&lt;/em&gt; by Jasmine Guillory
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;I went back and read the third book of &lt;a href=&#34;https://anotheryearofbooks.com/2020/04/london-calling/&#34;&gt;this&lt;/a&gt; series. It was as I predicted; skip this one.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Read on to learn more about my latest read.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Yas, Queen</title>
      <link>https://anotheryearofbooks.com/2020/04/yas-queen/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 19 Apr 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://anotheryearofbooks.com/2020/04/yas-queen/</guid>
      <description>&lt;!-- raw HTML omitted --&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If you haven’t watched &lt;em&gt;Queer Eye: More than a Makeover&lt;/em&gt; on Netflix, I recommend you do so immediately. There are already four seasons, so it’ll occupy some of your time. I&amp;rsquo;m guessing you probably have some time on your hands right now. Each time a new season comes out, we watch the whole season within two weeks (we try to pace ourselves so we can enjoy it more).&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Why am I suggesting this at the beginning of my post? Well, the author of this next read is one of the stars.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>YOU HAVE HOPE AS EACH NEW DAY DAWNS</title>
      <link>https://anotheryearofbooks.com/2020/04/you-have-hope-as-each-new-day-dawns/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 Apr 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://anotheryearofbooks.com/2020/04/you-have-hope-as-each-new-day-dawns/</guid>
      <description>&lt;!-- raw HTML omitted --&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Back before we all stayed home, I visited my aunt and grandparents to play cards. It’s one of our favorite things to do. Books came up as part of the conversation, as they usually do. My aunt told me I needed to read this book next. She even brought her copy to lend to me. Turns out, I already bought it on my latest trip to Half Price Books. After I finished Harry Potter and the Chamber of Secrets, I bumped this one up to next on my list.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>London Calling</title>
      <link>https://anotheryearofbooks.com/2020/04/london-calling/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Apr 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://anotheryearofbooks.com/2020/04/london-calling/</guid>
      <description>I won’t lie. I skipped the third book in this series. Whoops. I honestly didn’t mean to, but when I realized I did, I decided to push on and not turn back. Now, I’m not going to, but just a forewarning that this is book number four in the series, not three. If you are looking for three, The Wedding Party is the name.
 Book Read: Royal Holiday
Author: Jasmine Guillory</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Not Even Close, Not Even a Little Bit, Not Even at All</title>
      <link>https://anotheryearofbooks.com/2020/03/not-even-close-not-even-a-little-bit-not-even-at-all/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 30 Mar 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://anotheryearofbooks.com/2020/03/not-even-close-not-even-a-little-bit-not-even-at-all/</guid>
      <description>&lt;!-- raw HTML omitted --&gt;
&lt;p&gt;At this point, while staying in as much as possible since last weekend, I finished reading one book (Harry Potter and the Chamber of Secrets), downloaded a workout app (and used it), watched over two seasons of The Office, survived five days of working from home, and cleaned our stove. I figured after all of that, it was time to write another blog. Which brings us here.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Thank You for Being a Friend</title>
      <link>https://anotheryearofbooks.com/2020/03/thank-you-for-being-a-friend/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 15 Mar 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://anotheryearofbooks.com/2020/03/thank-you-for-being-a-friend/</guid>
      <description>Let’s admit it. We all know we are living in a weird time. I mean, no March Madness?! What will I do without it? Not lose in the family bracket, that&amp;rsquo;s what I&amp;rsquo;ll do.
I do see a bright side… there is always another book to read. What better way to pass the time? Yes, I know there’s such things as Netflix and Disney+, but to me, there is still nothing better than a great read.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>To the Window, to the Wall!</title>
      <link>https://anotheryearofbooks.com/2020/03/to-the-window-to-the-wall/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 07 Mar 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://anotheryearofbooks.com/2020/03/to-the-window-to-the-wall/</guid>
      <description>After I read something more challenging, like the last read, I always want my next book to be easy and light-hearted. Usually, I stick to the authors I know. That’s exactly how I picked this next book. Book Read: The Proposal 
Author: Jasmine Guillory
2020 Book Count: 6
Nikole Paterson’s boyfriend of five months just proposed on the Jumbotron at a baseball game, with no warning. Nik says no. It doesn’t go over well, at all.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Life Is Like a Cactus</title>
      <link>https://anotheryearofbooks.com/2020/02/life-is-like-a-cactus/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 29 Feb 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://anotheryearofbooks.com/2020/02/life-is-like-a-cactus/</guid>
      <description>This was the first e-book I borrowed from the library. I haven’t tried it before, because I always just went to the library. But at some point soon, the library I go to is closing for renovations. I wanted to make sure I had a back up plan, besides ordering ahead and picking it up.
Except when my eyes were tired, it definitely is a great alternative. Book Read: The Cactus</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>I&#39;m The Wife</title>
      <link>https://anotheryearofbooks.com/2020/02/im-the-wife/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Feb 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://anotheryearofbooks.com/2020/02/im-the-wife/</guid>
      <description>I am trying to clean out my bookshelf by reading the books I haven’t yet read. Mostly, I’m doing this so I can give some back to the library before I buy more later this year. It’s important to have priorities, right? This next read is one of those books - I purchased it at the library’s book sale last summer. I needed to decide if it would stay or go back to the library.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Now You’re Just Somebody</title>
      <link>https://anotheryearofbooks.com/2020/02/now-youre-just-somebody/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 12 Feb 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://anotheryearofbooks.com/2020/02/now-youre-just-somebody/</guid>
      <description>Since I started writing/editing this post, I have been singing Goyte’s hit… “Now you’re just somebody that I used to know… SOMEBODY (I used to know).” I’m not sure if that’s exactly how the lyrics go, but in my head, it makes perfect sense. This would be why I write blogs and not song lyrics. Stick to what you think you are good at, right?
Book Read: The Girl He Used to Know</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A Drop of Golden Sun</title>
      <link>https://anotheryearofbooks.com/2020/02/a-drop-of-golden-sun/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 06 Feb 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://anotheryearofbooks.com/2020/02/a-drop-of-golden-sun/</guid>
      <description>The Sound of Music is one of my all time favorite movies, hands down. I always have loved it. My family will tell you they can’t count how many times they had to rewind the two VHS’s so I could watch it again. Even now, I have watched it on Disney+ at least five times (they even have the intermission!). I can’t help it. I want to climb every mountain! So, of course I wanted to read Julie Andrews’ latest memoir.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Guess Who&#39;s Back...</title>
      <link>https://anotheryearofbooks.com/2020/01/guess-whos-back.../</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 Jan 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://anotheryearofbooks.com/2020/01/guess-whos-back.../</guid>
      <description>It’s Another Year of Books! I seem to have a trend when it comes to my first book of the year (or within the first 3). I always seem to start with an autobiography or memoir. In 2018, Anna Faris’s Unqualified was number 3; in 2019, Michelle Obama’s Becoming was the first read.
2020 is no different.
Book Read: Me
Author: Elton John
2020 Book Count: 1
We all know Elton John.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>NUMBER 52</title>
      <link>https://anotheryearofbooks.com/2020/01/number-52/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Jan 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://anotheryearofbooks.com/2020/01/number-52/</guid>
      <description>On December 31, 2019, at 12:04 PM, I sent my sister this text:

It was the last day of the year. Since December 25, I had read three books (and wrote 0 posts). On Christmas Eve, when asked if I was going to read all 52, I said no. I didn’t anticipate reading three books in 6 days. It helped that Matt has been sick and we didn’t leave the house much, and that the three books kept my attention.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Double Dutch</title>
      <link>https://anotheryearofbooks.com/2020/01/double-dutch/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 Jan 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://anotheryearofbooks.com/2020/01/double-dutch/</guid>
      <description>I actually started reading this book before I picked up The Christmas Star. I was only 10 pages or so into this one when I set it back down. Then when I picked it back up again, I started over. It only seemed right. I don’t often start a book and stop for another, but decided that Christmas was an acceptable night to do so.  Book Read: Going Dutch</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>SO THIS IS CHRISTMAS</title>
      <link>https://anotheryearofbooks.com/2019/12/so-this-is-christmas/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 31 Dec 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://anotheryearofbooks.com/2019/12/so-this-is-christmas/</guid>
      <description>On Christmas night, I put on How the Grinch Stole Christmas (first the animated version, which was then followed by the Jim Carrey version) and settled in with a comfy blanket. I was in the mood for a Christmas themed book. Luckily, I had one on my shelf. I mean, truthfully, I only have one. This was my only option. I picked it up, and by the time I went to bed, I was half way finished.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>THIS COULD BE THE START OF SOMETHING NEW</title>
      <link>https://anotheryearofbooks.com/2019/12/this-could-be-the-start-of-something-new/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 28 Dec 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://anotheryearofbooks.com/2019/12/this-could-be-the-start-of-something-new/</guid>
      <description>Every Friday, theSkimm recommends a book. I look forward to it every week. I reckon all but one a month make it onto my “to read” list. This Friday, I beat t_heSkimm_! What a day. Last week at the library, I picked up yesterday&amp;rsquo;s recommendation. I am impressed with myself to say the least.
 Book Read: Evvie Drake Starts Over
Author: Linda Holmes
Number of Books Read, 2019 Edition: 49</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>TROUBLE, TROUBLE, TROUBLE</title>
      <link>https://anotheryearofbooks.com/2019/12/trouble-trouble-trouble/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Dec 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://anotheryearofbooks.com/2019/12/trouble-trouble-trouble/</guid>
      <description>It’s hard to find time to read during all the holiday hooplah. There’s the cooking, the baking, the wrapping, the cleaning, the Christmas movies, the family time. Although a book is a good excuse to avoid family time. Just saying. (I did not do this, also just saying.)
 Book Read: Fleishman is In Trouble
Author: Taffy Brodesser-Akner
Number of Books Read, 2019 Edition: 48
 Toby Fleishman became a ladies’ man after his wife finally agreed to his requested divorce.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CIRCLE, CIRCLE, DOT, DOT</title>
      <link>https://anotheryearofbooks.com/2019/12/circle-circle-dot-dot/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Dec 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://anotheryearofbooks.com/2019/12/circle-circle-dot-dot/</guid>
      <description>The last read was a heavy topic. I enjoyed it (find out here), but afterwards, I wanted my next read to be more mindless and quick. I found it at my trip to the library at lunchtime last week (I know, a book found at a library - shocking!)
 Book Read: The Friend Zone
Author: Abby Jimenez
Number of Books Read, 2019 Edition: 47
 Kristen Peterson’s best friend is getting married.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>WHEN I GROW UP</title>
      <link>https://anotheryearofbooks.com/2019/12/when-i-grow-up/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 15 Dec 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://anotheryearofbooks.com/2019/12/when-i-grow-up/</guid>
      <description>In the first grade, our teacher asked us what we wanted to be when we grew up. I remember I wanted to be a teacher. We made paper dolls showing what we wanted to be - I can still picture what mine looked like (she was wearing a pink shirt). I also remember multiple girls in my class wanting to be models. But I’m pretty sure one girl copied the other, so who knows!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>PARADISE BY THE DASHBOARD LIGHT</title>
      <link>https://anotheryearofbooks.com/2019/12/paradise-by-the-dashboard-light/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 08 Dec 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://anotheryearofbooks.com/2019/12/paradise-by-the-dashboard-light/</guid>
      <description>Sequels can be tough to write about. I don’t want to give away too much. That way you want to read this book, but you also want to read the first in the series. It is a line easily crossed. If I say too much for the second book, do I give away the ending of the first?
Gosh, I hope not.  Book Read: What Happens in Paradise
Author: Elin Hilderbrand</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>LET&#39;S FEAST!</title>
      <link>https://anotheryearofbooks.com/2019/11/lets-feast/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Nov 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://anotheryearofbooks.com/2019/11/lets-feast/</guid>
      <description>I hope at this point, everyone has watched Always Be My Maybe on Netflix, or maybe the comedy specials Baby Cobra or Hard Knock Wife. Because Ali Wong is hysterical; completely hysterical. My friends and I are obsessed. I’ve watched Always Be My Maybe I don’t even know how many times. I mean, it has Keanu Reeves! It’s a laugh-out-loud romantic comedy, that is more comedy than most.
When I saw that Ali Wong wrote a book, I knew I had to read it, leading to read number 44.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>FASTER, DENNY, FASTER</title>
      <link>https://anotheryearofbooks.com/2019/11/faster-denny-faster/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 23 Nov 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://anotheryearofbooks.com/2019/11/faster-denny-faster/</guid>
      <description>This next read came as a recommendation from a friend. Yes, I know it’s a movie too, so eventually I would have gotten to it. But a recommendation usually bumps up the book on the &amp;ldquo;to read&amp;rdquo; list. Really, if this book wasn’t as good as I expected, who knows what would have happened - awkwardness, bitterness, loss of a friend. Just kidding of course. I will never hold a book recommendation grudge… unless it is really, really bad.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>AND MY FLIPPY FLOPPIES</title>
      <link>https://anotheryearofbooks.com/2019/11/and-my-flippy-floppies/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 17 Nov 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://anotheryearofbooks.com/2019/11/and-my-flippy-floppies/</guid>
      <description>In the first weekend of November, my mom, aunt and I ventured to New York City to visit my sister and brother-in-law. We planned ahead for 2 main events - to see Waitress on Broadway, since it is in its final run, and to go to Strand Book Store. Strand is a magical place that has EIGHTEEN miles of books. You read that right - eighteen miles. Us visitors came prepared with room in our suitcases.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>EVERYTHING IS FINE</title>
      <link>https://anotheryearofbooks.com/2019/11/everything-is-fine/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 07 Nov 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://anotheryearofbooks.com/2019/11/everything-is-fine/</guid>
      <description>I’m writing this while it is 34 degrees outside. Thirty four! Did I blink and miss fall? It really feels like I did. It’s a good thing there are so many books that go well with a cozy blanket. It’s also a good thing that I bought four new books on a trip to visit my sister and brother-in-law in New York City (shout out to the Strand!).
 Book Read: Mrs.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CAUSE I&#39;M BURNIN&#39; UP</title>
      <link>https://anotheryearofbooks.com/2019/10/cause-im-burnin-up/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 Oct 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://anotheryearofbooks.com/2019/10/cause-im-burnin-up/</guid>
      <description>When I was writing this, I could not get Burnin’ Up by the Jonas Brothers out of my head. Why? Because it is a catchy song. Also, because I love the Jonas Brothers; meaning I LOVE the Jonas Brothers. My aunt and I had a fabulous time at their concert in September. “I’m hot. You’re cold…”  Book Read: Things You Save in a Fire
Author: Katherine Carter
Number of Books Read, 2019 Edition: 40</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>OK, LADIES...</title>
      <link>https://anotheryearofbooks.com/2019/10/ok-ladies.../</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Oct 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://anotheryearofbooks.com/2019/10/ok-ladies.../</guid>
      <description>Let us get in formation.
I struggle with non-fiction. I’m sure I’ve mentioned this each time I talk about non-fiction, but it’s true. This book took me awhile to read. Not because it was a bad book, but because I feel like I have to really pay attention to what I’m reading.
This is a book that requires your attention, for good reasons. And I’m not just talking to the ladies.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>DECISIONS, DECISIONS, DECISIONS</title>
      <link>https://anotheryearofbooks.com/2019/10/decisions-decisions-decisions/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 11 Oct 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://anotheryearofbooks.com/2019/10/decisions-decisions-decisions/</guid>
      <description>I look forward to Friday’s. Not just because TGIF, but because every Friday, the Skimm has a book recommendation. I’d say 95% of the time, I end up adding the book to my “to read” list; then, I wait. I wait until the book is finally available at the library. Usually it takes weeks, at the minimum.
Somehow, when I went to return An American Marriage to the library, I found this next read.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>NOW, DO YOU LOVE ME?</title>
      <link>https://anotheryearofbooks.com/2019/10/now-do-you-love-me/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 06 Oct 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://anotheryearofbooks.com/2019/10/now-do-you-love-me/</guid>
      <description>It seems like October crashed into me. I looked up and BAM&amp;hellip; October. I feel like I should have seen it coming considering Giant Eagle had Halloween candy out before school started. This is entirely too soon, by the way. Don’t even get me started on the Christmas decorations that are already out in stores.
Finishing this book means I have 15 more to read to make it to 52 books read in 2019.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>I GOT MY FIRST REAL SIX-STRING</title>
      <link>https://anotheryearofbooks.com/2019/10/i-got-my-first-real-six-string/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Oct 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://anotheryearofbooks.com/2019/10/i-got-my-first-real-six-string/</guid>
      <description>Another Year of Books started with an Elin Hilderbrand novel. In fact, it started with three. She’s appeared over and over again ever since. It’s a cycle: Hilderbrand writes a book, I read it, Hilderbrand writes a book, I read it. I blame my sister. If I remember correctly, she started reading Hilderbrand’s books first, then I picked them up. Now, we alternate who buys the newest one. FYI - she bought this one.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Loving You Isn’t the Right Thing to Do</title>
      <link>https://anotheryearofbooks.com/2019/09/loving-you-isnt-the-right-thing-to-do/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 Sep 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://anotheryearofbooks.com/2019/09/loving-you-isnt-the-right-thing-to-do/</guid>
      <description>When I was reading this next read on the bus, the woman who sat down next to me asked how it was. I have been taking the bus for almost three years now, and this is the first time someone has asked me how my book was. Why did she ask? Because this one was also on her list to read. It had good reviews and was supposed to be a good read.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>GO AWAY, ANNA</title>
      <link>https://anotheryearofbooks.com/2019/09/go-away-anna/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 14 Sep 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://anotheryearofbooks.com/2019/09/go-away-anna/</guid>
      <description>I feel very fortunate I have great friends: great friends who always pay me back; great friends I always pay back. Venmo definitely helps. A few weeks ago, when I met my BFF for brunch, she bought us a pastry. I felt so guilty that I owed her two dollars! But alas she didn’t make me pay. Like I said, great friends.
Rachel DeLoache Williams was not as lucky.  Book Read: My Friend Anna: The True Story of a Fake Heiress</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Alexa, Play “One Day More”</title>
      <link>https://anotheryearofbooks.com/2019/09/alexa-play-one-day-more/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Sep 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://anotheryearofbooks.com/2019/09/alexa-play-one-day-more/</guid>
      <description>There were multiple times when reading this book and typing this post when the song from Les Miserables “One Day More” started playing in my head. I can even picture the movie seen when Hugh Jackman is belting out “ONE DAY MOREEEE” when Helena Bohnam Carter and Sasha Baron Cohen jump in with “watch ‘em run amuck.” Maybe even this is a result of buying tickets to see Hugh Jackman in October?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Way Out Yonder, Where the Crawdads Sing</title>
      <link>https://anotheryearofbooks.com/2019/09/way-out-yonder-where-the-crawdads-sing/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 Sep 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://anotheryearofbooks.com/2019/09/way-out-yonder-where-the-crawdads-sing/</guid>
      <description>This next read came as a recommendation from a fellow library-goer and reader, known by her family as GMA. That’s right, this book came recommended by Grandma Donna. She told me to read it, told my aunt (probably both of my aunts), and told my sister to read it. She may have told my mom too - not 100% on that one, but I feel confident. So I listened to her advice, and reserved a copy at the library… after 3 weeks, I was still waiting.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hey, Hey, Hey. Just Walk Away.</title>
      <link>https://anotheryearofbooks.com/2019/08/hey-hey-hey.-just-walk-away./</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 24 Aug 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://anotheryearofbooks.com/2019/08/hey-hey-hey.-just-walk-away./</guid>
      <description>I have a love-hate relationship with Target, as most people do. The one thing I love/hate as much as Target? The Target Cartwheel app, especially when it gives me twenty percent off books. That means a new book, like this week’s read, to add to my ever-growing bookshelf. How can anyone pass that up?  Book Read: How to Walk Away
Author: Katherine Carter
Number of Books Read, 2019 Edition: 31</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Never Drink the Kool Aid (or Smoothie)</title>
      <link>https://anotheryearofbooks.com/2019/05/never-drink-the-kool-aid-or-smoothie/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://anotheryearofbooks.com/2019/05/never-drink-the-kool-aid-or-smoothie/</guid>
      <description>I am eagerly waiting for the second season of Big Little Lies. I loved the show, and the book started me down a path of reading Liane Moriarty’s books. Of course, I had to read her newest novel:
Book Read: Nine Perfect Strangers
Author: Liane Moriarty
Number of Books Read, 2019 Edition: 15
Frances Welty fell victim to an Internet dating scam. Heartbroken and in need of a break, at the advice of a friend, she signs up for a 10 day cleanse at the Tranquillum House.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Do You Remember, the 21st Night of December?</title>
      <link>https://anotheryearofbooks.com/2019/01/do-you-remember-the-21st-night-of-december/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 19 Jan 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://anotheryearofbooks.com/2019/01/do-you-remember-the-21st-night-of-december/</guid>
      <description>I’m 26 years old, and every year, I’m still asked what’s on my Christmas list. The answer is usually pretty standard: money, something I’ve been putting off buying, and books. Becoming was a Christmas gift (thanks, Mom), as was this next read (thanks, Aunt Barb), and the one after this (again, thanks Aunt Barb). My philosophy: there is plenty of room on my bookshelf, so no amount of books is too many.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>They’re Still Rich… and Still Crazy</title>
      <link>https://anotheryearofbooks.com/2018/04/theyre-still-rich-and-still-crazy/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 15 Apr 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://anotheryearofbooks.com/2018/04/theyre-still-rich-and-still-crazy/</guid>
      <description>I know it has been awhile - almost 2 weeks to be exact. But, when I went to the library (not at lunch this time – big change for me!) when I was almost done with my last read, I picked up not 1, but 2 books, and they were meant to be read and talked about together. So here you go – a two for one post.
 Book Read: China Rich Girlfriend &amp;amp; Rich People Problems</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>This Next Book is Insane(ly Good)</title>
      <link>https://anotheryearofbooks.com/2018/02/this-next-book-is-insanely-good/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Feb 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://anotheryearofbooks.com/2018/02/this-next-book-is-insanely-good/</guid>
      <description>My sister is getting married. My best friend’s sister is also getting married. Yesterday when we met for lunch, we were comparing the size of the guest lists. But this book trumped us - the wedding of the century with 888 guests. Eight hundred and eighty eight. Wow, sorry Meghan for commenting on the size of yours.
 Book Read: Crazy Rich Asians
Author: Kevin Kwan
Number of Books Read: 11</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>No One is Going to Save Me... From this Book</title>
      <link>https://anotheryearofbooks.com/2018/01/no-one-is-going-to-save-me...-from-this-book/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 19 Jan 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://anotheryearofbooks.com/2018/01/no-one-is-going-to-save-me...-from-this-book/</guid>
      <description>I tend to find books as I’m wandering the library at lunch. Sometimes, if I can’t find a book on my “to read” list, I pick one based on the cover, the author, or if I saw other people looking at it. Usually, it works out pretty well. This one… I’m still not convinced that picking a book because Powell was in the author’s name was a good idea. You win some, you lose some.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>