<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>2020 Reads on Another Year of Books</title>
    <link>https://anotheryearofbooks.com/categories/2020-reads/</link>
    <description>Recent content in 2020 Reads on Another Year of Books</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 04 Apr 2020 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://anotheryearofbooks.com/categories/2020-reads/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>ENTER TITLE HERE</title>
      <link>https://anotheryearofbooks.com/2020/04/enter-title-here/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 04 Apr 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://anotheryearofbooks.com/2020/04/enter-title-here/</guid>
      <description>&lt;!-- raw HTML omitted --&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This is a test&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>London Calling</title>
      <link>https://anotheryearofbooks.com/2020/04/london-calling/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Apr 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://anotheryearofbooks.com/2020/04/london-calling/</guid>
      <description>I won’t lie. I skipped the third book in this series. Whoops. I honestly didn’t mean to, but when I realized I did, I decided to push on and not turn back. Now, I’m not going to, but just a forewarning that this is book number four in the series, not three. If you are looking for three, The Wedding Party is the name.
 Book Read: Royal Holiday
Author: Jasmine Guillory</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Not Even Close, Not Even a Little Bit, Not Even at All</title>
      <link>https://anotheryearofbooks.com/2020/03/not-even-close-not-even-a-little-bit-not-even-at-all/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 30 Mar 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://anotheryearofbooks.com/2020/03/not-even-close-not-even-a-little-bit-not-even-at-all/</guid>
      <description>&lt;!-- raw HTML omitted --&gt;
&lt;p&gt;At this point, while staying in as much as possible since last weekend, I finished reading one book (Harry Potter and the Chamber of Secrets), downloaded a workout app (and used it), watched over two seasons of The Office, survived five days of working from home, and cleaned our stove. I figured after all of that, it was time to write another blog. Which brings us here.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Thank You for Being a Friend</title>
      <link>https://anotheryearofbooks.com/2020/03/thank-you-for-being-a-friend/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 15 Mar 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://anotheryearofbooks.com/2020/03/thank-you-for-being-a-friend/</guid>
      <description>Let’s admit it. We all know we are living in a weird time. I mean, no March Madness?! What will I do without it? Not lose in the family bracket, that&amp;rsquo;s what I&amp;rsquo;ll do.
I do see a bright side… there is always another book to read. What better way to pass the time? Yes, I know there’s such things as Netflix and Disney+, but to me, there is still nothing better than a great read.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>To the Window, to the Wall!</title>
      <link>https://anotheryearofbooks.com/2020/03/to-the-window-to-the-wall/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 07 Mar 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://anotheryearofbooks.com/2020/03/to-the-window-to-the-wall/</guid>
      <description>After I read something more challenging, like the last read, I always want my next book to be easy and light-hearted. Usually, I stick to the authors I know. That’s exactly how I picked this next book. Book Read: The Proposal 
Author: Jasmine Guillory
2020 Book Count: 6
Nikole Paterson’s boyfriend of five months just proposed on the Jumbotron at a baseball game, with no warning. Nik says no. It doesn’t go over well, at all.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Life Is Like a Cactus</title>
      <link>https://anotheryearofbooks.com/2020/02/life-is-like-a-cactus/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 29 Feb 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://anotheryearofbooks.com/2020/02/life-is-like-a-cactus/</guid>
      <description>This was the first e-book I borrowed from the library. I haven’t tried it before, because I always just went to the library. But at some point soon, the library I go to is closing for renovations. I wanted to make sure I had a back up plan, besides ordering ahead and picking it up.
Except when my eyes were tired, it definitely is a great alternative. Book Read: The Cactus</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>I&#39;m The Wife</title>
      <link>https://anotheryearofbooks.com/2020/02/im-the-wife/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Feb 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://anotheryearofbooks.com/2020/02/im-the-wife/</guid>
      <description>I am trying to clean out my bookshelf by reading the books I haven’t yet read. Mostly, I’m doing this so I can give some back to the library before I buy more later this year. It’s important to have priorities, right? This next read is one of those books - I purchased it at the library’s book sale last summer. I needed to decide if it would stay or go back to the library.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Now You’re Just Somebody</title>
      <link>https://anotheryearofbooks.com/2020/02/now-youre-just-somebody/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 12 Feb 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://anotheryearofbooks.com/2020/02/now-youre-just-somebody/</guid>
      <description>Since I started writing/editing this post, I have been singing Goyte’s hit… “Now you’re just somebody that I used to know… SOMEBODY (I used to know).” I’m not sure if that’s exactly how the lyrics go, but in my head, it makes perfect sense. This would be why I write blogs and not song lyrics. Stick to what you think you are good at, right?
Book Read: The Girl He Used to Know</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A Drop of Golden Sun</title>
      <link>https://anotheryearofbooks.com/2020/02/a-drop-of-golden-sun/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 06 Feb 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://anotheryearofbooks.com/2020/02/a-drop-of-golden-sun/</guid>
      <description>The Sound of Music is one of my all time favorite movies, hands down. I always have loved it. My family will tell you they can’t count how many times they had to rewind the two VHS’s so I could watch it again. Even now, I have watched it on Disney+ at least five times (they even have the intermission!). I can’t help it. I want to climb every mountain! So, of course I wanted to read Julie Andrews’ latest memoir.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Guess Who&#39;s Back...</title>
      <link>https://anotheryearofbooks.com/2020/01/guess-whos-back.../</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 Jan 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://anotheryearofbooks.com/2020/01/guess-whos-back.../</guid>
      <description>It’s Another Year of Books! I seem to have a trend when it comes to my first book of the year (or within the first 3). I always seem to start with an autobiography or memoir. In 2018, Anna Faris’s Unqualified was number 3; in 2019, Michelle Obama’s Becoming was the first read.
2020 is no different.
Book Read: Me
Author: Elton John
2020 Book Count: 1
We all know Elton John.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>