<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Blog on Another Year of Books</title>
    <link>https://anotheryearofbooks.com/blog/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Blog on Another Year of Books</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 05 Aug 2020 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://anotheryearofbooks.com/blog/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>WE&#39;RE BACK IN 3, 2, 1...</title>
      <link>https://anotheryearofbooks.com/2020/08/were-back-in-3-2-1.../</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 05 Aug 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://anotheryearofbooks.com/2020/08/were-back-in-3-2-1.../</guid>
      <description>&lt;!-- raw HTML omitted --&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Welcome back to Another Year of Books! It’s been over a month since my last post about a recently read book. I’ve taken the past month to just relax, whether it was by re-reading some books I previously read, or by reading some corny romance novels I stumbled upon. Long story short, I didn’t have much to write home about. But I’m back! Don’t worry, more reads are coming soon.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>AN UPDATE</title>
      <link>https://anotheryearofbooks.com/2020/07/an-update/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 Jul 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://anotheryearofbooks.com/2020/07/an-update/</guid>
      <description>&lt;!-- raw HTML omitted --&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Greetings, readers of Another Year of Books!&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>HEY NOW, HEY NOW</title>
      <link>https://anotheryearofbooks.com/2020/06/hey-now-hey-now/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 25 Jun 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://anotheryearofbooks.com/2020/06/hey-now-hey-now/</guid>
      <description>&lt;!-- raw HTML omitted --&gt;
&lt;p&gt;… this is what dreams are made of! Apologies if that song is now stuck in your head.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Usually, I try to come up with a tidbit to include at the beginning of a post, before I go into the book and my thoughts on it. Today, I am struggling to come up with anything to say, so I’ll just jump right into it!&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>WHERE DO YOU SEE YOURSELF?</title>
      <link>https://anotheryearofbooks.com/2020/06/where-do-you-see-yourself/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Jun 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://anotheryearofbooks.com/2020/06/where-do-you-see-yourself/</guid>
      <description>&lt;!-- raw HTML omitted --&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Where do you see yourself?” is my least favorite question. I never know how to answer because it seems like a trick question. It could lead to great things, but it could lead to weird ones. Plus, life changes so constantly, how can you predict what life will be like in five years?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;That is why when asked, I don’t give an answer, or I give the broadest answer possible (i.e.: “Well, I would like to have a job.”). It’s better that way.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>&#39;OUR STORY BEGINS...&#39;</title>
      <link>https://anotheryearofbooks.com/2020/06/our-story-begins.../</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Jun 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://anotheryearofbooks.com/2020/06/our-story-begins.../</guid>
      <description>&lt;!-- raw HTML omitted --&gt;
&lt;p&gt;It’s hard to believe that it’s pretty much summer. Even though Memorial Day is the “unofficial” start to summer, the temperatures would make me think it’s summer anyway. I’ve had to start wearing sunscreen on longer walks. But the best part of summertime? Being able to stay in the AC and read a good book. I’ve already started participating.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>LOVE IT IF WE MADE IT</title>
      <link>https://anotheryearofbooks.com/2020/05/love-it-if-we-made-it/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 May 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://anotheryearofbooks.com/2020/05/love-it-if-we-made-it/</guid>
      <description>&lt;!-- raw HTML omitted --&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I do my best to remember when a sequel I want to read is coming out. Some authors make it easy, like Elin Hilderbrand. For the past three years, I could count on her to put out a new book in her Winter in Paradise series in the fall. When I stumble upon a sequel I forgot about, it’s always a nice thrill. This next book is a sequel that I completely forgot about until I was browsing Amazon one day and found it.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>BOW DOWN</title>
      <link>https://anotheryearofbooks.com/2020/05/bow-down/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 May 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://anotheryearofbooks.com/2020/05/bow-down/</guid>
      <description>&lt;!-- raw HTML omitted --&gt;
&lt;p&gt;It seems like the weather is finally turning here in Pittsburgh. Although, I can’t be too sure, as it snowed last week and now it’s 80 degrees. I&amp;rsquo;m hoping Mother Nature throws us a bone and it stays this way. It&amp;rsquo;s been nice to sit outside and read, or even walk and read if I can read the book on my phone and it looks safe.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>REWRITE THE STARS</title>
      <link>https://anotheryearofbooks.com/2020/05/rewrite-the-stars/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 08 May 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://anotheryearofbooks.com/2020/05/rewrite-the-stars/</guid>
      <description>&lt;!-- raw HTML omitted --&gt;
&lt;p&gt;It’s been a while since my last post. Don&amp;rsquo;t think I haven’t been reading - I’ve knocked out a few more books since the last post; I just decided not to write about them. While I’ve been gone, here is what I’ve read and a quick “should you read this?&amp;rdquo; answer.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;em&gt;Red, White &amp;amp; Royal Blue&lt;/em&gt; by Casey McQuiston
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;What would happen if the First Son of the USA and the Prince of England hooked up? I finished this one in two days if that tells you if I liked it or not. Warning, it is a little risque.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;em&gt;Harry Potter and the Prisoner of Azkaban&lt;/em&gt; by JK Rowling
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Do you even have to ask if you should read this one?&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;em&gt;The Wedding Party&lt;/em&gt; by Jasmine Guillory
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;I went back and read the third book of &lt;a href=&#34;https://anotheryearofbooks.com/2020/04/london-calling/&#34;&gt;this&lt;/a&gt; series. It was as I predicted; skip this one.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Read on to learn more about my latest read.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Yas, Queen</title>
      <link>https://anotheryearofbooks.com/2020/04/yas-queen/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 19 Apr 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://anotheryearofbooks.com/2020/04/yas-queen/</guid>
      <description>&lt;!-- raw HTML omitted --&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If you haven’t watched &lt;em&gt;Queer Eye: More than a Makeover&lt;/em&gt; on Netflix, I recommend you do so immediately. There are already four seasons, so it’ll occupy some of your time. I&amp;rsquo;m guessing you probably have some time on your hands right now. Each time a new season comes out, we watch the whole season within two weeks (we try to pace ourselves so we can enjoy it more).&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Why am I suggesting this at the beginning of my post? Well, the author of this next read is one of the stars.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>YOU HAVE HOPE AS EACH NEW DAY DAWNS</title>
      <link>https://anotheryearofbooks.com/2020/04/you-have-hope-as-each-new-day-dawns/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 Apr 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://anotheryearofbooks.com/2020/04/you-have-hope-as-each-new-day-dawns/</guid>
      <description>&lt;!-- raw HTML omitted --&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Back before we all stayed home, I visited my aunt and grandparents to play cards. It’s one of our favorite things to do. Books came up as part of the conversation, as they usually do. My aunt told me I needed to read this book next. She even brought her copy to lend to me. Turns out, I already bought it on my latest trip to Half Price Books. After I finished Harry Potter and the Chamber of Secrets, I bumped this one up to next on my list.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>London Calling</title>
      <link>https://anotheryearofbooks.com/2020/04/london-calling/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Apr 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://anotheryearofbooks.com/2020/04/london-calling/</guid>
      <description>I won’t lie. I skipped the third book in this series. Whoops. I honestly didn’t mean to, but when I realized I did, I decided to push on and not turn back. Now, I’m not going to, but just a forewarning that this is book number four in the series, not three. If you are looking for three, The Wedding Party is the name.
 Book Read: Royal Holiday
Author: Jasmine Guillory</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Not Even Close, Not Even a Little Bit, Not Even at All</title>
      <link>https://anotheryearofbooks.com/2020/03/not-even-close-not-even-a-little-bit-not-even-at-all/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 30 Mar 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://anotheryearofbooks.com/2020/03/not-even-close-not-even-a-little-bit-not-even-at-all/</guid>
      <description>&lt;!-- raw HTML omitted --&gt;
&lt;p&gt;At this point, while staying in as much as possible since last weekend, I finished reading one book (Harry Potter and the Chamber of Secrets), downloaded a workout app (and used it), watched over two seasons of The Office, survived five days of working from home, and cleaned our stove. I figured after all of that, it was time to write another blog. Which brings us here.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Thank You for Being a Friend</title>
      <link>https://anotheryearofbooks.com/2020/03/thank-you-for-being-a-friend/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 15 Mar 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://anotheryearofbooks.com/2020/03/thank-you-for-being-a-friend/</guid>
      <description>Let’s admit it. We all know we are living in a weird time. I mean, no March Madness?! What will I do without it? Not lose in the family bracket, that&amp;rsquo;s what I&amp;rsquo;ll do.
I do see a bright side… there is always another book to read. What better way to pass the time? Yes, I know there’s such things as Netflix and Disney+, but to me, there is still nothing better than a great read.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>To the Window, to the Wall!</title>
      <link>https://anotheryearofbooks.com/2020/03/to-the-window-to-the-wall/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 07 Mar 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://anotheryearofbooks.com/2020/03/to-the-window-to-the-wall/</guid>
      <description>After I read something more challenging, like the last read, I always want my next book to be easy and light-hearted. Usually, I stick to the authors I know. That’s exactly how I picked this next book. Book Read: The Proposal 
Author: Jasmine Guillory
2020 Book Count: 6
Nikole Paterson’s boyfriend of five months just proposed on the Jumbotron at a baseball game, with no warning. Nik says no. It doesn’t go over well, at all.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Life Is Like a Cactus</title>
      <link>https://anotheryearofbooks.com/2020/02/life-is-like-a-cactus/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 29 Feb 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://anotheryearofbooks.com/2020/02/life-is-like-a-cactus/</guid>
      <description>This was the first e-book I borrowed from the library. I haven’t tried it before, because I always just went to the library. But at some point soon, the library I go to is closing for renovations. I wanted to make sure I had a back up plan, besides ordering ahead and picking it up.
Except when my eyes were tired, it definitely is a great alternative. Book Read: The Cactus</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>I&#39;m The Wife</title>
      <link>https://anotheryearofbooks.com/2020/02/im-the-wife/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Feb 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://anotheryearofbooks.com/2020/02/im-the-wife/</guid>
      <description>I am trying to clean out my bookshelf by reading the books I haven’t yet read. Mostly, I’m doing this so I can give some back to the library before I buy more later this year. It’s important to have priorities, right? This next read is one of those books - I purchased it at the library’s book sale last summer. I needed to decide if it would stay or go back to the library.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Now You’re Just Somebody</title>
      <link>https://anotheryearofbooks.com/2020/02/now-youre-just-somebody/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 12 Feb 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://anotheryearofbooks.com/2020/02/now-youre-just-somebody/</guid>
      <description>Since I started writing/editing this post, I have been singing Goyte’s hit… “Now you’re just somebody that I used to know… SOMEBODY (I used to know).” I’m not sure if that’s exactly how the lyrics go, but in my head, it makes perfect sense. This would be why I write blogs and not song lyrics. Stick to what you think you are good at, right?
Book Read: The Girl He Used to Know</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A Drop of Golden Sun</title>
      <link>https://anotheryearofbooks.com/2020/02/a-drop-of-golden-sun/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 06 Feb 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://anotheryearofbooks.com/2020/02/a-drop-of-golden-sun/</guid>
      <description>The Sound of Music is one of my all time favorite movies, hands down. I always have loved it. My family will tell you they can’t count how many times they had to rewind the two VHS’s so I could watch it again. Even now, I have watched it on Disney+ at least five times (they even have the intermission!). I can’t help it. I want to climb every mountain! So, of course I wanted to read Julie Andrews’ latest memoir.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Guess Who&#39;s Back...</title>
      <link>https://anotheryearofbooks.com/2020/01/guess-whos-back.../</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 Jan 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://anotheryearofbooks.com/2020/01/guess-whos-back.../</guid>
      <description>It’s Another Year of Books! I seem to have a trend when it comes to my first book of the year (or within the first 3). I always seem to start with an autobiography or memoir. In 2018, Anna Faris’s Unqualified was number 3; in 2019, Michelle Obama’s Becoming was the first read.
2020 is no different.
Book Read: Me
Author: Elton John
2020 Book Count: 1
We all know Elton John.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Another Year of Books: The 2019 Recap</title>
      <link>https://anotheryearofbooks.com/2020/01/another-year-of-books-the-2019-recap/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 Jan 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://anotheryearofbooks.com/2020/01/another-year-of-books-the-2019-recap/</guid>
      <description>Another year has already come and gone. I can’t believe it. I still can’t believe that I read all 52 books in 2019. I was filled with doubt and, mostly, annoyance at myself. But then, after I finished, all I felt was pride, and a little tired. This one is always the hardest… the recap. Which books were the best? Which were the worst? Which books are waiting for Hallmark to pick them up?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Number 52</title>
      <link>https://anotheryearofbooks.com/2020/01/number-52/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Jan 2020 05:00:00 -0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://anotheryearofbooks.com/2020/01/number-52/</guid>
      <description>On December 31, 2019, at 12:04 PM, I sent my sister this text:

It was the last day of the year. Since December 25, I had read three books (and wrote 0 posts). On Christmas Eve, when asked if I was going to read all 52, I said no. I didn’t anticipate reading three books in 6 days. It helped that Matt has been sick and we didn’t leave the house much, and that the three books kept my attention.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Double Dutch</title>
      <link>https://anotheryearofbooks.com/2020/01/double-dutch/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 Jan 2020 18:26:00 -0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://anotheryearofbooks.com/2020/01/double-dutch/</guid>
      <description>I actually started reading this book before I picked up The Christmas Star. I was only 10 pages or so into this one when I set it back down. Then when I picked it back up again, I started over. It only seemed right. I don’t often start a book and stop for another, but decided that Christmas was an acceptable night to do so. Book Read: Going Dutch
Author: James Gregor</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>So This is Christmas</title>
      <link>https://anotheryearofbooks.com/2019/12/so-this-is-christmas/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 31 Dec 2019 10:10:00 -0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://anotheryearofbooks.com/2019/12/so-this-is-christmas/</guid>
      <description>On Christmas night, I put on How the Grinch Stole Christmas (first the animated version, which was then followed by the Jim Carrey version) and settled in with a comfy blanket. I was in the mood for a Christmas themed book. Luckily, I had one on my shelf. I mean, truthfully, I only have one. This was my only option. I picked it up, and by the time I went to bed, I was half way finished.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>This Could Be the Start of Something New</title>
      <link>https://anotheryearofbooks.com/2019/12/this-could-be-the-start-of-something-new/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 28 Dec 2019 17:49:00 -0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://anotheryearofbooks.com/2019/12/this-could-be-the-start-of-something-new/</guid>
      <description>Every Friday, theSkimm recommends a book. I look forward to it every week. I reckon all but one a month make it onto my “to read” list. This Friday, I beat t_heSkimm_! What a day. Last week at the library, I picked up yesterday&amp;rsquo;s recommendation. I am impressed with myself to say the least.
Book Read: Evvie Drake Starts Over
Author: Linda Holmes
Number of Books Read, 2019 Edition: 49</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Trouble, Trouble, Trouble </title>
      <link>https://anotheryearofbooks.com/2019/12/trouble-trouble-trouble/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Dec 2019 18:22:00 -0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://anotheryearofbooks.com/2019/12/trouble-trouble-trouble/</guid>
      <description>It’s hard to find time to read during all the holiday hooplah. There’s the cooking, the baking, the wrapping, the cleaning, the Christmas movies, the family time. Although a book is a good excuse to avoid family time. Just saying. (I did not do this, also just saying.)
Book Read: Fleishman is In Trouble
Author: Taffy Brodesser-Akner
Number of Books Read, 2019 Edition: 48
Toby Fleishman became a ladies’ man after his wife finally agreed to his requested divorce.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Circle, Circle, Dot, Dot</title>
      <link>https://anotheryearofbooks.com/2019/12/circle-circle-dot-dot/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Dec 2019 18:48:00 -0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://anotheryearofbooks.com/2019/12/circle-circle-dot-dot/</guid>
      <description>The last read was a heavy topic. I enjoyed it (find out here), but afterwards, I wanted my next read to be more mindless and quick. I found it at my trip to the library at lunchtime last week (I know, a book found at a library - shocking!)
Book Read: The Friend Zone Author: Abby Jimenez
Number of Books Read, 2019 Edition: 47
Kristen Peterson’s best friend is getting married.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>When I Grow Up</title>
      <link>https://anotheryearofbooks.com/2019/12/when-i-grow-up/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 15 Dec 2019 10:12:00 -0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://anotheryearofbooks.com/2019/12/when-i-grow-up/</guid>
      <description>In the first grade, our teacher asked us what we wanted to be when we grew up. I remember I wanted to be a teacher. We made paper dolls showing what we wanted to be - I can still picture what mine looked like (she was wearing a pink shirt). I also remember multiple girls in my class wanting to be models. But I’m pretty sure one girl copied the other, so who knows!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Paradise by the Dashboard Light</title>
      <link>https://anotheryearofbooks.com/2019/12/paradise-by-the-dashboard-light/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 08 Dec 2019 14:17:00 -0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://anotheryearofbooks.com/2019/12/paradise-by-the-dashboard-light/</guid>
      <description>Sequels can be tough to write about. I don’t want to give away too much. That way you want to read this book, but you also want to read the first in the series. It is a line easily crossed. If I say too much for the second book, do I give away the ending of the first?
Gosh, I hope not. Book Read: What Happens in Paradise
Author: Elin Hilderbrand</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Let&#39;s Feast!</title>
      <link>https://anotheryearofbooks.com/2019/11/lets-feast/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Nov 2019 07:44:00 -0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://anotheryearofbooks.com/2019/11/lets-feast/</guid>
      <description>I hope at this point, everyone has watched Always Be My Maybe on Netflix, or maybe the comedy specials Baby Cobra or Hard Knock Wife. Because Ali Wong is hysterical; completely hysterical. My friends and I are obsessed. I’ve watched Always Be My Maybe I don’t even know how many times. I mean, it has Keanu Reeves! It’s a laugh-out-loud romantic comedy, that is more comedy than most.
When I saw that Ali Wong wrote a book, I knew I had to read it, leading to read number 44.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Faster, Denny, Faster</title>
      <link>https://anotheryearofbooks.com/2019/11/faster-denny-faster/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 23 Nov 2019 14:43:00 -0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://anotheryearofbooks.com/2019/11/faster-denny-faster/</guid>
      <description>This next read came as a recommendation from a friend. Yes, I know it’s a movie too, so eventually I would have gotten to it. But a recommendation usually bumps up the book on the &amp;ldquo;to read&amp;rdquo; list. Really, if this book wasn’t as good as I expected, who knows what would have happened - awkwardness, bitterness, loss of a friend. Just kidding of course. I will never hold a book recommendation grudge… unless it is really, really bad.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>And My Flippy Floppies</title>
      <link>https://anotheryearofbooks.com/2019/11/and-my-flippy-floppies/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 17 Nov 2019 15:30:00 -0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://anotheryearofbooks.com/2019/11/and-my-flippy-floppies/</guid>
      <description>In the first weekend of November, my mom, aunt and I ventured to New York City to visit my sister and brother-in-law. We planned ahead for 2 main events - to see Waitress on Broadway, since it is in its final run, and to go to Strand Book Store. Strand is a magical place that has EIGHTEEN miles of books. You read that right - eighteen miles. Us visitors came prepared with room in our suitcases.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Everything is Fine</title>
      <link>https://anotheryearofbooks.com/2019/11/everything-is-fine/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 07 Nov 2019 19:16:00 -0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://anotheryearofbooks.com/2019/11/everything-is-fine/</guid>
      <description>I’m writing this while it is 34 degrees outside. Thirty four! Did I blink and miss fall? It really feels like I did. It’s a good thing there are so many books that go well with a cozy blanket. It’s also a good thing that I bought four new books on a trip to visit my sister and brother-in-law in New York City (shout out to the Strand!).
Book Read: Mrs.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Cause I’m Burnin’ Up</title>
      <link>https://anotheryearofbooks.com/2019/10/cause-im-burnin-up/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 Oct 2019 18:43:00 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://anotheryearofbooks.com/2019/10/cause-im-burnin-up/</guid>
      <description>When I was writing this, I could not get Burnin’ Up by the Jonas Brothers out of my head. Why? Because it is a catchy song. Also, because I love the Jonas Brothers; meaning I LOVE the Jonas Brothers. My aunt and I had a fabulous time at their concert in September. “I’m hot. You’re cold…” Book Read: Things You Save in a Fire
Author: Katherine Carter
Number of Books Read, 2019 Edition: 40</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ok, Ladies…</title>
      <link>https://anotheryearofbooks.com/2019/10/ok-ladies/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Oct 2019 18:35:00 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://anotheryearofbooks.com/2019/10/ok-ladies/</guid>
      <description>Let us get in formation.
I struggle with non-fiction. I’m sure I’ve mentioned this each time I talk about non-fiction, but it’s true. This book took me awhile to read. Not because it was a bad book, but because I feel like I have to really pay attention to what I’m reading.
This is a book that requires your attention, for good reasons. And I’m not just talking to the ladies.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Decisions, Decisions, Decisions</title>
      <link>https://anotheryearofbooks.com/2019/10/decisions-decisions-decisions/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 11 Oct 2019 04:32:00 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://anotheryearofbooks.com/2019/10/decisions-decisions-decisions/</guid>
      <description>I look forward to Friday’s. Not just because TGIF, but because every Friday, the Skimm has a book recommendation. I’d say 95% of the time, I end up adding the book to my “to read” list; then, I wait. I wait until the book is finally available at the library. Usually it takes weeks, at the minimum.
Somehow, when I went to return An American Marriage to the library, I found this next read.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Now, Do You Love Me?</title>
      <link>https://anotheryearofbooks.com/2019/10/now-do-you-love-me/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 06 Oct 2019 10:47:00 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://anotheryearofbooks.com/2019/10/now-do-you-love-me/</guid>
      <description>It seems like October crashed into me. I looked up and BAM&amp;hellip; October. I feel like I should have seen it coming considering Giant Eagle had Halloween candy out before school started. This is entirely too soon, by the way. Don’t even get me started on the Christmas decorations that are already out in stores.
Finishing this book means I have 15 more to read to make it to 52 books read in 2019.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>I Got My First Real Six-String</title>
      <link>https://anotheryearofbooks.com/2019/10/i-got-my-first-real-six-string/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Oct 2019 18:21:00 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://anotheryearofbooks.com/2019/10/i-got-my-first-real-six-string/</guid>
      <description>Another Year of Books started with an Elin Hilderbrand novel. In fact, it started with three. She’s appeared over and over again ever since. It’s a cycle: Hilderbrand writes a book, I read it, Hilderbrand writes a book, I read it. I blame my sister. If I remember correctly, she started reading Hilderbrand’s books first, then I picked them up. Now, we alternate who buys the newest one. FYI - she bought this one.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Loving You Isn’t the Right Thing to Do</title>
      <link>https://anotheryearofbooks.com/2019/09/loving-you-isnt-the-right-thing-to-do/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 Sep 2019 17:31:00 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://anotheryearofbooks.com/2019/09/loving-you-isnt-the-right-thing-to-do/</guid>
      <description>When I was reading this next read on the bus, the woman who sat down next to me asked how it was. I have been taking the bus for almost three years now, and this is the first time someone has asked me how my book was. Why did she ask? Because this one was also on her list to read. It had good reviews and was supposed to be a good read.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Go Away, Anna</title>
      <link>https://anotheryearofbooks.com/2019/09/go-away-anna/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 14 Sep 2019 16:11:00 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://anotheryearofbooks.com/2019/09/go-away-anna/</guid>
      <description>I feel very fortunate I have great friends: great friends who always pay me back; great friends I always pay back. Venmo definitely helps. A few weeks ago, when I met my BFF for brunch, she bought us a pastry. I felt so guilty that I owed her two dollars! But alas she didn’t make me pay. Like I said, great friends.
Rachel DeLoache Williams was not as lucky. Book Read: My Friend Anna: The True Story of a Fake Heiress</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Alexa, Play “One Day More”</title>
      <link>https://anotheryearofbooks.com/2019/09/alexa-play-one-day-more/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Sep 2019 04:19:00 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://anotheryearofbooks.com/2019/09/alexa-play-one-day-more/</guid>
      <description>There were multiple times when reading this book and typing this post when the song from Les Miserables “One Day More” started playing in my head. I can even picture the movie seen when Hugh Jackman is belting out “ONE DAY MOREEEE” when Helena Bohnam Carter and Sasha Baron Cohen jump in with “watch ‘em run amuck.” Maybe even this is a result of buying tickets to see Hugh Jackman in October?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Way Out Yonder, Where the Crawdads Sing </title>
      <link>https://anotheryearofbooks.com/2019/09/way-out-yonder-where-the-crawdads-sing/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 Sep 2019 17:22:00 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://anotheryearofbooks.com/2019/09/way-out-yonder-where-the-crawdads-sing/</guid>
      <description>This next read came as a recommendation from a fellow library-goer and reader, known by her family as GMA. That’s right, this book came recommended by Grandma Donna. She told me to read it, told my aunt (probably both of my aunts), and told my sister to read it. She may have told my mom too - not 100% on that one, but I feel confident. So I listened to her advice, and reserved a copy at the library… after 3 weeks, I was still waiting.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hey, Hey, Hey. Just Walk Away.</title>
      <link>https://anotheryearofbooks.com/2019/08/hey-hey-hey.-just-walk-away./</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 24 Aug 2019 14:52:00 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://anotheryearofbooks.com/2019/08/hey-hey-hey.-just-walk-away./</guid>
      <description>I have a love-hate relationship with Target, as most people do. The one thing I love/hate as much as Target? The Target Cartwheel app, especially when it gives me twenty percent off books. That means a new book, like this week’s read, to add to my ever-growing bookshelf. How can anyone pass that up? Book Read: How to Walk Away
Author: Katherine Carter
Number of Books Read, 2019 Edition: 31</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Make Some LuluLemonade (Bag Not Included)</title>
      <link>https://anotheryearofbooks.com/2019/08/make-some-lululemonade-bag-not-included/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Aug 2019 05:18:00 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://anotheryearofbooks.com/2019/08/make-some-lululemonade-bag-not-included/</guid>
      <description>When I was reading Revenge Wears Prada, I had a strange feeling that I had read it before. At least I had started it, and maybe read the ending? I still am not 100% sure, but if I did read it before, the last two reads were the only time during Another Year of Books that I reread a book. 82 books in, and that’s a pretty good statistic. I know, with 100% confidence, that I have not read this next read.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>I Beat Meryl</title>
      <link>https://anotheryearofbooks.com/2019/08/i-beat-meryl/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 Aug 2019 18:32:00 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://anotheryearofbooks.com/2019/08/i-beat-meryl/</guid>
      <description>I found the third book in this series at the Beaver Library book sale. You can&amp;rsquo;t just start with book three and not read the first two, am I right? So back to the start I went, all leading to BOGO day here at Another Year of Books.
Book Read: The Devil Wears Prada
Author: Lauren Weisberger Number of Books Read, 2019 Edition: 28
Andy Sachs lands the job “a million girls would die for,” when she becomes Miranda Priestly’s junior assistant at Runway.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kissing in a Tree, K-I-S-S-I-N-G</title>
      <link>https://anotheryearofbooks.com/2019/07/kissing-in-a-tree-k-i-s-s-i-n-g/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 29 Jul 2019 17:53:00 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://anotheryearofbooks.com/2019/07/kissing-in-a-tree-k-i-s-s-i-n-g/</guid>
      <description>I learned how to make macarons on Saturday. It was a magical experience. The class was three hours long and well worth every minute. We have already ate half of one box. By the end of the afternoon following, I almost fell asleep reading a book. Not a bad way to spend a Saturday, right?
Book Read: The Kiss Quotient
Author: Helen Hoang
Number of Books Read, 2019 Edition: 27</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Halfway Point</title>
      <link>https://anotheryearofbooks.com/2019/07/the-halfway-point/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 25 Jul 2019 17:14:00 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://anotheryearofbooks.com/2019/07/the-halfway-point/</guid>
      <description>It’s official. Twenty six books down, twenty six books to go. But only twenty three weeks left in the year (if I counted correctly). I better get moving on the next twenty six. The next option may be to read when my boyfriend drives me too work, but he drives pretty quickly. I should probably stick to reading when I get home. Book Read: The Unlikely Adventures of the Shergill Sisters</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A Reserved, Family Cloud</title>
      <link>https://anotheryearofbooks.com/2019/07/a-reserved-family-cloud/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 15 Jul 2019 18:30:00 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://anotheryearofbooks.com/2019/07/a-reserved-family-cloud/</guid>
      <description>The hardest part of writing Another Year of Books is this intro paragraph. Sometimes, I have a hundred things to say. Other days, like today, I can’t think of even one. I’ve complained about the weather plenty of times, I’ve mentioned my love of walking to the library at lunch, and besides some family visits and yard work, my week has been pretty ordinary. So, I’ll just get right to the point:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>One Glass of Drama, Please</title>
      <link>https://anotheryearofbooks.com/2019/07/one-glass-of-drama-please/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Jul 2019 17:48:00 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://anotheryearofbooks.com/2019/07/one-glass-of-drama-please/</guid>
      <description>The week after a holiday, aka a day off, seems to either fly by or drag along. I can’t decide what this week is doing. One day fast, the next day slow. Maybe it’s the heat (I know, I’m still complaining about the heat), or it’s that it just feels like we should all be on a beach. If you are one of the lucky few, don’t forget your hat, sunscreen and a good book.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Six Feet Under the Stars (All Time Low)</title>
      <link>https://anotheryearofbooks.com/2019/07/six-feet-under-the-stars-all-time-low/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 07 Jul 2019 07:24:00 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://anotheryearofbooks.com/2019/07/six-feet-under-the-stars-all-time-low/</guid>
      <description>It is hot outside. Unbearably hot, which means I usually get slightly sun burnt on any walks/runs, and come back to work sweating from my lunchtime walk. It’s super fun, let me tell you. But when it’s this hot, there’s no better time to stay cool in the AC with a good book and an ice cold drink.
Book Read: This Will Only Hurt a Little
Author: Busy Philipps Number of Books Read, 2019 Edition: 23</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>I Can Still Recall Our Last Summer</title>
      <link>https://anotheryearofbooks.com/2019/06/i-can-still-recall-our-last-summer/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Jun 2019 17:44:00 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://anotheryearofbooks.com/2019/06/i-can-still-recall-our-last-summer/</guid>
      <description>Every year, ‍I look forward to the Beaver Area Library book sale. Over the years, I have found some gems. Since I moved, for the past two book sales, I drive to Beaver so my mom and I can walk to the book sale. This year was a successful year. Just ask my mom, she went back and got even more books. Book Read: Invincible Summer
Author: Alice Adams
Number of Books Read, 2019 Edition: 22</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>&#34;I Call It an Education&#34;</title>
      <link>https://anotheryearofbooks.com/2019/06/i-call-it-an-education/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Jun 2019 17:58:00 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://anotheryearofbooks.com/2019/06/i-call-it-an-education/</guid>
      <description>I just celebrated my five-year anniversary at work. That means I get to attend the fancy lunch in the fall (finally), but it also means I, along with the rest of the Class of 2014, graduated college 5 years ago. Time flies - especially when you have 52 books a year to read.
Book Read: Educated
Author: Tara Westover
Number of Books Read, 2019 Edition: 21
Tara Westover was raised by survivalists in Idaho.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>I Get By With a Little Help From My Friends</title>
      <link>https://anotheryearofbooks.com/2019/06/i-get-by-with-a-little-help-from-my-friends/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Jun 2019 18:28:00 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://anotheryearofbooks.com/2019/06/i-get-by-with-a-little-help-from-my-friends/</guid>
      <description>I have been putting off writing this post because I’ve been feeling discouraged when it came to AYOB. While I’m slowly marching towards 52 books, I feel behind. Then I had myself convinced that despite knowing people read this, no one was actually reading. I mean, even my best friend openly admits she doesn’t read it.
Then, I went to visit my aunt and grandparents this past weekend. My aunt was telling her friends about my blog and then commented that other friends read every post and take the recommendations.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mind the Gap</title>
      <link>https://anotheryearofbooks.com/2019/05/mind-the-gap/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 May 2019 13:50:00 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://anotheryearofbooks.com/2019/05/mind-the-gap/</guid>
      <description>AYOB has been MIA as my boyfriend, Matt, and I traveled to London and Paris for a vacation. While away, we took in historical sights, watched the Eiffel Tower&amp;rsquo;s 130th Anniversary light show, walked 124 total miles, and ate a lot of pastries. I mean a lot of pastries. Along the way, we found a bookshop in each city, each with its own uniqueness and fame (I might have picked up a book or two).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>In the Words of Aerosmith, Dream On</title>
      <link>https://anotheryearofbooks.com/2019/05/in-the-words-of-aerosmith-dream-on/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 May 2019 05:42:00 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://anotheryearofbooks.com/2019/05/in-the-words-of-aerosmith-dream-on/</guid>
      <description>The only medical show I have watched (and thoroughly enjoyed) was House. It wasn’t too gruesome, and it had a way of looking deeper. The synopsis of this book reminded me of it. How House would weave into the patient’s mind or body to show you something. This book sounded like it would do the same.
Book Read: The Book of Dreams
Author: Nina George
Number of Books Read, 2019 Edition: 16</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Never Drink the Kool Aid (or Smoothie)</title>
      <link>https://anotheryearofbooks.com/2019/05/never-drink-the-kool-aid-or-smoothie/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://anotheryearofbooks.com/2019/05/never-drink-the-kool-aid-or-smoothie/</guid>
      <description>I am eagerly waiting for the second season of Big Little Lies. I loved the show, and the book started me down a path of reading Liane Moriarty’s books. Of course, I had to read her newest novel:
Book Read: Nine Perfect Strangers
Author: Liane Moriarty
Number of Books Read, 2019 Edition: 15
Frances Welty fell victim to an Internet dating scam. Heartbroken and in need of a break, at the advice of a friend, she signs up for a 10 day cleanse at the Tranquillum House.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>IOU ... a Post</title>
      <link>https://anotheryearofbooks.com/2019/04/iou-...-a-post/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 25 Apr 2019 18:10:00 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://anotheryearofbooks.com/2019/04/iou-...-a-post/</guid>
      <description>Is this year flying by, or is it just me? It seems there is never enough time for reading, writing, running, laundry, the packing list I’ve been meaning to start. It feels like a week ago that my boyfriend and I booked our vacation. Now it’s less than 20 days away… all this makes me think I better get moving on this list of books.
Book Read: I Owe You</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>It’s BOGO Day on Another Year of Books</title>
      <link>https://anotheryearofbooks.com/2019/04/its-bogo-day-on-another-year-of-books/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Apr 2019 17:04:00 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://anotheryearofbooks.com/2019/04/its-bogo-day-on-another-year-of-books/</guid>
      <description>Last weekend, we ventured to Texas for a wedding. The wedding was spectacular, the bride was beautiful, and the BBQ was delicious. In the words of my BFF, 10/10. Sitting in an airport, then flying home gives me the perfect excuse to read. I was determined to finish Girl, Stop Apologizing before we left. Luckily, I did, so I could read More Than Words while we dealt with a two hour delay before getting home.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>No, Not the Morgan Freeman Movie</title>
      <link>https://anotheryearofbooks.com/2019/04/no-not-the-morgan-freeman-movie/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Apr 2019 17:49:00 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://anotheryearofbooks.com/2019/04/no-not-the-morgan-freeman-movie/</guid>
      <description>I am sure I’ve mentioned this before, but I keep an ever-growing list of books I want to read on my phone. It just makes it easier when I go to the library to pick a new one, or when I find one at a bookstore and don’t want to buy it just yet. Slowly, I’ve been dwindling it down, only to have it shoot back up, but a new tactic: request the books from the library so you can keep reading.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A History Lesson</title>
      <link>https://anotheryearofbooks.com/2019/03/a-history-lesson/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Mar 2019 18:08:00 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://anotheryearofbooks.com/2019/03/a-history-lesson/</guid>
      <description>In the 8th grade, our teacher gave us each an assignment - a book report written about a book focused on the Holocaust. I still remember mine - a collection of stories, each about a different race or religion impacted. I remember reading it, and visiting the Holocaust Museum as we wrapped up the lesson (that includes a group of 8th grade girls offering to sing Baby Got Back in order get on the radio&amp;hellip; only to end up in a tunnel when we had our shot).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>You Remind Me of Sunshine</title>
      <link>https://anotheryearofbooks.com/2019/03/you-remind-me-of-sunshine/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 Mar 2019 19:08:00 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://anotheryearofbooks.com/2019/03/you-remind-me-of-sunshine/</guid>
      <description>I enjoy a good sequel. There are always some good ones, and there are also some bad ones. Like movies, some books don’t need sequels but you get them anyway. For others, a sequel or companion never hurt anybody. Case in point: book #9 for 2019.
Book Read: Puddin’
Author: Julie Murphy
Number of Books Read, 2019 Edition: 9
Millie Michalchuk took a chance and signed up for the Miss Blue Bonnet Teen Pageant in Dumplin’.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Take a Chance, Take a-take a Chance-Chance, Take a Chance, Take a Chance</title>
      <link>https://anotheryearofbooks.com/2019/03/take-a-chance-take-a-take-a-chance-chance-take-a-chance-take-a-chance/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Mar 2019 17:07:00 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://anotheryearofbooks.com/2019/03/take-a-chance-take-a-take-a-chance-chance-take-a-chance-take-a-chance/</guid>
      <description>Daylight savings time. It&amp;rsquo;s amazing how one hour can make a difference. By difference, I mean make you annoyed that it&amp;rsquo;s dark when you go to work, or you&amp;rsquo;re just tired for the next few days. That sounds like a good opportunity to read a new book (or blog) before you fall asleep.
Book Read: This is Your Life, Harriet Chance!
Author: Jonathan Evison
Number of Books Read, 2019 Edition: 8</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>You can tell she&#39;s a good dancer by the way she drinks her soda pop.</title>
      <link>https://anotheryearofbooks.com/2019/03/you-can-tell-shes-a-good-dancer-by-the-way-she-drinks-her-soda-pop./</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 03 Mar 2019 14:06:00 -0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://anotheryearofbooks.com/2019/03/you-can-tell-shes-a-good-dancer-by-the-way-she-drinks-her-soda-pop./</guid>
      <description>The bargain finds section of Barnes and Noble occasionally has some gems that either sound interesting or have been on my list to read. So some weekends, I just like to browse. For my seventh of read of 2019, I just happened to pick one up that had a fun cover.
Book Read: The Decent Proposal
Author: Kemper Donovan
Number of Books Read, 2019 Edition: 7
In The Decent Proposal, two strangers are given an interesting proposal - if they spend 2 hours a week together for the next year, they’ll split a million dollars.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Take a Breath and Let the Rest Come Easy</title>
      <link>https://anotheryearofbooks.com/2019/02/take-a-breath-and-let-the-rest-come-easy/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 23 Feb 2019 13:51:00 -0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://anotheryearofbooks.com/2019/02/take-a-breath-and-let-the-rest-come-easy/</guid>
      <description>Rom-coms. Admit it or not, everyone occasionally likes them, book or movie. The books are usually a quick read, and pass the time. So when I felt behind on the number of books, reading one seemed like a good way to catch up. One author rarely lets me down.
Book Read: Every Breath
Author: Nicholas Sparks
Number of Books Read, 2019 Edition: 6
Hope Anderson and Tru Wells have never met.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>In Family We Trust (Maybe?)</title>
      <link>https://anotheryearofbooks.com/2019/02/in-family-we-trust-maybe/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 Feb 2019 14:27:00 -0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://anotheryearofbooks.com/2019/02/in-family-we-trust-maybe/</guid>
      <description>It&amp;rsquo;s been awhile since my last post. I&amp;rsquo;ll make no excuses. Maybe I&amp;rsquo;ve taken the bus a few times less than normal recently. Maybe I&amp;rsquo;ve spent some nights just watching Seinfeld (only 119 episodes more to go). Or maybe, it&amp;rsquo;s because this book took exactly two weeks to read. That&amp;rsquo;s not an excuse, right?
Book Read: Family Trust
Author: Kathy Wang
Number of Books Read, 2019 Edition: 5
Patriarch Stanley Huang has been recently diagnosed with pancreatic cancer and his death is soon approaching.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Pour Myself a Cup of Ambition</title>
      <link>https://anotheryearofbooks.com/2019/02/pour-myself-a-cup-of-ambition/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Feb 2019 12:38:00 -0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://anotheryearofbooks.com/2019/02/pour-myself-a-cup-of-ambition/</guid>
      <description>I admit, I went against my normal principle of reading the book before watching the movie for this one. I couldn’t help it! The Netflix movie got my attention. So I backtracked…
Book Read: Dumplin’
Author: Julie Murphy
Number of Books Read, 2019 Edition: 4
Willowdean Dickson, aka Dumplin’, is growing up in a town that lives for its Miss Teen Blue Bonnet beauty pageant. Her mom is the perfect example - a former winner, she runs the pageant and has been wearing her victory dress since she won (will it fit this year?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>And the Winner Is...</title>
      <link>https://anotheryearofbooks.com/2019/01/and-the-winner-is.../</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 Jan 2019 17:52:00 -0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://anotheryearofbooks.com/2019/01/and-the-winner-is.../</guid>
      <description>When the weather is as bad as it has been in western PA (if you don’t live here, just let me tell you, it has not been good), all I want to do is curl up in a blanket and read (or watch Netflix - both are acceptable). But I still have to go to work, so I find a little joy in getting to the bus stop three minutes before it pulls up, finding a seat, and pulling out my current read for the next 30 minutes.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Do You Remember, the 21st Night of December?</title>
      <link>https://anotheryearofbooks.com/2019/01/do-you-remember-the-21st-night-of-december/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 19 Jan 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://anotheryearofbooks.com/2019/01/do-you-remember-the-21st-night-of-december/</guid>
      <description>I’m 26 years old, and every year, I’m still asked what’s on my Christmas list. The answer is usually pretty standard: money, something I’ve been putting off buying, and books. Becoming was a Christmas gift (thanks, Mom), as was this next read (thanks, Aunt Barb), and the one after this (again, thanks Aunt Barb). My philosophy: there is plenty of room on my bookshelf, so no amount of books is too many.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2019 is Becoming a Good One</title>
      <link>https://anotheryearofbooks.com/2019/01/2019-is-becoming-a-good-one/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 13 Jan 2019 08:33:00 -0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://anotheryearofbooks.com/2019/01/2019-is-becoming-a-good-one/</guid>
      <description>It’s been awhile. At least it seems like it. 2019 is here, holiday decorations are coming down, the weather is see-sawing and can’t make up its mind, and right now, in Pennsylvania, it’s, frankly, frigid as heck.
I’ve still been reading, just not typing. We’re also trying to build a 1500 piece puzzle (as you can see, it’s a slow process over 3 weeks in).

But the first book of 2019 is officially complete.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Another Year of Books: The 2018 Recap</title>
      <link>https://anotheryearofbooks.com/2018/12/another-year-of-books-the-2018-recap/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 28 Dec 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://anotheryearofbooks.com/2018/12/another-year-of-books-the-2018-recap/</guid>
      <description>Well, 2019 is approaching, surely and quickly, and there’s nothing we can do to slow it down. As 2018 comes to a close, and the goal is officially complete (and then some), it felt like it was time to think back, remember to the good days (or reads), and the bad ones (again, or reads), especially when we are all feeling like this:
I had to dig a little deep to remember which books I liked the most, because there were so many of them.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Class Dismissed.</title>
      <link>https://anotheryearofbooks.com/2018/12/class-dismissed./</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 16 Dec 2018 17:42:00 -0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://anotheryearofbooks.com/2018/12/class-dismissed./</guid>
      <description>In January, it all began with an Elin Hilderbrand book. Well, actually it began with multiple Elin Hilderbrand books. It seemed fitting that my 52nd read should be her latest winter novel. On Black Friday, thanks to Amazon, it was purchased. Then it laid around waiting to be read.
So without further ado, the 52nd read of 2018.
Book Read: Winter in Paradise
Author: Elin Hilderbrand
Number of Books Read: 52</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Small Admissions? I Think Not</title>
      <link>https://anotheryearofbooks.com/2018/12/small-admissions-i-think-not/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 10 Dec 2018 17:21:00 -0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://anotheryearofbooks.com/2018/12/small-admissions-i-think-not/</guid>
      <description>This past week seemed to calm down. Only plan was to do some Christmas shopping. Thank goodness my list is small. Maybe next year everyone will get a print out of this blog accompanied by a book? Just a thought.
Book Read: Small Admissions
Authors: Amy Poeppel
Number of Books Read: 51
After being dumped at the Paris airport by her “almost” fiancé, Kate finds herself in a serious slump. Her sister and friends are worried about her mental health.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Harder than a Bag of Bricks, This One</title>
      <link>https://anotheryearofbooks.com/2018/12/harder-than-a-bag-of-bricks-this-one/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 04 Dec 2018 16:58:00 -0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://anotheryearofbooks.com/2018/12/harder-than-a-bag-of-bricks-this-one/</guid>
      <description>We all know the holiday season is busy. It never seems like there is enough time to shop, bake, cook and wrap. Add in a book that seems to drag. Trust me, it does not help this time of year.
Book Read: How Hard Can It Be?
Authors: Allison Pearson
Number of Books Read: 50
Kate Reddy’s life has changed - her adorable kids are now teenagers obsessed with video games and selfies, her family relocated to a house in need of serious work, and her husband, Richard, has decided that bicycling and therapy are better than his job as an architect.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A Power Couple Writes a Book</title>
      <link>https://anotheryearofbooks.com/2018/11/a-power-couple-writes-a-book/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 24 Nov 2018 06:14:00 -0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://anotheryearofbooks.com/2018/11/a-power-couple-writes-a-book/</guid>
      <description>When I found myself at the library one day at lunch (again), I couldn&amp;rsquo;t not pick this one up. I mean look at the cover:

See what I mean?
**
It’s Karen (also Tammy) and Ron (also the Plumber) telling their story. Each has their own books but this one was different. The two come together to tell:**
Book Read: The Greatest Love Story Ever Told
Authors: Megan Mullally &amp;amp; Nick Offerman</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ignore the Long Title. It&#39;s Worth It.</title>
      <link>https://anotheryearofbooks.com/2018/11/ignore-the-long-title.-its-worth-it./</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 18 Nov 2018 06:13:00 -0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://anotheryearofbooks.com/2018/11/ignore-the-long-title.-its-worth-it./</guid>
      <description>It’s becoming more and more difficult to pick which book I read. Since I’m on the last leg of 52 for the year, I feel as if I should make sure they are good ones (PS - this one worked out in my favor). But my time for reading 52 this year is quickly dwindling. I feel like I woke up one morning and it was Halloween, and the next thing I knew I was figuring out what I’m doing on Turkey Day.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What’s Behind Door #1?</title>
      <link>https://anotheryearofbooks.com/2018/11/whats-behind-door-#1/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 Nov 2018 17:45:00 -0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://anotheryearofbooks.com/2018/11/whats-behind-door-#1/</guid>
      <description>Surprise! It’s already mid-November. The year is continuing to fly by. I’m looking forward to the Christmas cookies, and Thanksgiving dinner. Not looking forward to thinking about Christmas gifts. Too soon, Father Time, too soon. But on another note, not too many books left to read!

A picture&amp;hellip; of fall.
Book Read: Surprise Me
Author: Sophie Kinsella
Number of Books Read: 47
Sylvie and Dan are comfortable. Comfortable in their marriage, their jobs, and at home with their two daughters.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Queue “Save The Last Dance for Me”</title>
      <link>https://anotheryearofbooks.com/2018/11/queue-save-the-last-dance-for-me/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Nov 2018 08:00:00 -0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://anotheryearofbooks.com/2018/11/queue-save-the-last-dance-for-me/</guid>
      <description>I saw this book at Target once, and added it to my list to read. Target is great for this by the way - gives you an excuse to go pick up a few items you need. I then forgot I saw it at Half Price Books, bought it, and put it on my bookshelf…I then borrowed it from the library and read that copy.
It took me until 5 days after I finished this book (and another) to realize what I had done.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>No Sleep Till Brooklyn</title>
      <link>https://anotheryearofbooks.com/2018/10/no-sleep-till-brooklyn/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 30 Oct 2018 07:00:00 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://anotheryearofbooks.com/2018/10/no-sleep-till-brooklyn/</guid>
      <description>It’s the end of October, and we are on book number 45. I can see the end in sight - pending I get to the library at lunch today because I have nothing to read on the bus. Can we do it? I’m thinking we can.
Book Read: Halsey Street
Author: Naima Coster
Number of Books Read: 45
Penelope moves to Pittsburgh after an explosive fight with her mother, looking to make it as an artist.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Advice Found Here</title>
      <link>https://anotheryearofbooks.com/2018/10/advice-found-here/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 21 Oct 2018 08:00:00 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://anotheryearofbooks.com/2018/10/advice-found-here/</guid>
      <description>It’s fall already. FALL. Time for boots, pumpkin patches, and being cold waiting for the bus. This year is flying by, as it usually does. Maybe it’s all the stuff going on, or maybe it’s because I’ve read book #44 already and can (hopefully) see the end in sight.

Book Read: Dear Mrs. Bird
Author: AJ Pearce
Number of Books Read: 44
It’s London in the middle of World War II.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>It’s the Final Countdown</title>
      <link>https://anotheryearofbooks.com/2018/10/its-the-final-countdown/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Oct 2018 09:00:00 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://anotheryearofbooks.com/2018/10/its-the-final-countdown/</guid>
      <description>Completing this read means there’s less than 10 books to go until I can call this mission complete. It’s the beginning of October so I have hope. But it’s officially the final countdown. Good or bad, we read on.
Book Read: The Woman in Cabin 10
Author: Ruth Ware
Number of Books Read: 43
Lo is a travel journalist looking for more opportunities. When her boss is unable to make a press tour of a new luxury cruise ship, Lo is given one of the best opportunities of her career.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Did You Miss Me?</title>
      <link>https://anotheryearofbooks.com/2018/10/did-you-miss-me/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Oct 2018 09:00:00 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://anotheryearofbooks.com/2018/10/did-you-miss-me/</guid>
      <description>The past two weeks have been busy, so I’ve been MIA for awhile. First my sister got married (that wore me out for days), then this next book was decently long, then there were concerts to go to, plays to usher and a new car to be bought. But we are back and after this, we only have ten more till the goal!
 
Book Read: Miss You
Author: Kate Eberlen</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>“Ryan Started the Fire!”</title>
      <link>https://anotheryearofbooks.com/2018/09/ryan-started-the-fire/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 21 Sep 2018 06:30:00 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://anotheryearofbooks.com/2018/09/ryan-started-the-fire/</guid>
      <description>“We didn&amp;rsquo;t start the fire
It was always burning
Since the world&amp;rsquo;s been turning.”
But wait, in this case, someone did start the little fires.
Book Read: Little Fires Everywhere
Author: Celeste Ng
Number of Books Read: 41
In Shaker Heights, everything has a purpose, and it’s planned. Shaker was built on it. When Mia Warren and her daughter Pearl arrive in town, one family will never be the same.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>You Can’t Always Get What You Want</title>
      <link>https://anotheryearofbooks.com/2018/09/you-cant-always-get-what-you-want/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 19 Sep 2018 07:30:00 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://anotheryearofbooks.com/2018/09/you-cant-always-get-what-you-want/</guid>
      <description>I was supposed to pick a happier book to read for number 40. After all the suspenseful, slightly disturbing reads, my boyfriend told me it would be a good idea. This read has a happy ending but is pretty socially relevant all at the same time.
Book Read: All We Ever Wanted
Author: Emily Giffin
Number of Books Read: 40
Emily Giffin’s latest novel is written in the point of view of three people - Nina, whose son has done something really stupid, Tom, whose daughter is impacted by this stupidity, and Lyla, who just wants to get through high school.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Thank Goodness This Isn’t My Neighborhood</title>
      <link>https://anotheryearofbooks.com/2018/09/thank-goodness-this-isnt-my-neighborhood/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 12 Sep 2018 08:30:00 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://anotheryearofbooks.com/2018/09/thank-goodness-this-isnt-my-neighborhood/</guid>
      <description>My boyfriend and I bought a townhouse a few months back, so when we say we have neighbors, they is no yard to separate us. Luckily, we like them.
Book Read: The Couple Next Door
Author: Shari Lapena
Number of Books Read: 39
Anne and Marco Conti go to a dinner party next door. They decide it’s best to leave their newborn daughter at home, checking on her with a clockwork-like schedule.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tell Me Something I Don’t Know</title>
      <link>https://anotheryearofbooks.com/2018/09/tell-me-something-i-dont-know/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 06 Sep 2018 08:30:00 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://anotheryearofbooks.com/2018/09/tell-me-something-i-dont-know/</guid>
      <description>Imagine you think your husband is a serial killer. Actually you’re convinced he is because you keep finding evidence it may be true. How would you react?
My guess: probably not well. Not well at all.
Book Read: Tell Me I’m Wrong
Author: Adam Croft
Number of Books Read: 38
Megan Miller thought her life was normal. She and her husband, an elementary school teacher, seem happy with their newborn daughter.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>In The Sky With Diamonds</title>
      <link>https://anotheryearofbooks.com/2018/08/in-the-sky-with-diamonds/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 30 Aug 2018 17:30:00 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://anotheryearofbooks.com/2018/08/in-the-sky-with-diamonds/</guid>
      <description>Sometimes, I don’t have a reason for picking up at pickup at the library. If it’s not a book on my ever-growing iPhone list titled “Books,” it may be someone, somewhere told me to read it. Or in this case, the cover reminds be of a Fredrik Backman novel. That alone is enough to make me read a book.
Book Read: We Own the Sky
Author: Luke Allnutt
Number of Books Read: 37</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>That&#39;s My Name. Don&#39;t Wear It Out.</title>
      <link>https://anotheryearofbooks.com/2018/08/thats-my-name.-dont-wear-it-out./</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 24 Aug 2018 08:30:00 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://anotheryearofbooks.com/2018/08/thats-my-name.-dont-wear-it-out./</guid>
      <description>Ever since I saw the movie version of The Notebook before I read the book (loved both by the way), I have always tried to read books before I watch the movie. See The Mountain Between Us as an example. This movie had serious Oscar buzz, but let’s not let that stray us from tradition here.
Book Read: Call Me By Your Name
Author: Andre Aciman
Number of Books Read: 36</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Seven Days Can Be a Long Time</title>
      <link>https://anotheryearofbooks.com/2018/08/seven-days-can-be-a-long-time/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 12 Aug 2018 17:00:00 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://anotheryearofbooks.com/2018/08/seven-days-can-be-a-long-time/</guid>
      <description>I mentioned I read two books during my weekend of relaxation in Sea Isle City. You already know I liked the first - did I like the second? Considering I read both in 6 days, you probably can guess. But let’s talk about it anyway. So picture you’re sitting here with this view, and read on!

Book Read: Seven Days of Us
Author: Francesca Hornak
Number of Books Read: 35</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Here Comes the Bride (maybe?)</title>
      <link>https://anotheryearofbooks.com/2018/08/here-comes-the-bride-maybe/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 Aug 2018 08:30:00 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://anotheryearofbooks.com/2018/08/here-comes-the-bride-maybe/</guid>
      <description>I spent this past weekend completely relaxed on vacation in Sea Isle City, NJ. My plans consisted of eating, drinking, walking, sitting in the sand with SPF 50 on, and reading a book or two. All objectives: met.
My boyfriend’s objectives: take some photos with his drone. Objective: met.

Spoiler: two books were read during the weekend - but let’s only focus on one for now.)
Book Read: The Perfect Couple</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Teach Them to Fly (or Roar)</title>
      <link>https://anotheryearofbooks.com/2018/08/teach-them-to-fly-or-roar/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 Aug 2018 07:00:00 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://anotheryearofbooks.com/2018/08/teach-them-to-fly-or-roar/</guid>
      <description>Most of us understand being in a sports town. Whether it’s football, soccer, hockey, curling or any other sort, we understand it. Beartown looks like Pittsburgh on steroids when it comes to hockey. And that’s saying something.
Book Read: Us Against You
Author: Fredrik Backman
Number of Books Read: 33
Spoilers ahead: stop here, go borrow Beartown from your local library, then come back to finish reading this post. Us Against You is a sequel, and while you could probably read one without the other, I highly suggest you go in order.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Week and a Half I Wanted a Book to Fall Apart</title>
      <link>https://anotheryearofbooks.com/2018/07/the-week-and-a-half-i-wanted-a-book-to-fall-apart/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Jul 2018 05:12:00 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://anotheryearofbooks.com/2018/07/the-week-and-a-half-i-wanted-a-book-to-fall-apart/</guid>
      <description>I very rarely give up on a book. I can probably actually count on one hand how many times I haven&amp;rsquo;t finished a book I started. So I forced myself to finish book 32, with many complaints about it along the way.
Book Read: The Summer We Fell Apart
Author: Robin Antalek
Number of Books Read: 32
I picked this one up at the library book sale, and luckily only spent a single dollar on it.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Queue the Pretty Little Liars Theme Song</title>
      <link>https://anotheryearofbooks.com/2018/07/queue-the-pretty-little-liars-theme-song/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Jul 2018 08:30:00 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://anotheryearofbooks.com/2018/07/queue-the-pretty-little-liars-theme-song/</guid>
      <description>“Got a secret,
Can you keep it?
Swear this one you’ll save.
Better lock it, in your pocket
Taking this one to the grave.”
Keep in mind, all I know about Pretty Liars is this theme song. I once tried to watch it with my sister and she became so annoyed with my questions, told me not to watch it and I’m pretty sure changed the channel.
I only bring it up because the theme song was constantly playing in my head as I read book #31 of 2018.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Take This Book to the Beach</title>
      <link>https://anotheryearofbooks.com/2018/07/take-this-book-to-the-beach/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Jul 2018 17:29:00 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://anotheryearofbooks.com/2018/07/take-this-book-to-the-beach/</guid>
      <description>Another library book find, another book that really is a beach read. While reading this book on the bus daily, I found myself wishing it were August so I could be sitting in the sand, SPF 75 on, a book in hand with the ocean in view.
Book Read: Falling Together
Author: Maria de los Santos
Number of Books Read: 30
Pen, Will and Cat became instant friends in college. They were so inseparable that people thought, well, they were all “together” if you catch my drift.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>But Will The Glass Castle Look Like the One in Frozen?</title>
      <link>https://anotheryearofbooks.com/2018/07/but-will-the-glass-castle-look-like-the-one-in-frozen/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 Jul 2018 09:00:00 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://anotheryearofbooks.com/2018/07/but-will-the-glass-castle-look-like-the-one-in-frozen/</guid>
      <description>Another Beaver library book sale find, and another book to read before watching the movie. Except unlike my last read, this one is a memoir by a woman who has had an adventure of a life.
Book Read: The Glass Castle
Author: Jeannette Walls
Number of Books Read: 29
Jeannette Walls’ family is different, to say the least. Vibrant is another good way to describe them and their adventures. Her mother and father are free spirits who rather “skedaddle” than sit still.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Cause Baby There Ain’t No Mountain High Enough</title>
      <link>https://anotheryearofbooks.com/2018/06/cause-baby-there-aint-no-mountain-high-enough/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Jun 2018 17:41:00 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://anotheryearofbooks.com/2018/06/cause-baby-there-aint-no-mountain-high-enough/</guid>
      <description>But maybe, there actually is? The Beaver library’s annual book sale came in for the win again when I found the next read just lying around, waiting to be purchased (along with about 8 others that filled my bag). I’m a big believer in reading the book before you see the movie based on it (did it in reverse for The Notebook and we all know that movie is fantastic). So when I found this next read, I had to buy it.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Give Me a Beach Read and I’ll Want to Be at the Beach</title>
      <link>https://anotheryearofbooks.com/2018/06/give-me-a-beach-read-and-ill-want-to-be-at-the-beach/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 Jun 2018 08:30:00 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://anotheryearofbooks.com/2018/06/give-me-a-beach-read-and-ill-want-to-be-at-the-beach/</guid>
      <description>This book was a hand-me down, which always seems to work out well for me. This one went from Massachusetts to Brooklyn to Carnegie (and will probably go to Beaver next). It reminded me a book that you would read while sitting on a beach chair, feet in the water, SPF 50 on and getting some sun. (Or maybe SPF 75 - your call).
Book Read: The Glass Kitchen
Author: Linda Francis Lee</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Every Family Has Its Secrets. This One is No Different</title>
      <link>https://anotheryearofbooks.com/2018/06/every-family-has-its-secrets.-this-one-is-no-different/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 09 Jun 2018 12:50:00 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://anotheryearofbooks.com/2018/06/every-family-has-its-secrets.-this-one-is-no-different/</guid>
      <description>This book has been on my list for a while now. It worked out that one day in the Big Apple while visiting my sister and her fiancé, it rained. We looked for something to do. Matt suggested the Amazon Book store…. yes the Amazon book store (NYC has these things). Perfect opportunity to buy a new book, no?
Book Read: Everything I Never Told You
Author: Celeste Ng
Number of Books Read: 26 (the halfway point!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>It’s Been Awhile…</title>
      <link>https://anotheryearofbooks.com/2018/06/its-been-awhile/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Jun 2018 08:30:00 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://anotheryearofbooks.com/2018/06/its-been-awhile/</guid>
      <description>I haven’t posted anything for two weeks… I know, two weeks is a long time. What have I been doing in these two weeks you may ask? Visiting my sister and her fiancé in Brooklyn, working, getting settled in our new house, and reading. That’s right, this one took me two full weeks to read.
Book Read: The Sparsholt Affair
Author: Alan Hollinghurst
Number of Books Read: 25
This another “Emily went to the library at lunch and picked up a book.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Promise Me You’ll Think About Reading It</title>
      <link>https://anotheryearofbooks.com/2018/05/promise-me-youll-think-about-reading-it/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 16 May 2018 08:30:00 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://anotheryearofbooks.com/2018/05/promise-me-youll-think-about-reading-it/</guid>
      <description>I have no desire to bring politics into Another Year of Books. I promise not to preach to you if you promise not to preach to me. When I picked up my latest read, there were many reasons and very few were political. The most important one being I heard it was a really well written book.
Book Read: Promise Me, Dad
Author: Joe Biden
Number of Books Read: 24</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>You Write It, I&#39;ll Read It</title>
      <link>https://anotheryearofbooks.com/2018/05/you-write-it-ill-read-it/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 11 May 2018 08:30:00 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://anotheryearofbooks.com/2018/05/you-write-it-ill-read-it/</guid>
      <description>Not going to lie… my reading has been suffering some. Between buying a house, moving into said house, and running a half marathon, my focus has been on other things. Reading a book of short stories helped some – more stop and go then others.
Book Read: YouThink It, I’ll Say It
Author: Curtis Sittenfield
Number of Books Read: 23
I’ve read a couple of Sittenfield’s books previously (Prep, Eligible) so when I was wandering the library (after work this time, not a lunch) and saw this one, I figured she wouldn’t lead me astray.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>I Now Understand Why HBO Made This a Show</title>
      <link>https://anotheryearofbooks.com/2018/05/i-now-understand-why-hbo-made-this-a-show/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 05 May 2018 06:30:00 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://anotheryearofbooks.com/2018/05/i-now-understand-why-hbo-made-this-a-show/</guid>
      <description>I’m sure most of you have heard of it. It swept awards shows, Nicole Kidman gave a few speeches, so did Laura Dern. And drumroll please… Meryl will be on season 2 (MERYL!), which takes us to book number 22…
Book Read: Big Little Lies
Author: Liane Moriarty
Number of Books Read: 22
A coworker recommended I read Moriarty’s The Husband’s Secret, so I went hunting for it at the library.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Every Note Leads to Every Page</title>
      <link>https://anotheryearofbooks.com/2018/04/every-note-leads-to-every-page/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Apr 2018 19:30:00 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://anotheryearofbooks.com/2018/04/every-note-leads-to-every-page/</guid>
      <description>Let me start with one note… I read this book in two day. Two days. Two days of wishing the bus ride was longer so I could keep reading, two days of reading before falling asleep (which I usually don’t do anymore), two days of a great read. And away we go&amp;hellip;
Book Read: Every Note Played
Author: Lisa Genova
Number of Books Read: 21
If the two days comment didn’t tell you I liked this book, I’m not sure what will.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>She Isn’t a Nobody Anymore</title>
      <link>https://anotheryearofbooks.com/2018/04/she-isnt-a-nobody-anymore/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Apr 2018 08:30:00 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://anotheryearofbooks.com/2018/04/she-isnt-a-nobody-anymore/</guid>
      <description>You know her from Into the Woods, Pitch Perfect and Trolls. Maybe you even remember she was in Twilight (I do). Apparently she also wrote a book!
Book Read: Scrappy Little Nobody
Author: Anna Kendrick
Number of Books Read: 20
My sister Meghan was kind enough to lug Scrappy Little Nobody all the way from Brooklyn so I figured I’d give it a go. Nice of me, huh?
Anna Kendrick has stories to tell.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>They’re Still Rich… and Still Crazy</title>
      <link>https://anotheryearofbooks.com/2018/04/theyre-still-rich-and-still-crazy/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 15 Apr 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://anotheryearofbooks.com/2018/04/theyre-still-rich-and-still-crazy/</guid>
      <description>I know it has been awhile - almost 2 weeks to be exact. But, when I went to the library (not at lunch this time – big change for me!) when I was almost done with my last read, I picked up not 1, but 2 books, and they were meant to be read and talked about together. So here you go – a two for one post.
 Book Read: China Rich Girlfriend &amp;amp; Rich People Problems</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A Book that Speaks to My Appetite</title>
      <link>https://anotheryearofbooks.com/2018/04/a-book-that-speaks-to-my-appetite/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 03 Apr 2018 08:30:00 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://anotheryearofbooks.com/2018/04/a-book-that-speaks-to-my-appetite/</guid>
      <description>An autobiography that ties almost every story back to food? Check. A book that has recipes about these experiences at the end of every section? Check. Another random find at the library? Check. A book for you to read? Check.
Book Read: Blue Plate Special: An Autobiography of My Appetites
Author: Kate Christensen
Number of Books Read: 17
Kate Christensen has had a lot of experiences, all which shaped her life.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Well, Plot Twist... You Got Me</title>
      <link>https://anotheryearofbooks.com/2018/03/well-plot-twist...-you-got-me/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 26 Mar 2018 08:30:00 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://anotheryearofbooks.com/2018/03/well-plot-twist...-you-got-me/</guid>
      <description>I didn&amp;rsquo;t know what to expect for this one. I picked it up at the library’s new bookshelf, drawn to the colorful cover and the description in the flap (I know, something new for me). Did I see this ending coming? Nope. I usually can guess, which means this was a well written novel.
Book Read: Speak No Evil
Author: Uzodinma Iweala
Number of Books Read: 16
Niru’s parents are conservative Nigerians, who came to the US hoping to give the family a better life.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A Room Can Be a Scary Place</title>
      <link>https://anotheryearofbooks.com/2018/03/a-room-can-be-a-scary-place/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Mar 2018 08:30:00 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://anotheryearofbooks.com/2018/03/a-room-can-be-a-scary-place/</guid>
      <description>This one has been on my bookshelf for a year or two. I picked it up at my local library’s annual book sale because I heard it was a great novel and a great movie. So when I accidently picked up a book I had already read, I went to the shelf and Room caught my eye.
Book Read: Room
Author: Emma Donoghue
Number of Books Read: 15
Most probably know of it… Room, the Oscar nominated/winning movie based on the novel about a woman, Joy “Ma,” who is being held against her own will, and her young son, Jack, who knows nothing but the Room they are in, and their journey to see the outside world.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A Rose is a Rose is a Rose is a Rosie</title>
      <link>https://anotheryearofbooks.com/2018/03/a-rose-is-a-rose-is-a-rose-is-a-rosie/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Mar 2018 08:30:00 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://anotheryearofbooks.com/2018/03/a-rose-is-a-rose-is-a-rose-is-a-rosie/</guid>
      <description>Books with the name Rosie in the title catch my eye. It’s probably because I really liked The Rosie Project. While in the middle of my last read, I once again found myself at the library during lunch, picking out the next one. This one was on the new book shelf, caught my eye, and here we are, book number 14 of 2018.
Book Read: Rosie Colored Glasses
Author: Brianna Wolfson</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Name &#34;Tom Hanks&#34; Got Me…</title>
      <link>https://anotheryearofbooks.com/2018/03/the-name-tom-hanks-got-me/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Mar 2018 08:30:00 -0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://anotheryearofbooks.com/2018/03/the-name-tom-hanks-got-me/</guid>
      <description>T-Hanks… famous actor, director, producer, voice of Woody, most importantly star of one of my favorite movies You’ve Got Mail. Add author to the list and you&amp;rsquo;ve got book #13.
Book Read: Uncommon Type: Some Stories
Author: Tom Hanks
Number of Books Read: 13
Not going to lie, it took me about a week to read this book. At first, I thought it was because collections of fictional short stories may not be my thing, and it may be best to read one at a time rather than straight through.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Louisa Clark is Back, and Tougher than Ever</title>
      <link>https://anotheryearofbooks.com/2018/02/louisa-clark-is-back-and-tougher-than-ever/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 26 Feb 2018 09:30:00 -0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://anotheryearofbooks.com/2018/02/louisa-clark-is-back-and-tougher-than-ever/</guid>
      <description>When I read the third part of the Me Before You trilogy was due to come out, I had to have it right away because Louisa Clark’s story wasn’t over yet. I loved Me Before You, I loved After You. So I asked my BF, who has Amazon prime, to buy Still Me. After a purchase of the wrong book (way to go, Matt), the book was on its way and I was ready to read.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>This Next Book is Insane(ly Good)</title>
      <link>https://anotheryearofbooks.com/2018/02/this-next-book-is-insanely-good/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Feb 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://anotheryearofbooks.com/2018/02/this-next-book-is-insanely-good/</guid>
      <description>My sister is getting married. My best friend’s sister is also getting married. Yesterday when we met for lunch, we were comparing the size of the guest lists. But this book trumped us - the wedding of the century with 888 guests. Eight hundred and eighty eight. Wow, sorry Meghan for commenting on the size of yours.
 Book Read: Crazy Rich Asians
Author: Kevin Kwan
Number of Books Read: 11</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Turtles Will Get Ya</title>
      <link>https://anotheryearofbooks.com/2018/02/the-turtles-will-get-ya/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Feb 2018 08:30:00 -0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://anotheryearofbooks.com/2018/02/the-turtles-will-get-ya/</guid>
      <description>When I think of turtles, my mind goes to Sea Isle City, NJ. Why? Well, each year I visit, I see a turtle, they have signs about turtles crossing the road, and my cousin is a turtle whisperer. I realize these are not the turtles John Green had in mind, so I digress.
Book Read: Turtles All The Way Down
Author: John Green
Number of Books Read: 10
Technically, this is a “young adult” novel.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Where Are They? Do They Live Forever? I still have no idea…</title>
      <link>https://anotheryearofbooks.com/2018/02/where-are-they-do-they-live-forever-i-still-have-no-idea/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 Feb 2018 18:00:00 -0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://anotheryearofbooks.com/2018/02/where-are-they-do-they-live-forever-i-still-have-no-idea/</guid>
      <description>Since I read and loved Dave Egger’s The Circle a couple of years back, I have been trying to give him another chance_._ I finished _The Circle_ in one weekend on a girls’ trip to the beach, so I tried a few of his other books… no success. When I saw this one at the library (again at lunchtime), I decided to give it another go. It helped that the book was relatively short.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>I’m Glad… I Picked Up This Book</title>
      <link>https://anotheryearofbooks.com/2018/02/im-glad-i-picked-up-this-book/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 04 Feb 2018 17:00:00 -0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://anotheryearofbooks.com/2018/02/im-glad-i-picked-up-this-book/</guid>
      <description>Back to fiction we go with another Skimm recommendation. According to this novel, the Navajo do not have words for “I love you.” They believe that no one can possess another. Instead, they say “I’m glad about you” (I did consult the Google on this and can’t find any evidence to the contrary). Either way, a fitting title for this read. **Book Read: **I’m Glad About You
**Author: **Theresa Rebeck</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>12 Things I Would Like You to Tell Me More About</title>
      <link>https://anotheryearofbooks.com/2018/02/12-things-i-would-like-you-to-tell-me-more-about/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Feb 2018 08:30:00 -0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://anotheryearofbooks.com/2018/02/12-things-i-would-like-you-to-tell-me-more-about/</guid>
      <description>The 7th book of 2018, I picked up because the cover was colorful. I walked into the library, looked at the front tables, and it caught my eye. Unless it’s an author I have heard of, or someone recommended it to me, I usually struggle with the essay/memoir type of book (example: didn’t think twice about Anna Faris’s). Frankly, I tend to avoid them.
But – if you read the author information on the back sleeve, the author has been called the “voice of her generation” by O: The Oprah Magazine; when has Oprah ever been wrong?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Astonish Me… With Your Ballet Moves</title>
      <link>https://anotheryearofbooks.com/2018/01/astonish-me-with-your-ballet-moves/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 26 Jan 2018 08:30:00 -0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://anotheryearofbooks.com/2018/01/astonish-me-with-your-ballet-moves/</guid>
      <description>After my previous read, all I wanted was the next book to be light-hearted, not as challenging to read and to not fall asleep on the bus. Good news… I didn’t fall asleep once reading this one!
Book Read: Astonish Me
Author: Maggie Shipstead
Books Read: 6
I have had Shipstead’s other novel Seating Arrangements on my “to read” list for a while now, and haven’t picked it up yet. So when I was reading the Skimm’s recommendations and saw another by Shipstead, I looked for it at the library and picked it up, intrigued by the description that was focused on ballet.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>No One is Going to Save Me… From This Book</title>
      <link>https://anotheryearofbooks.com/2018/01/no-one-is-going-to-save-me-from-this-book/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 19 Jan 2018 08:00:00 -0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://anotheryearofbooks.com/2018/01/no-one-is-going-to-save-me-from-this-book/</guid>
      <description>I tend to find books as I’m wandering the library at lunch. Sometimes, if I can’t find a book on my “to read” list, I pick one based on the cover, the author, or if I saw other people looking at it. Usually, it works out pretty well. This one… I’m still not convinced that picking a book because Powell was in the author’s name was a good idea. You win some, you lose some.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Anna Faris Is, In Fact, Qualified</title>
      <link>https://anotheryearofbooks.com/2018/01/anna-faris-is-in-fact-qualified/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 13 Jan 2018 08:00:00 -0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://anotheryearofbooks.com/2018/01/anna-faris-is-in-fact-qualified/</guid>
      <description>I listen to the podcast Anna Faris is Unqualified religiously (seriously, once a week, just like going to church except the podcast comes out Tuesday mornings), so I was pretty excited when Anna Faris announced she was writing a book.
Book Read: Unqualified
Author: Anna Faris
**Number of Books Read:**4
I can’t tell you how many times I have actually laughed out loud while listening to this podcast at the gym (I mean come on, have you seen The House Bunny?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The First Three of 2018</title>
      <link>https://anotheryearofbooks.com/2018/01/the-first-three-of-2018/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Jan 2018 19:35:00 -0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://anotheryearofbooks.com/2018/01/the-first-three-of-2018/</guid>
      <description>I’ll start by saying this should probably be called the “first four” because it&amp;rsquo;s about a series, but since I finished the first on New Year’s Eve, we’ll go with the first three of 2018.
Books Read: Winter Stroll; Winter Storms; Winter Solstice
Author: Elin Hilderbrand
2018 Book Count: 3
First let me say, I am already a big fan of Elin Hilderbrand. Each book that I have read, I&amp;rsquo;ve enjoyed (The Identicals made it on the 2017 challenge list), so when my sister brought the 2 newest books in this series home over Christmas, I was ready to read.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Another Year of Books: The Beginning</title>
      <link>https://anotheryearofbooks.com/2018/01/another-year-of-books-the-beginning/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 07 Jan 2018 18:25:00 -0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://anotheryearofbooks.com/2018/01/another-year-of-books-the-beginning/</guid>
      <description>For as long as I can remember, I have loved to read. I remember a picture where I fell asleep with a Samantha American Girl doll book draped over my face. Reading was a hobby. Year after year, one book came after another.
Then college began, and reading fell on the priority list. Honestly, I don’t remember reading anything but textbooks and Facebook feeds during the school year (summers - replace textbooks with books and keep the Facebook feeds).</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>